<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <root> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint back Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint back Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Imprint back For questions about Biosynex Deutschland GmbH or the content of this website, including the editorial, please contact the below mentioned contact person. Biosynex Deutschland GmbH Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 37079 Goettingen, Germany Phone: +49 (0) 551 504 11 -0 Fax: +49 (0) 551 504 11 -29 Emal: info(ad)dima-diagnostika.com Internet: www.dima-diagnostika.com General Manager: Dr. Thierry Paper Seat and court of registration: Amtsgericht Göttingen Trade register: HRB 3176 VAT: DE208852195 Responsible editor: Stefan Raupach Technical support: 0711concept.de | Internet-Programmierung Stuttgart Disclaimer 1. Content The author reserves the right not to be responsible for the topicality, correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided. Liability claims regarding damage caused by the use of any information provided, including any kind of information which is incomplete or incorrect,will therefore be rejected. All offers are not-binding and without obligation. Parts of the pages or the complete publication including all offers and information might be extended, changed or partly or completely deleted by the author without separate announcement. 2. Referrals and links The author is not responsible for any contents linked or referred to from his pages - unless he has full knowledge of illegal contents and would be able to prevent the visitors of his site fromviewing those pages. If any damage occurs by the use of information presented there, only the author of the respective pages might be liable, not the one who has linked to these pages. Furthermore the author is not liable for any postings or messages published by users of discussion boards, guestbooks or mailinglists provided on his page. 3. Copyright The author intended not to use any copyrighted material for the publication or, if not possible, to indicate the copyright of the respective object. The copyright for any material created by the author is reserved. Any duplication or use of objects such as images, diagrams, sounds or texts other electronic or printed publications is not permitted without the author's agreement. 4. Privacy policy If the opportunity for the input of personal or business data (email addresses, name, addresses) is given, the input of these data takes place voluntarily. The use and payment of all offered services are permitted - if and far technically possible and reasonable - without specification of any personal data or under specification of anonymized data or alias. The use of published postal addresses, telephone or fax numbers and email addresses for marketing purposes is prohibited, offenders sending unwanted spam messages be punished. 5. Legal validity of this disclaimer This disclaimer is to be regarded as part of the internet publication which you were referred from. If sections or individual terms of this statement are not legal or correct, the content or validity of the other parts remain uninfluenced by this fact. Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Privacy back We take the protection of your personal information very seriously and observe strictly the rules of data protection laws. Personal data is collected, particular by the contact form on this website only for technical purposes. The company Biosynex Deutschland GmbH expressly states that no personal data be passed on to third parties without prior consent. This website uses Google Analytics, web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer, to analyze the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google server the U.S. and stored there. Google use this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other website activity and internet related services. In addition, Google may transfer this information to third parties, unless required by law or if third parties process the information on behalf of Google. Google not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, but we point out that you then probably cannot use all features of this website. By using this site you agree to the processing of data about you by Google the manner described above and for the purpose. Your confidence is important to us. Therefore, we gladly answer your questions regarding the processing of your personal data. If you have questions that are not answered by this privacy statement or if you wish to receive more detailed information, please feel free to contact us. Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Contact back For Information or Questions, please contact us: Biosynex Deutschland GmbH Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 37079 Göttingen Germany Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Fax: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -29 E-Mail: info(ad)biosynex.de Contact Privacy Imprint Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2014 back We look forward to seeing you at the following exhibitions and conferences at our booth. 28.02.2014 - 01.03.2014 Deutsches Forum für Sucht Kongress Palais Kassel Holger-Börner-Platz 1 - 34119 Kassel 07.03.2014 - 09.03.2014 20. Kongress für Jugendmedizin Unesco-Platz 1 - 99423 Weimar 21.05.2014 14. Hochstadter Gespräche Weitere Infos folgen 13.06.2014 - 15.06.2014 44. Kinder- Jugendärztetag 2014 Jahrestagung Berufsverbandes Kinder- Jugendärzte e.V. Berlin 08.10.2014- 11.10.2014 60. Kongress Deutschen Gesellschaft für Gynäkologie Geburtshilfe e.V. ICM – Internationales Congress Center München 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2015 back We look forward to seeing you at the following exhibitions and conferences at our booth. 02.09.2015 - 05.09.2015 111. Jahrestagung Deutschen Gesellschaft für Kinder- Jugendmedizin e.V. ICM – Internationales Congress Center München 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint 2013 back We look forward to seeing you at the following exhibitions and conferences at our booth. 12.–16.10.2013 41. Herbst-Seminar-Kongress Berufsverbandes Kinder Jugendärzte e.V. , Bad Orb 01.11. – 03.11.13 Suchtkongress Berlin 20.11.2013 – 23.11.2013 Medica Düsseldorf – Halle 3/H60 2015 2014 2013 Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint Our Service back Services - In-house development department - Professional advice regarding cross reactions and interactions - Scientific background knowledge - 24-month shelf-life of tests from the date of manufacture - Production of DOA multi-test combinations accordance with customer wishes* Quality - Biosynex Deutschland GmbH is certified accordance with ISO 9001 and ISO EN 13485 - Biosynex Deutschland GmbH products are CE-certified - Biosynex Deutschland GmbH products are user-friendly - Regular participation round-robin tests - Test results 95 % consistent with GC/MS (DOA) - What we develop, we produce and market ourselves * depending on order volumes About us Our Service Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Dima Gesellschaft für Diagnostika mbH - Drogentests Home Company About us Our Service News 2015 2014 2013 Contact Contact Privacy Imprint About us back Biosynex Deutschland GmbH has been reliable partner for diagnostics throughout the world for many years. We know the requirements of the various target groups inside out, and our development department is working constantly on new user-friendly procedures and rapid tests. As one of the most significant manufacturers of rapid membrane tests, we stand out from the crowd with our particularly high degree of flexibility and rapid action. We respond to the requirements of the market, and fulfill the special wishes of our customers. Maintaining constant dialogue with our customers enables us to respond reactively to problems and changes and to be able to offer products at all times with consistently high quality. Our main competences: Drugs of Abuse Tumor Marker Cardiac Marker Infectious Disease Fertility Proteins About us Our Service Biosynex Deutschland GmbH · Robert-Bosch-Breite 23 · 37079 Göttingen · Germany · Phone: +49 (0) 551 - 504 11 -0 Contact Data Protection Imprint </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> </fragment> </item> </root> 