<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <root> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} CORPORATE GROUP CHRONOLOGY CONTACT de fr ru cn Data Privacy Imprint In order to view this video, you need to download and install the latest version of Adobe Flash Player. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} Unternehmensgruppe Chronik Karriere Kontakt de fr ru cn Datenschutz Impressum Karriere HAUBER Wir erfolgreiche Unternehmensgruppe Textil- Bekleidungsindustriemit Geschäftsfeldern Damenoberbekleidung orthopädischeHilfsmittel. Wir freuen uns, Sie bewerben möchten! Leider derzeit offenen Stellen besetzen. Wenn Sie möchten, können Sie gerne Ihre Initiativbewerbung zukommen lassen. FERD. HAUBER GmbH Personalabteilung Weberstr. 1 72604 Nürtingen Tel: +49 (0) 7022/705-0 personal@hauber.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} Unternehmensgruppe Chronik Karriere Kontakt de fr ru cn Datenschutz Impressum Um Inhalt Seite sehen benötigen Sie Flash Player Version 9+ ! </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} Unternehmensgruppe Chronik Karriere Kontakt de fr ru cn Datenschutz Impressum Drei starke Marken. Die HAUBER GRUPPE, Nürtingen Die Marke LUISA CERANO punktet klar konturierten femininen Erscheinungsbild – Wachstumsraten über Branchendurchschnitt. Die Marke SPORLASTIC, führender deutscher Orthopädiehersteller, überträgt textile Kompetenz Hauses HAUBER medizinischen Bereich. Die Marke HAUBER, Label, Namen Gründers trägt, gestaltet modische Landschaft DOB-Bereich führend mit. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} 集团公司 发展历程 联系方式 cn de fr ru Data Privacy 制作公司 In order to view this video, you need to download and install the latest version of Adobe Flash Player. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} Группа предприятий Хроника КОНТАКТ ru de fr cn Data Privacy Реквизиты In order to view this video, you need to download and install the latest version of Adobe Flash Player. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} GROUPE D'ENTREPRISES CHRONIQUE CONTACT fr de ru cn Data Privacy Adresse In order to view this video, you need to download and install the latest version of Adobe Flash Player. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} CORPORATE GROUP CHRONOLOGY CONTACT de fr ru cn Data Privacy Imprint Three strong brands. The HAUBER GROUP, Nürtingen The LUISA CERANO brand gains the competitive edge with its clearly contoured feminine image – and growth rates above the industry average. The SPORLASTIC brand, leading German orthopaedic manufacturer transfers, HAUBER's textile skills to the medical field. HAUBER brand, the label which bears the founder's name, plays leading role shaping the womenswear fashion scene. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} 集团公司 发展历程 联系方式 cn de fr ru Data Privacy 制作公司 三大强势品牌 HAUBER 集团，座落于Nürtingen LUISA CERANO 品牌，因其很好地突显了女性的线条美而取得了竞争优势，其增长率超过了行业的平均水平。 SPORLASTIC 品牌，德国一处于领先地位的骨科用品生产商，把 HAUBER的纺织技术转移到医学领域。 HAUBER品牌，以创建者的名字命名，在引领女装时尚潮流方面处于领先地位。 </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} Группа предприятий Хроника КОНТАКТ ru de fr cn Data Privacy Реквизиты Три сильные марки. Группа HAUBER, Нюртинген Марка LUISA CERANO выигрывает за счет четко выраженного женственного образа и может похвастаться ростом оборота намного выше среднего в своей области. Марка SPORLASTIC, ведущий производитель ортопедических изделий, успешно применяет в медицине знания дома HAUBER в текстильной промышленности. Марка HAUBER, бренд, носящий имя своего создателя, формирует модный ландшафт в качестве одного из ведущих производителей женской одежды. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Die HAUBER GRUPPE Marken HAUBER COLLECTION, LUISA CERANO SPORLASTIC, Nürtingen body,td,th {font-size: 0.75em;}html, body {height:100%;} GROUPE D'ENTREPRISES CHRONIQUE CONTACT fr de ru cn Data Privacy Adresse Trois marques fortes. Le GROUPE HAUBER, Nürtingen La marque LUISA CERANO marque points avec présentation féminine aux contours clairs – et un taux de croissance largement supérieur à la moyenne de la branche. La marque SPORLASTIC, fabricant de matériel orthopédique qui fait figure de leader Allemagne, transpose la compétence textile de la société HAUBER dans le domaine médical. La marque HAUBER, le label qui porte le nom fondateur, prend une part active à la création tendances de la mode dans le secteur prêt-à-porter femme. </fragment> </item> </root> 