<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <root> <item> <fragment> Willkommen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Willkommen ***************** **** * PROTONENRESONANZ ********************* ***************** * EAV-GERÄTE ***************** ********************** * BIORESONANZ-GERÄTE ********************** Lichttherapie Curator. [Protonenresonanz] Unsere EAV-Geräten bieten Ihnen komfortables Arbeiten EAV fairen Preisen. [EAV-Sortiment] In unserem Sortiment finden Sie sowohl manuell gesteuerte, computerunterstützte Bioresonanzgeräte für erfolgreiche Anwendungen Ihrer Praxis. [Bioresonanz-Sortiment] Sehr geehrte Besucher, Sie bemerkt - Vertriebsstrukturen neu organisiert. Für Sie bedeutet weiterhin gewohnte Kindling-Qualität bewährten Sortiment Neuentwicklungen direkt Hersteller. Lassen Sie beraten - individuelle Lösungen für Ihren Arbeitsbereich erarbeiten profitieren Sie über 30 jährigen Erfahrung. Auch Service erfolgt direkt unkompliziert gewohnter Qualität über unseren Standort Hildesheim. Mit über 30 Jahren Erfahrung zertifizierten Qualitätsmanagement Kindling führenden Hersteller qualitativ hochwertiger Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Bioresonanz. Auf Internetseite bieten Ihnen Überblick über Produkte Kontakte qualifizierten Vertrieben, Ihnen ebenfalls Ansprechpartner Verfügung stehen. Als zertifizierter Medizinproduktehersteller bieten Ihnen technischen Service Ihr Gerät. Aus gegebenen Anlass Serviceangebot Geräte Firma Pitterling erweitert, Sie Ihr Gerät weiterhin Praxis einsetzen können (MPBetreibV). ********************************************************************** Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät versehen sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! Unsere Produktion unterliegt hohen Standard Qualitätsmanagement- system DIN EN ISO 13485, TÜV NORD CERT GmbH überwacht zertifiziert ist. Alle Geräte registrierte Medizinprodukte DIMDI (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information) gemeldet. ************************* ************************* Individuelles Therapieren Punktmessung, Tensor unserem Neuesten: Kindling EASY! ************************* Kostenfreie Workshops Bioresonanz Kindling Easy: Samstag, 26.9.15 Köln Samstag, 24.10.15 Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15 Raum Stuttgart Information Anmeldung Messen 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Kindling Gmbh Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Tel: +49 (0)5121/511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121/511927 info@kindling.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Workshop: Kindling-EASY Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Kindling EASY &gt;&gt; Workshops Kindling EASY Workshops Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Workshop: Kindling-EASY Einladung Testen - Anfassen - Ausprobieren So einfach Bioresonanz nie! Wir laden Sie ein, Generation Bioresonanz kennenzulernen testen. Während unseres kostenfreien Workshops zeigen Ihnen erfahrene Kollegen Möglichkeiten Vorteile systemisch funktionellen Bioresonanz Kindling EASY auf. Schnell – kalibrierend – delegierbar kostengünstig Attribute Kindling EASY. Darüber hinaus visualisiert Kindling EASY Therapieergebnis. Ein unschlagbarer Vorteil, Patienten-Compliance geht. Wir zeigen Ihnen, Sie Bioresonanz einfachste effektivste Weise Ihre Praxis integrieren können. Ohne zeitaufwendige Seminare. Einfach anmelden! Wir freuen Sie. Termine: Samstag, 26.9.15, 10-13 Uhr - Köln Samstag, 24.10.15, 10-13 Uhr - Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15, 10-13 Uhr - Raum Stuttgart Den genauen Seminarort erhalten Sie Anmelde-Bestätigung. Anmeldung: easy-vertrieb@kindling.de Telefon: 02663/9170-228 Fax: 02663/9170-229 Anmeldung Download [1.510 KB] </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling EASY Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Kindling EASY Kindling EASY Workshops Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Kindling EASY Bioresonanz Individuelles Therapieren OHNE Punktmessung, OHNE Tensor Das KINDLING-EASY kalibrieren Mess- Therapiegerät für täglichen Einsatz systemischen funktionellen Bioresonanz. Der systemische funktionelle Therapieansatz ergibt Notwendigkeit heraus, organisch fassbaren Erkrankungen zunehmend großer Anteil Patienten über Beﬁndlichkeitsstörungen beklagt, jegliches Raster klassischen schulmedizinischen Diagnostik fallen ergänzenden, komplementärmedizinischen, Diagnostik Therapie bedürfen. Sowohl ﬂankierend adjuvant therapeutischen Fokus stehend, systemische funktionelle Bioresonanztherapie KINDLING-EASY insbesondere lohnend sogenannten „SäureKrankheiten“ &gt;&gt; Das KINDLING-EASY kalibriert sich, Basis Messungen Hautleitfähigkeit, 2 Minuten selbstständig &gt; Der Patient erhält neu geprüfte, aktuelle individuelle Bioresonanztherapie, Engste Regulationsbedürftigkeit Organismus anschmiegt „untersucherunabhängig“ fehlerfreie Therapieparameterwahl garantiert. &gt;&gt; Der Anwender erhält Ende Therapiesitzung graphische Darstellung Therapieverlaufs &gt; Ergebnis- Maßnahmenbesprechnung gemeinsam Patienten. &gt;&gt; Komplexen Vorgänge Bioresonanz automatisiert Ende Therapieergebnis sofort verständlich visualisiert &gt; Das Resultat: hohe Patientenakzeptanz. &gt;&gt; Für Anwender bedeutet schlechte Anwendbarkeit (Usability), Bedienfehler entstehen Zeitressourcen verschwendet werden. Im heutigen Gesundheitssystem efﬁziente Arbeitsabläufe, aufgrund permanenter Kostensenkungsmaßnahmen, dringend erforderlich &gt; Mit Taster bildlichen Darstellung Therapie fehlerfrei selbstständig durchgeführt. &gt;&gt; Die Therapie zeitsparend 100% deligierbar. Kindling EASY Therapie *"Echte" 2-Kanal-Technik für simultane endogene exogene Bioresonanz *Automatisierte Therapie individuell Patienten abgestimmt *Wiederkehrende, selbstständige Kalibrierung Einfache Messtechnik (Hand-Hand-Messung) *Untersucherunabhängige Messung *Fehlerfreie Parameterwahl *Komplexe Vorgänge Bioresonanz automatisiert Intuitive Anwendung (sehr Deligierbarkeit) *Graphische Darstellung Therapieverlaufs *66% Zeitersparnis *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! FLYER Flyer HIER Download [2.366 KB] ******************************************************************************* § Das Heilmittelwerbegesetz erlaubt keinerlei Veröffentlichung Anwendungsgebieten Erfahrungsberichten. Auf Anfrage senden medizinischen Fachpersonen gerne ausführliche Produktinformation zu. [Kontakt] ******************************************************************************* Kostenfreie Workshops Bioresonanz Kindling Easy : Samstag, 26.9.15 Köln Samstag, 24.10.15 Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15 Raum Stuttgart Information Anmeldung Messen 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 7.-8.11.2015 Internationaal Therapeut, Apeldoorn 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg ************************ Therapeutischer Support PaedDr. Uwe Uellendahl, HP Praxis für Naturheilverfahren Therapeutische Anwendungsfragen Kindling-EASY: Mo.-Do. 18:15 - 19:15 Uhr Tel.: 0176-43037799 easy@kindling.de Technischer Support Eduard Abrams Kindling GmbH Tel.: 05121-511997 easy@kindling.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Welcome Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Welcome Dear Visitor, we are happy to present you our newest: Kindling EASY! Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor. For the first time we present the Kindling EASY on following trade fairs and invite you to test and inform you on site: 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Elektroacupuncture Bioresonance Our electroacupuncture devices offer you ease of working with EAV ans other methods at reasonable prices. In our inventory you find both manually controlled and computer-controlled bioresonance devices for successful use your practice. With more than 25 years of experience and certified quality management, Kindling is one of the leading manufacturers of high-quality devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Dr. Voll and Bioresonance. On our website, we offer you overview of our products as well as contacts to qualified seminars and distributors. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044. Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! Our production is subject to the high standard assured under the Quality Management System DIN EN ISO 13485 (CAN/CSA 13485), which is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. All devices are registered medical products, registered with the German Institute for Medical Documentation and Information (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information). [Certification] ************************* ************************* Watch out buying medical device! You use the device your practice? Is the device certified as medical product? See more information HERE ************************* Trade Fairs For Trade Fairs your country, please contact our dirstributors on-site . 18.4.2015 CAM 2015, Düsseldorf 9.5.2015 Roadshow: Testen – Anfassen – Ausprobieren, Köln 13.-14.6.2015 Deutscher Heilpraktikerkongress, Karlsruhe 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg ************************* </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Willkommen Willkommen ***************** **** * PROTONENRESONANZ ********************* ***************** * EAV-GERÄTE ***************** ********************** * BIORESONANZ-GERÄTE ********************** Lichttherapie Curator. [Protonenresonanz] Unsere EAV-Geräten bieten Ihnen komfortables Arbeiten EAV fairen Preisen. [EAV-Sortiment] In unserem Sortiment finden Sie sowohl manuell gesteuerte, computerunterstützte Bioresonanzgeräte für erfolgreiche Anwendungen Ihrer Praxis. [Bioresonanz-Sortiment] Sehr geehrte Besucher, Sie bemerkt - Vertriebsstrukturen neu organisiert. Für Sie bedeutet weiterhin gewohnte Kindling-Qualität bewährten Sortiment Neuentwicklungen direkt Hersteller. Lassen Sie beraten - individuelle Lösungen für Ihren Arbeitsbereich erarbeiten profitieren Sie über 30 jährigen Erfahrung. Auch Service erfolgt direkt unkompliziert gewohnter Qualität über unseren Standort Hildesheim. Mit über 30 Jahren Erfahrung zertifizierten Qualitätsmanagement Kindling führenden Hersteller qualitativ hochwertiger Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Bioresonanz. Auf Internetseite bieten Ihnen Überblick über Produkte Kontakte qualifizierten Vertrieben, Ihnen ebenfalls Ansprechpartner Verfügung stehen. Als zertifizierter Medizinproduktehersteller bieten Ihnen technischen Service Ihr Gerät. Aus gegebenen Anlass Serviceangebot Geräte Firma Pitterling erweitert, Sie Ihr Gerät weiterhin Praxis einsetzen können (MPBetreibV). ********************************************************************** Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät versehen sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! Unsere Produktion unterliegt hohen Standard Qualitätsmanagement- system DIN EN ISO 13485, TÜV NORD CERT GmbH überwacht zertifiziert ist. Alle Geräte registrierte Medizinprodukte DIMDI (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information) gemeldet. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. ************************* ************************* Individuelles Therapieren Punktmessung, Tensor unserem Neuesten: Kindling EASY! ************************* Kostenfreie Workshops Bioresonanz Kindling Easy: Samstag, 26.9.15 Köln Samstag, 24.10.15 Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15 Raum Stuttgart Information Anmeldung Messen 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Kindling Gmbh Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Tel: +49 (0)5121/511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121/511927 info@kindling.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Reparatur Wartung Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Service | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Reparatur Wartung Unser geschultes Fachpersonal bietet Ihnen Reparaturen Wartungen, Sie Ihr Gerät weiterhin Praxis einsetzen können (MPBetreibV). Aus gegebenen Anlass Serviceangebot EAV-Geräte Firma Pitterling erweitert. Wir reparieren warten u.a.: Eigene Geräte Kindling GmbH: Akuport M1(+) Akuport M2 Akuport MT Akuport MR2 Akuport D-tec Combi-2 Kindling 2000 Retec 2000 Vistron Kindling EASY Nervenpunktdetektor 4B Neuropuls EAV-Geräte Firma Pitterling: Dermatron Dermatron ST Dermatron CL Pitterling Diagnost Sollte Ihr Gerät aufgelistet sein, kontaktieren Sie bitte, helfen Ihnen gerne [Kontakt] . </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vertrieb / Distributor Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Vertrieb | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Vertrieb / Distributor Deutschland Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim, Deutschland Telefon: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 E-Mail: info@kindling.de ******************************************************************** Niederlande R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Niederlande Telefon: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Österreich Trikomvit Austria e.U. Dr. M. Hohl Georgestraße 27 4222 Langenstein Telefon: +43 7237438011 Internet: www.trikomvit.at E-Mail: info@trikomvit.at ******************************************************************** Spanien Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spanien Telefon: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Türkei Anfora Saglik Tic.Ltd. Sti Karaman Mahallesi Açelya Sokak Ufuk Apt. No 8 03730 Afyonkarahisar Internet: www.akupunkturkey.com E-Mail: info@akupunkturkey.com ******************************************************************** Kanada Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Kanada Telefon: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Kanada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Telefon: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** Japan Gain Inc. Mr. Yasuaki Yoshikawa 6F Onoe Building, 4-4-2 Takadanobaba Shinjuku-ku, Tokiyo, Japan Telefon: +81 (0)3-5332-6334 Fax: +81 (0)3-5332-3488 E-mail: lucky@gain-life.jp </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Software Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Software | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Software Computerunterstützt arbeiten Computerunterstützes Arbeiten alternativen Medizin gewinnt Bedeutung. Sie vereinfacht umfangreichen Dokumentationsaufwand ermöglicht effektives Arbeiten. Durch Wegfallen vieler Präparate erhält Softwareprogramm höheren Stellenwert, Präparate-Information digital Verfügung stellt (digitale Waves). In enger Zusammenarbeit erfahrenen Praktikern, Ärzten Software-Ingenieuren unterschiedliche Software-Systeme entwickelt, Kindling-Geräte angepasst sind. Meditest X-Kits BREVIS Nähere Informationen finden Sie HOMOPATH ® Nähere Informationen finden Sie </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Zubehör Zubehör EAV Zubehör Bioresonanz Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Zubehör für Bioresonanz Für genaue Messergebnisse erfolgreiche Therapien Kindling-EAV-Geräten bieten Ihnen passendes Zubehör für Anwendungen. Hier finden Sie speziell abgestimmtes Standard- Sonderzubehör für erfolgreiches Arbeiten Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Modellkombinationen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Modellkombinationen Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Voll Kombination Bioresonanztherapie Auf Seite finden Sie Kombinationsmöglichkeiten, Gehäusetyp speziell aufeinander abgestimmt sind. Zudem können lle Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments miteinander kombiniert außerdem Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. Akuport M1+ / MT Abgestimmte Harmonie moderner EAV-Diagnose Therapie Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV- Resonanztherapie kompakten Systemeinheit. Der Ideale Einstieg modernen Mess- Retec-Therapieverfahren. Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Der Akuport Tower vereint EAV Diagnose Therapie Vorzügen Bioresonanz. Einfach, schnell Platz sparend steht Ihnen komplette Systemeinheit Verfügung. Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport-Geräten Combi-2 / Retec 2000 C Ob Retec 2000 C professional – gekoppelt Combi-2 uneingeschränktes Arbeiten EAV Bioresonanz gewährleistet. Vistron / Akuport D-tec Das Akuport D-tec Helfer Vistron Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Akuport-Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es einzige Stromversorgung nötig. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Bioresonanz Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Bioresonanz Geräte für Bioresonaztherapie Die Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments können größtenteils miteinander kombiniert [Modellkombinationen] Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. Kindling EASY Selbstkalibrierendes Bioresonanzgerät. Individuelles Therapieren OHNE Punktmessung / Tensor Akuport MR2 Modulares Gerät für Resonanztherapie – Stand-Alone-Version kombinierbar EAV Diagnose-Gerät Akuport M1+ Retec 2000 CP Softwaregesteuertes Bioresonanzgerät für universelle vielseitige Resonanztherapie Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt nativen virtuellen Informationen elektronische Potenzen. Kombinierbar Akuport MR2, RETEC 2000CP Vistron. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Elektroakupunktur Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Elektroakupunktur Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Voll (EAV) Die Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments können miteinander kombiniert [Modellkombinationen] außerdem Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. DIAGNOSE &amp; THERAPIE Combi-2 Die Vielseitigkeit Diagnose Therapie Gerät – gehobene Mittelklasse für anspruchsvolle Anwender Akuport M1+/MT Einzeln einfachen Plug&amp;Play-System verbunden bieten Geräte individuelle Arbeitsplatzgestaltung. Vistron Perfekte Kombination Diagnose, Elektrotherapie Informationsübertragung – neueste Modell Produktpalette überzeugt neuartige Technik präzisen Leuchtbandanzeige. DIAGNOSE Akuport M2 Das portable Diagnosegerät integrierter Mundstrommessung, großem Zeigerinstrument Digitalanzeige ideal für Praxis Unterwegs Akuport M1+ Das ideale Einstiegsgerät modernen bioelektrischen Messverfahren EAV erweiterbar modularen System Akuport MT und/oder MR2. THERAPIE Akuport MT Therapiegerät für Elektroakupunktur – Modul M1+ Stand-alone-Version erhältlich. Unsere Geräte zugelassene Medizinprodukte EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling GmbH stellt Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Kindling GmbH stellt Mit Qualität Kompetenz Impulse setzen Seit 30 Jahren Firma Kindling für Elektroakupunkturgeräte national international bekannt. Als Marktführer Entwicklung Produktion Geräten für Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik wichtiger Partner für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Heilpraktiker, biometrischen Systemdiagnostik befassen. Unsere langjährige Erfahrung intensive Zusammenarbeit unseren Kunden gewährleistet hohen Qualitätsmaßstab ermöglicht uns, Produkte enger Anlehnung Praxis optimieren Neuentwicklungen durchzuführen. Wir zugelassener Entwickler Hersteller Medizinprodukten. Dieses erfordert Einhaltung Anforderungen EU-Richtlinie 93/42/EWG bzw. 2007/47/EWG Vorhandensein überwachten Qualitätssicherungssystems (EN DIN ISO 13485). Die Überwachung Zertifizierung benannte Stelle TÜV NORD CERT GmbH (Kenn-Nummer 0044) durchgeführt. [Zertifizierung] Die Anbringung CE-Zeichens inkl. Kenn-Nummer 0044 unseren Geräten zeigt, zugelassenes zertifiziertes Medizinprodukt handelt. Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE-Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät angebracht sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! Wichtig Kauf Gebrauchtgerätes! Auch Sie Augen aufhalten. Denn vermeidbares Schnäppchen schnell kostspielig werden. Häufig sicherheitstechnische Kontrollen notwendig, Gerät Praxis verwenden dürfen – Verschleißteile z. B. Akku Jahren Nutzung Leistungsgrenzen müssen ausgetauscht werden. Die hohe Qualität Produkte, fachlich kompetente Beratungen zuverlässiger technischer Service Grundlage für feste Marktposition Produkte. So stehen Ihnen persönlich Ort Hildesheim, telefonisch per E-Mail Beratung, Verkauf Service jederzeit Verfügung. Des Weiteren bestehen Vertriebsstrukturen Ländern z. B. Niederlande, Spanien, Schweiz, Kanada, Taiwan, Japan u. a. [Vertrieb] Überzeugen Sie Produktvielfalt Website lassen Sie individuell beraten – Wir Ihre Ansprüche Erstellung optimalen Arbeitsplatzes Ihrer Zufriedenheit erfüllen. Ihr Kindling-Team </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Workshop: Kindling-EASY Workshop: Kindling-EASY Einladung Testen - Anfassen - Ausprobieren So einfach Bioresonanz nie! Wir laden Sie ein, Generation Bioresonanz kennenzulernen testen. Während unseres kostenfreien Workshops zeigen Ihnen erfahrene Kollegen Möglichkeiten Vorteile systemisch funktionellen Bioresonanz Kindling EASY auf. Schnell – kalibrierend – delegierbar kostengünstig Attribute Kindling EASY. Darüber hinaus visualisiert Kindling EASY Therapieergebnis. Ein unschlagbarer Vorteil, Patienten-Compliance geht. Wir zeigen Ihnen, Sie Bioresonanz einfachste effektivste Weise Ihre Praxis integrieren können. Ohne zeitaufwendige Seminare. Einfach anmelden! Wir freuen Sie. Termine: Samstag, 26.9.15, 10-13 Uhr - Köln Samstag, 24.10.15, 10-13 Uhr - Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15, 10-13 Uhr - Raum Stuttgart Den genauen Seminarort erhalten Sie Anmelde-Bestätigung. Anmeldung: easy-vertrieb@kindling.de Telefon: 02663/9170-228 Fax: 02663/9170-229 Anmeldung Download (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Literaturempfehlungen Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Literaturempfehlungen BIORESONANZ Allergien Tiere heilbar Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Biophysikalische Therapie Allergien Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Allergien nehmen weltweit zu. Allergien entwickeln stets variierende maskierte Formen - zuletzt umweltbedingt. Die Belastungen Asthma bronchiale, Heuschnupfen Neurodermitis reduzieren Lebensqualität Patienten dramatisch. Chemische Suppression Hyposensibilisierungsbehandlung zeigen unzureichend Erfolge erhöhten Nebenwirkungen Gefahren. Anhand langjähriger, sorgfältig dokumentierter Erfolge kinderärztlicher Praxis weist Verfasser nach, daß Allergien vollständig nachhaltig heilbar können, biophysikalisches Phänomen erkennt physikalischen Gesetzen behandelt. Auf Basis 'Bioresonanztherapie' bewährten Konzeption vermittelt Buch umfassend systematisch Grundlagen Praxis biophysikalischen 'Löschung' Allergien - Fremdsubstanzen belastende Nebenwirkungen, insbesondere Aspekt Kinderheilkunde. Bioresonanz - Heilen Medikamente Maasz-Daley, Lerch, Haug Verlag Heilen inneren Kraft: Die Bioresonanztherapie - revolutionäre wirksame Heilmethode - Fachkundigund verständlich beschrieben - Zahlreiche Fallbeispiele, Behandlungsmöglichkeiten anschaulicherläutert werden. Endlich Allergien mehr, Schluß quälenden Kopf- Rückenschmerzen. Die erfolgreiche Heilmethode deutschen Arzt Franz Morell entwickelt. Zahlreiche Beispiele Praxis veranschaulichen, Krankheiten Rheuma, Morbus Bechterew, akuten chronischen Schmerzzuständen, Migräne, Allergien, Asthma, Neurodermitis stressbedingten Erkrankungen bewährt hat. Die Bioresonanztherapie bietet Möglichkeit, Medikamente völlig schmerzlos gesund werden. Sie für Kinder geeignet. Neue Lebenskraft Bioresonanz Dr. med. Dörfler, Simondo Gesundheitsservice Erstmals möglich, Belastungen unseres energetischen Systems exakt erfasen. Die Behandlung greift tief Gefüge ermöglicht es, Patienten "rückwärts Sackgasse Krankheit" herauszuführen. Warum kränker? Wie funktioniert Energiesystem? Wie Diagnostik Therapie sich? Welche Mitarbeit Patienten verlangt? Wie Patient weiterhin gesund erhalten? Welche begleitenden Behandlungen hilfreich sinnvoll? </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Akuport D-tec Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport D-tec Potenzierer Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen – kombinierbar Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP EAV Gerät Vistron . Bei bioenergetischen Testverfahren Potenzreihen Anwendung. Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt elektronische Potenzen, Anwender große Vielfalt komplementär-medizinischen Prozessen ermöglichen. Das Akuport D-tec arbeitet Kombination Geräten für bioenergetische Messverfahren - Stand-alone Version Vistron Retec 2000CP einfachen plug&amp;play-System Akuport MR2. Kindling Akuport D-tec *Potenzstufen: D3, D4, D6, D8, D10, D12, D15, D30, D60, D100, D200 Ausgang Übertragung elektronischen Potenz Trägermedium Potenzierungskontrolle LED-Anzeige *Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil *Modulares System für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Erarbeitung individueller Potenzen Kombination bioenergetischen Messverfahren (EAV, BFD, usw.) Erstellung Auto-Nosoden (z.B. Sekrete, Exkrete) Feststellung Unverträglichkeiten Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das plug&amp;play-System ermöglicht zusätzliches Ergänzen Diagnosegerätes Akuport M1+ Reizstromtherapiemodul Akuport MT kompletten Thereapieeinheit. Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Ausgangsbecher Lieferumfang Maße (BxHxT): 16x6x15cm, Gewicht ca. 200g Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport MR2 Akuport D-tec Adapterleitung für Stromzufuhr Bedienungsanleitung Akuport D-tec stand alone Version Retec 2000CP, Vistron Fremdgeräten Akuport D-tec Netzteil (für MPG-Geräte zugelassen) Verbindungsleitungen Kunststoffabdeckkappe Gehäusedesign Bedienungsanleitung Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport MR2/D-tec Akuport M1+/MR2/D-tec Akuport M1+/MT/MR2/D-tec Vistron/D-tec </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Retec 2000 CP Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Retec 2000 CP Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Retec 2000 CP Bioresonanz Softwaregesteuertes Bioresonanzgerät für universelle vielseitige Resonanztherapie inkl. 340 automatische Programme Das Retec 2000CP setzt multifunktionelle Einstellung Parameter einzigartige zukunftsorientierte Maßstäbe Resonanztherapie. Es Verbindung extern angeschlossenen PC (Notebook) betrieben. Die Benutzeroberfläche für intuitive Nutzung gestaltet unterstützt Behandlungsablauf sortierte Indikationslisten, gezielt Symptombildern aufgerufen können. Mit Hilfe optisch angezeigten Elektrodenbelegung Bestückung Ausgangsbechers schnelle Einarbeitung erreicht. Verwenden Sie Multitherapie 5 Programme automatisch ablaufen lassen. Oder nutzen Sie manuelle Therapie , Sie notwendigen Parameter anpassen können abspeichern. Auch Möglichkeit elektronische Potenzierung steht Ihnen Verfügung. Multitherapie Die Multitherapie ermöglicht Ihnen automatische Abfolge Programmen erstellen, für evtl. nächste Sitzungen abgespeichert kann. Bis 5 Programme können gewählt werden. Manuelle Therapie Sie können Programme individuell ändern erstellen. Veränderungen Einstellungen können anklicken Schaltsymbole Beschriftungsflächen erreicht werden. Ist Parametergröße Schaltsymbol zugeordnet (z. B. Verstärkereinstellung) öffnet zusätzlich Fenster, Wert eingeschrieben wird. Es können Werte Anklicken Pfeilmarken erhöht (Pfeil oben) verkleinert (Pfeil unten) werden. Potenzieren Die elektronische Potenzierung Substanzen erfolgt Dr.Würthle. Durch Verwendung Harmonischen Dis-Harmonischen Informationen Potenzierung D100 möglich. Kindling Retec 2000CP Therapie Bipolares Therapiegerät Integrierte Ein- Ausgangsplatten *Kindling Special! Externe Bechererweiterung 2 Ein- Ausgänge Differenzverfahren, Umwelteinflüsse Übertragungen *Kindling Special! leichte Handhabung Retec-Hardware übersichtliche Menüführung Software delegierbar Bildhafte Zubehörvorschläge Therapiewahl *Kindling Special! einfaches Update-Verfahren mittels installierender CD-ROM 340 Festprogramme Indikationen sortiert Frequenzbereich 1.000.000 Hz Filterbereich 100.000 Hz automatischer Banddurchlauf Wobbelbetrieb individuell einstellbare Verstärkung 100-fach bzw. Abschwächung 0,01 Therapie-Modus: Seperator-Schaltung (H, DI), direkt invers (A, AI) Testfunktion Ausgangsverstärkers *Kindling Special! Therapiekontrolle LED-Anzeige *Kindling Special! Anzeige verbleibenden Therapiezeit Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil – Opitonal: Akkubetrieb übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen Zubehörablage Geräteoberseite *Kindling Special! baulich abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept Kindling EAV Combi-2 Hohe Störsicherheit externen PC kompatibel handelsüblichen Windows-PCs (Windows XP, Vista, Windows7, Windows8) CD-ROM-Laufwerk freien USB-Port Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Informationsübertragung Medikamentenübertragung Ausleiten Inversübertragung Becherbelegung: Eingang z. B. Nosoden, Viren, Bakterien, Sekrete, Exkrete, Parasiten, Schwermetalle, Virtuelle Datenbank, etc.; Ausgang z.B. Patient, Medium, Globuli, etc. Multitherapie Potenzieren Einlesen Schwingungsmustern Homopath-Software Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-EAV-Geräten speziell EAV-Combi-2 aufeinander abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept Kombinierbar virtuellen Medikamentendatenbanken Softwareprogramme Meditest Homopath umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Eingangs- Augangsbecher, etc. Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messing-Fußelektroden 2 flexible Elektroden 1 Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde 1 Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde 1 Individualisierungsstab/Salbenstab 1 Magnetfeldmatte 2 Paar Retecleitungen 2m 3 Glasschalen Deckel Software Retec 2000pro CD-ROM USB-Verbindungsleitung medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 20x8x38cm, Gewicht ca. 1700g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Combi-2 / Retec 2000C EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MR2 Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Bioresonanz &gt;&gt; Akuport MR2 Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport MR2 Bioresonanz Modulares Gerät für Resonanztherapie – Stand-Alone-Version kombinierbar EAV Diagnose-Gerät Akuport M1+ Das Kindling Akuport MR2 erweitert EAV Diagnose moderne Resonanztherapie. Physiologische körpereigene Schwingungen extern vorgegebene Schwingungsinformationen regulieren stabilisieren energetischen Laufbahnen Körper, aktivieren stärken Selbstheilungskräfte. Invers- Direktbetrieb hierfür breiten Frequenzspektrum Anwendung eingesetzt. Durch Kombination virtuellen Medikamenten Softwareprogramme Anwendungsgebiet stark erweitert werden. Kindling Akuport MR2 Therapie *Großer Frequenzbereich 1.000.000 Hz *Hoch- Tiefpass für akute degenerative Behandlung Stufenlose Verstärkung 60-fach, übersichtlich einzustellen Direkt- Invers-Schaltung *Integrierte Ein- Ausgangsplatten *Differenzverfahren, Umwelteinflüsse Übertragungen Externe Bechererweiterung 2 Ein- Ausgänge Breites Indikationsspektrum Timerschaltung Therapiekontrolle LED-Anzeige *Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Direkt- Inverstherapie Medikamentenübertragung Direktübertragung Ausleiten Inversübertragung Becherbelegung: Eingang z. B. Nosoden, Viren, Bakterien, Sekrete, Exkrete, Parasiten, Schwermetalle, Virtuelle Datenbank, etc.; Ausgang z.B. Patient, Medium, Globuli, etc. Einlesen Schwingungsmustern Homopath-Software Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das Akuport MR2 Einzelgerät betrieben jederzeit verschiedenen Modulen erweitert – speziellen Diagnosemodul (M1+) und/oder Reizstromtherapiemodul (MT) einfachen plug&amp;play-System. Einsatz virtuellen Medikamenten Softwareprogramme Meditest Homopath umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Ausgangsbecher Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitungen für Handelektroden abgeschirmtes Leitungspaar Schottglas Glasschale Deckel Abdeckkappe integrierter Ablagefläche Differenz-Abdeckplatte medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g, Grundplatte: 26x23cm Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MR2 Modulkombination Akuport MR2/D-tec Modulkombination Akuport Tower Modulkombination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling EASY Kindling EASY Bioresonanz Individuelles Therapieren OHNE Punktmessung, OHNE Tensor Das KINDLING-EASY kalibrieren Mess- Therapiegerät für täglichen Einsatz systemischen funktionellen Bioresonanz. Der systemische funktionelle Therapieansatz ergibt Notwendigkeit heraus, organisch fassbaren Erkrankungen zunehmend großer Anteil Patienten über Beﬁndlichkeitsstörungen beklagt, jegliches Raster klassischen schulmedizinischen Diagnostik fallen ergänzenden, komplementärmedizinischen, Diagnostik Therapie bedürfen. Sowohl ﬂankierend adjuvant therapeutischen Fokus stehend, systemische funktionelle Bioresonanztherapie KINDLING-EASY insbesondere lohnend sogenannten „SäureKrankheiten“ &gt;&gt; Das KINDLING-EASY kalibriert sich, Basis Messungen Hautleitfähigkeit, 2 Minuten selbstständig &gt; Der Patient erhält neu geprüfte, aktuelle individuelle Bioresonanztherapie, Engste Regulationsbedürftigkeit Organismus anschmiegt „untersucherunabhängig“ fehlerfreie Therapieparameterwahl garantiert. &gt;&gt; Der Anwender erhält Ende Therapiesitzung graphische Darstellung Therapieverlaufs &gt; Ergebnis- Maßnahmenbesprechnung gemeinsam Patienten. &gt;&gt; Komplexen Vorgänge Bioresonanz automatisiert Ende Therapieergebnis sofort verständlich visualisiert &gt; Das Resultat: hohe Patientenakzeptanz. &gt;&gt; Für Anwender bedeutet schlechte Anwendbarkeit (Usability), Bedienfehler entstehen Zeitressourcen verschwendet werden. Im heutigen Gesundheitssystem efﬁziente Arbeitsabläufe, aufgrund permanenter Kostensenkungsmaßnahmen, dringend erforderlich &gt; Mit Taster bildlichen Darstellung Therapie fehlerfrei selbstständig durchgeführt. &gt;&gt; Die Therapie zeitsparend 100% deligierbar. Kindling EASY Therapie *"Echte" 2-Kanal-Technik für simultane endogene exogene Bioresonanz *Automatisierte Therapie individuell Patienten abgestimmt *Wiederkehrende, selbstständige Kalibrierung Einfache Messtechnik (Hand-Hand-Messung) *Untersucherunabhängige Messung *Fehlerfreie Parameterwahl *Komplexe Vorgänge Bioresonanz automatisiert Intuitive Anwendung (sehr Deligierbarkeit) *Graphische Darstellung Therapieverlaufs *66% Zeitersparnis *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! FLYER Flyer HIER Download ******************************************************************************* § Das Heilmittelwerbegesetz erlaubt keinerlei Veröffentlichung Anwendungsgebieten Erfahrungsberichten. Auf Anfrage senden medizinischen Fachpersonen gerne ausführliche Produktinformation zu. [Kontakt] ******************************************************************************* (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Vistron Vistron Details Potentizer Akuport D-tec Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Vistron Diagnostics and Therapy, Information transfer Perfect combination of diagnostics, electrotherapy and data transfer – the latest model our product portfolio impress you with its new technology, precision and ease of reading the new LED display. The Vistron combines the diagnostic and therapy component for bio-symmetrical function testing using the Electroacupuncture new, modern, flat housing design. Novelties include among other things the microprocessor-controlled light bar, the inertia-less of the measurement end value, as well as the measured indicator drop. The folding display makes the values optimally reviewable and readable. Membrane keyboards make the device easy to read and operate. The power supply is now provided as standard using high-grade medical power supply, approved under EN 60601-1, or optionally using easily replaceable 12 Volt rechargeable battery. [more details] Along with the proven features diagnostic and therapeutic applications, such as the “Opto-point” point locator the ergonomically designed stylus, you find new EAV functions which simplify processes everyday practice: Kindling Vistron EAV-Diagnostics and Therapy *Stationary operation with power supply Available for portable operation with optional rechargeable battery *Maintenance-free light bar display *Automatic or manual point measurement selectable *Saves the current measurement display until the next measurement is taken Volume of measurement tone can be regulated or turned off Integrated removable large honeycomb; can be switched off with button Tooth electrode that can be placed on the stylus for tooth enamel testing All measurement electrodes expanded assortment *Sweep wave therapy with simultaneous measurement display (T+M) *Expanded frequency spectrum to max. 199 Hz *Frequency range 0-10Hz or 10-100 Hz *Control of individual point therapy Also useable needle stimulation and ear acupuncture *Retec transfer unit for surge substance on carriers *Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Applications Diagnostic measurements and evaluations according to the standards of EAV Comfortable tooth enamel test Direct information transfer: input, e.g. nosodes, homeopathically prepared substances, information from the virtual data bank (Homopath, Meditest) etc; output e.g. medium, globuli, etc, or patient Sweep wave therapy (tonifying and sedating) via acupuncture points: Fixed frequency (0.1 – 19.9 Hz or 10 – 199 Hz); Frequency range (1.0 – 10.0 Hz or 10 – 100 Hz) Special Supplemental Options Extensive special accessories Expandable with all Kindling bioresonance devices Can be combined with EAV software Homopath or the Meditest software program for compiling assessment data and virtual resonance tests, which is available both beginner´s and expert´s version Quadrant switch for testing with hand, foot and forehead electrodes Scope of Delivery Pair of hand electrodes, brass 2 wires for hand electrodes (red, black) Stylus with fixed 4-slice-tip Dental electrode Output beaker XL Retec wire 0,5m Honeycomb ø ca. 10 cm, integrated and removeable Power supply Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 31x5,5(11)x28cm, Weight ca. 2200g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Ergonomically designed stylus Potentizer Akuport D-tec combination with Vistron EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Willkommen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Willkommen ***************** **** * PROTONENRESONANZ ********************* ***************** * EAV-GERÄTE ***************** ********************** * BIORESONANZ-GERÄTE ********************** Lichttherapie Curator. [Protonenresonanz] Unsere EAV-Geräten bieten Ihnen komfortables Arbeiten EAV fairen Preisen. [EAV-Sortiment] In unserem Sortiment finden Sie sowohl manuell gesteuerte, computerunterstützte Bioresonanzgeräte für erfolgreiche Anwendungen Ihrer Praxis. [Bioresonanz-Sortiment] Sehr geehrte Besucher, Sie bemerkt - Vertriebsstrukturen neu organisiert. Für Sie bedeutet weiterhin gewohnte Kindling-Qualität bewährten Sortiment Neuentwicklungen direkt Hersteller. Lassen Sie beraten - individuelle Lösungen für Ihren Arbeitsbereich erarbeiten profitieren Sie über 30 jährigen Erfahrung. Auch Service erfolgt direkt unkompliziert gewohnter Qualität über unseren Standort Hildesheim. Mit über 30 Jahren Erfahrung zertifizierten Qualitätsmanagement Kindling führenden Hersteller qualitativ hochwertiger Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Bioresonanz. Auf Internetseite bieten Ihnen Überblick über Produkte Kontakte qualifizierten Vertrieben, Ihnen ebenfalls Ansprechpartner Verfügung stehen. Als zertifizierter Medizinproduktehersteller bieten Ihnen technischen Service Ihr Gerät. Aus gegebenen Anlass Serviceangebot Geräte Firma Pitterling erweitert, Sie Ihr Gerät weiterhin Praxis einsetzen können (MPBetreibV). ********************************************************************** Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät versehen sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! Unsere Produktion unterliegt hohen Standard Qualitätsmanagement- system DIN EN ISO 13485, TÜV NORD CERT GmbH überwacht zertifiziert ist. Alle Geräte registrierte Medizinprodukte DIMDI (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information) gemeldet. ************************* ************************* Individuelles Therapieren Punktmessung, Tensor unserem Neuesten: Kindling EASY! ************************* Kostenfreie Workshops Bioresonanz Kindling Easy: Samstag, 26.9.15 Köln Samstag, 24.10.15 Raum Stuttgart Samstag, 14.11.15 Raum Stuttgart Information Anmeldung Messen 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Kindling Gmbh Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Tel: +49 (0)5121/511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121/511927 info@kindling.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Reparatur Wartung Reparatur Wartung Unser geschultes Fachpersonal bietet Ihnen Reparaturen Wartungen, Sie Ihr Gerät weiterhin Praxis einsetzen können (MPBetreibV). Aus gegebenen Anlass Serviceangebot EAV-Geräte Firma Pitterling erweitert. Wir reparieren warten u.a.: Eigene Geräte Kindling GmbH: Akuport M1(+) Akuport M2 Akuport MT Akuport MR2 Akuport D-tec Combi-2 Kindling 2000 Retec 2000 Vistron Kindling EASY Nervenpunktdetektor 4B Neuropuls EAV-Geräte Firma Pitterling: Dermatron Dermatron ST Dermatron CL Pitterling Diagnost Sollte Ihr Gerät aufgelistet sein, kontaktieren Sie bitte, helfen Ihnen gerne [Kontakt] . (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vertrieb / Distributor Vertrieb / Distributor Deutschland Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim, Deutschland Telefon: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 E-Mail: info@kindling.de ******************************************************************** Niederlande R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Niederlande Telefon: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Österreich Trikomvit Austria e.U. Dr. M. Hohl Georgestraße 27 4222 Langenstein Telefon: +43 7237438011 Internet: www.trikomvit.at E-Mail: info@trikomvit.at ******************************************************************** Spanien Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spanien Telefon: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Türkei Anfora Saglik Tic.Ltd. Sti Karaman Mahallesi Açelya Sokak Ufuk Apt. No 8 03730 Afyonkarahisar Internet: www.akupunkturkey.com E-Mail: info@akupunkturkey.com ******************************************************************** Kanada Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Kanada Telefon: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Kanada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Telefon: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** Japan Gain Inc. Mr. Yasuaki Yoshikawa 6F Onoe Building, 4-4-2 Takadanobaba Shinjuku-ku, Tokiyo, Japan Telefon: +81 (0)3-5332-6334 Fax: +81 (0)3-5332-3488 E-mail: lucky@gain-life.jp (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Software Software Computerunterstützt arbeiten Computerunterstützes Arbeiten alternativen Medizin gewinnt Bedeutung. Sie vereinfacht umfangreichen Dokumentationsaufwand ermöglicht effektives Arbeiten. Durch Wegfallen vieler Präparate erhält Softwareprogramm höheren Stellenwert, Präparate-Information digital Verfügung stellt (digitale Waves). In enger Zusammenarbeit erfahrenen Praktikern, Ärzten Software-Ingenieuren unterschiedliche Software-Systeme entwickelt, Kindling-Geräte angepasst sind. Meditest X-Kits BREVIS Nähere Informationen finden Sie HOMOPATH ® Nähere Informationen finden Sie (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Zubehör für Bioresonanz Für genaue Messergebnisse erfolgreiche Therapien Kindling-EAV-Geräten bieten Ihnen passendes Zubehör für Anwendungen. Hier finden Sie speziell abgestimmtes Standard- Sonderzubehör für erfolgreiches Arbeiten Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Modellkombinationen Modellkombinationen Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Voll Kombination Bioresonanztherapie Auf Seite finden Sie Kombinationsmöglichkeiten, Gehäusetyp speziell aufeinander abgestimmt sind. Zudem können lle Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments miteinander kombiniert außerdem Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. Akuport M1+ / MT Abgestimmte Harmonie moderner EAV-Diagnose Therapie Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV- Resonanztherapie kompakten Systemeinheit. Der Ideale Einstieg modernen Mess- Retec-Therapieverfahren. Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Der Akuport Tower vereint EAV Diagnose Therapie Vorzügen Bioresonanz. Einfach, schnell Platz sparend steht Ihnen komplette Systemeinheit Verfügung. Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport-Geräten Combi-2 / Retec 2000 C Ob Retec 2000 C professional – gekoppelt Combi-2 uneingeschränktes Arbeiten EAV Bioresonanz gewährleistet. Vistron / Akuport D-tec Das Akuport D-tec Helfer Vistron (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Bioresonanz Bioresonanz Geräte für Bioresonaztherapie Die Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments können größtenteils miteinander kombiniert [Modellkombinationen] Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. Kindling EASY Selbstkalibrierendes Bioresonanzgerät. Individuelles Therapieren OHNE Punktmessung / Tensor Akuport MR2 Modulares Gerät für Resonanztherapie – Stand-Alone-Version kombinierbar EAV Diagnose-Gerät Akuport M1+ Retec 2000 CP Softwaregesteuertes Bioresonanzgerät für universelle vielseitige Resonanztherapie Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt nativen virtuellen Informationen elektronische Potenzen. Kombinierbar Akuport MR2, RETEC 2000CP Vistron. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Elektroakupunktur Elektroakupunktur Geräte für Elektroakupunktur Voll (EAV) Die Kindling Geräte aktuellen Sortiments können miteinander kombiniert [Modellkombinationen] außerdem Kindling-Softwareprogramme angeschlossen werden. DIAGNOSE &amp; THERAPIE Combi-2 Die Vielseitigkeit Diagnose Therapie Gerät – gehobene Mittelklasse für anspruchsvolle Anwender Akuport M1+/MT Einzeln einfachen Plug&amp;Play-System verbunden bieten Geräte individuelle Arbeitsplatzgestaltung. Vistron Perfekte Kombination Diagnose, Elektrotherapie Informationsübertragung – neueste Modell Produktpalette überzeugt neuartige Technik präzisen Leuchtbandanzeige. DIAGNOSE Akuport M2 Das portable Diagnosegerät integrierter Mundstrommessung, großem Zeigerinstrument Digitalanzeige ideal für Praxis Unterwegs Akuport M1+ Das ideale Einstiegsgerät modernen bioelektrischen Messverfahren EAV erweiterbar modularen System Akuport MT und/oder MR2. THERAPIE Akuport MT Therapiegerät für Elektroakupunktur – Modul M1+ Stand-alone-Version erhältlich. Unsere Geräte zugelassene Medizinprodukte EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling GmbH stellt Kindling GmbH stellt Mit Qualität Kompetenz Impulse setzen Seit 30 Jahren Firma Kindling für Elektroakupunkturgeräte national international bekannt. Als Marktführer Entwicklung Produktion Geräten für Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik wichtiger Partner für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Heilpraktiker, biometrischen Systemdiagnostik befassen. Unsere langjährige Erfahrung intensive Zusammenarbeit unseren Kunden gewährleistet hohen Qualitätsmaßstab ermöglicht uns, Produkte enger Anlehnung Praxis optimieren Neuentwicklungen durchzuführen. Wir zugelassener Entwickler Hersteller Medizinprodukten. Dieses erfordert Einhaltung Anforderungen EU-Richtlinie 93/42/EWG bzw. 2007/47/EWG Vorhandensein überwachten Qualitätssicherungssystems (EN DIN ISO 13485). Die Überwachung Zertifizierung benannte Stelle TÜV NORD CERT GmbH (Kenn-Nummer 0044) durchgeführt. [Zertifizierung] Die Anbringung CE-Zeichens inkl. Kenn-Nummer 0044 unseren Geräten zeigt, zugelassenes zertifiziertes Medizinprodukt handelt. Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE-Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät angebracht sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! Wichtig Kauf Gebrauchtgerätes! Auch Sie Augen aufhalten. Denn vermeidbares Schnäppchen schnell kostspielig werden. Häufig sicherheitstechnische Kontrollen notwendig, Gerät Praxis verwenden dürfen – Verschleißteile z. B. Akku Jahren Nutzung Leistungsgrenzen müssen ausgetauscht werden. Die hohe Qualität Produkte, fachlich kompetente Beratungen zuverlässiger technischer Service Grundlage für feste Marktposition Produkte. So stehen Ihnen persönlich Ort Hildesheim, telefonisch per E-Mail Beratung, Verkauf Service jederzeit Verfügung. Des Weiteren bestehen Vertriebsstrukturen Ländern z. B. Niederlande, Spanien, Schweiz, Kanada, Taiwan, Japan u. a. [Vertrieb] Überzeugen Sie Produktvielfalt Website lassen Sie individuell beraten – Wir Ihre Ansprüche Erstellung optimalen Arbeitsplatzes Ihrer Zufriedenheit erfüllen. Ihr Kindling-Team (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über &gt;&gt; AGBs Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Literaturempfehlungen BIORESONANZ Allergien Tiere heilbar Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Biophysikalische Therapie Allergien Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Allergien nehmen weltweit zu. Allergien entwickeln stets variierende maskierte Formen - zuletzt umweltbedingt. Die Belastungen Asthma bronchiale, Heuschnupfen Neurodermitis reduzieren Lebensqualität Patienten dramatisch. Chemische Suppression Hyposensibilisierungsbehandlung zeigen unzureichend Erfolge erhöhten Nebenwirkungen Gefahren. Anhand langjähriger, sorgfältig dokumentierter Erfolge kinderärztlicher Praxis weist Verfasser nach, daß Allergien vollständig nachhaltig heilbar können, biophysikalisches Phänomen erkennt physikalischen Gesetzen behandelt. Auf Basis 'Bioresonanztherapie' bewährten Konzeption vermittelt Buch umfassend systematisch Grundlagen Praxis biophysikalischen 'Löschung' Allergien - Fremdsubstanzen belastende Nebenwirkungen, insbesondere Aspekt Kinderheilkunde. Bioresonanz - Heilen Medikamente Maasz-Daley, Lerch, Haug Verlag Heilen inneren Kraft: Die Bioresonanztherapie - revolutionäre wirksame Heilmethode - Fachkundigund verständlich beschrieben - Zahlreiche Fallbeispiele, Behandlungsmöglichkeiten anschaulicherläutert werden. Endlich Allergien mehr, Schluß quälenden Kopf- Rückenschmerzen. Die erfolgreiche Heilmethode deutschen Arzt Franz Morell entwickelt. Zahlreiche Beispiele Praxis veranschaulichen, Krankheiten Rheuma, Morbus Bechterew, akuten chronischen Schmerzzuständen, Migräne, Allergien, Asthma, Neurodermitis stressbedingten Erkrankungen bewährt hat. Die Bioresonanztherapie bietet Möglichkeit, Medikamente völlig schmerzlos gesund werden. Sie für Kinder geeignet. Neue Lebenskraft Bioresonanz Dr. med. Dörfler, Simondo Gesundheitsservice Erstmals möglich, Belastungen unseres energetischen Systems exakt erfasen. Die Behandlung greift tief Gefüge ermöglicht es, Patienten "rückwärts Sackgasse Krankheit" herauszuführen. Warum kränker? Wie funktioniert Energiesystem? Wie Diagnostik Therapie sich? Welche Mitarbeit Patienten verlangt? Wie Patient weiterhin gesund erhalten? Welche begleitenden Behandlungen hilfreich sinnvoll? (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec Akuport D-tec Potenzierer Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen – kombinierbar Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP EAV Gerät Vistron . Bei bioenergetischen Testverfahren Potenzreihen Anwendung. Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt elektronische Potenzen, Anwender große Vielfalt komplementär-medizinischen Prozessen ermöglichen. Das Akuport D-tec arbeitet Kombination Geräten für bioenergetische Messverfahren - Stand-alone Version Vistron Retec 2000CP einfachen plug&amp;play-System Akuport MR2. Kindling Akuport D-tec *Potenzstufen: D3, D4, D6, D8, D10, D12, D15, D30, D60, D100, D200 Ausgang Übertragung elektronischen Potenz Trägermedium Potenzierungskontrolle LED-Anzeige *Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil *Modulares System für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Erarbeitung individueller Potenzen Kombination bioenergetischen Messverfahren (EAV, BFD, usw.) Erstellung Auto-Nosoden (z.B. Sekrete, Exkrete) Feststellung Unverträglichkeiten Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das plug&amp;play-System ermöglicht zusätzliches Ergänzen Diagnosegerätes Akuport M1+ Reizstromtherapiemodul Akuport MT kompletten Thereapieeinheit. Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Ausgangsbecher Lieferumfang Maße (BxHxT): 16x6x15cm, Gewicht ca. 200g Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport MR2 Akuport D-tec Adapterleitung für Stromzufuhr Bedienungsanleitung Akuport D-tec stand alone Version Retec 2000CP, Vistron Fremdgeräten Akuport D-tec Netzteil (für MPG-Geräte zugelassen) Verbindungsleitungen Kunststoffabdeckkappe Gehäusedesign Bedienungsanleitung (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Retec 2000 CP Retec 2000 CP Bioresonanz Softwaregesteuertes Bioresonanzgerät für universelle vielseitige Resonanztherapie inkl. 340 automatische Programme Das Retec 2000CP setzt multifunktionelle Einstellung Parameter einzigartige zukunftsorientierte Maßstäbe Resonanztherapie. Es Verbindung extern angeschlossenen PC (Notebook) betrieben. Die Benutzeroberfläche für intuitive Nutzung gestaltet unterstützt Behandlungsablauf sortierte Indikationslisten, gezielt Symptombildern aufgerufen können. Mit Hilfe optisch angezeigten Elektrodenbelegung Bestückung Ausgangsbechers schnelle Einarbeitung erreicht. Verwenden Sie Multitherapie 5 Programme automatisch ablaufen lassen. Oder nutzen Sie manuelle Therapie , Sie notwendigen Parameter anpassen können abspeichern. Auch Möglichkeit elektronische Potenzierung steht Ihnen Verfügung. Multitherapie Die Multitherapie ermöglicht Ihnen automatische Abfolge Programmen erstellen, für evtl. nächste Sitzungen abgespeichert kann. Bis 5 Programme können gewählt werden. Manuelle Therapie Sie können Programme individuell ändern erstellen. Veränderungen Einstellungen können anklicken Schaltsymbole Beschriftungsflächen erreicht werden. Ist Parametergröße Schaltsymbol zugeordnet (z. B. Verstärkereinstellung) öffnet zusätzlich Fenster, Wert eingeschrieben wird. Es können Werte Anklicken Pfeilmarken erhöht (Pfeil oben) verkleinert (Pfeil unten) werden. Potenzieren Die elektronische Potenzierung Substanzen erfolgt Dr.Würthle. Durch Verwendung Harmonischen Dis-Harmonischen Informationen Potenzierung D100 möglich. Kindling Retec 2000CP Therapie Bipolares Therapiegerät Integrierte Ein- Ausgangsplatten *Kindling Special! Externe Bechererweiterung 2 Ein- Ausgänge Differenzverfahren, Umwelteinflüsse Übertragungen *Kindling Special! leichte Handhabung Retec-Hardware übersichtliche Menüführung Software delegierbar Bildhafte Zubehörvorschläge Therapiewahl *Kindling Special! einfaches Update-Verfahren mittels installierender CD-ROM 340 Festprogramme Indikationen sortiert Frequenzbereich 1.000.000 Hz Filterbereich 100.000 Hz automatischer Banddurchlauf Wobbelbetrieb individuell einstellbare Verstärkung 100-fach bzw. Abschwächung 0,01 Therapie-Modus: Seperator-Schaltung (H, DI), direkt invers (A, AI) Testfunktion Ausgangsverstärkers *Kindling Special! Therapiekontrolle LED-Anzeige *Kindling Special! Anzeige verbleibenden Therapiezeit Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil – Opitonal: Akkubetrieb übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen Zubehörablage Geräteoberseite *Kindling Special! baulich abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept Kindling EAV Combi-2 Hohe Störsicherheit externen PC kompatibel handelsüblichen Windows-PCs (Windows XP, Vista, Windows7, Windows8) CD-ROM-Laufwerk freien USB-Port Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Informationsübertragung Medikamentenübertragung Ausleiten Inversübertragung Becherbelegung: Eingang z. B. Nosoden, Viren, Bakterien, Sekrete, Exkrete, Parasiten, Schwermetalle, Virtuelle Datenbank, etc.; Ausgang z.B. Patient, Medium, Globuli, etc. Multitherapie Potenzieren Einlesen Schwingungsmustern Homopath-Software Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-EAV-Geräten speziell EAV-Combi-2 aufeinander abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept Kombinierbar virtuellen Medikamentendatenbanken Softwareprogramme Meditest Homopath umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Eingangs- Augangsbecher, etc. Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messing-Fußelektroden 2 flexible Elektroden 1 Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde 1 Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde 1 Individualisierungsstab/Salbenstab 1 Magnetfeldmatte 2 Paar Retecleitungen 2m 3 Glasschalen Deckel Software Retec 2000pro CD-ROM USB-Verbindungsleitung medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 20x8x38cm, Gewicht ca. 1700g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MR2 Akuport MR2 Bioresonanz Modulares Gerät für Resonanztherapie – Stand-Alone-Version kombinierbar EAV Diagnose-Gerät Akuport M1+ Das Kindling Akuport MR2 erweitert EAV Diagnose moderne Resonanztherapie. Physiologische körpereigene Schwingungen extern vorgegebene Schwingungsinformationen regulieren stabilisieren energetischen Laufbahnen Körper, aktivieren stärken Selbstheilungskräfte. Invers- Direktbetrieb hierfür breiten Frequenzspektrum Anwendung eingesetzt. Durch Kombination virtuellen Medikamenten Softwareprogramme Anwendungsgebiet stark erweitert werden. Kindling Akuport MR2 Therapie *Großer Frequenzbereich 1.000.000 Hz *Hoch- Tiefpass für akute degenerative Behandlung Stufenlose Verstärkung 60-fach, übersichtlich einzustellen Direkt- Invers-Schaltung *Integrierte Ein- Ausgangsplatten *Differenzverfahren, Umwelteinflüsse Übertragungen Externe Bechererweiterung 2 Ein- Ausgänge Breites Indikationsspektrum Timerschaltung Therapiekontrolle LED-Anzeige *Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Direkt- Inverstherapie Medikamentenübertragung Direktübertragung Ausleiten Inversübertragung Becherbelegung: Eingang z. B. Nosoden, Viren, Bakterien, Sekrete, Exkrete, Parasiten, Schwermetalle, Virtuelle Datenbank, etc.; Ausgang z.B. Patient, Medium, Globuli, etc. Einlesen Schwingungsmustern Homopath-Software Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das Akuport MR2 Einzelgerät betrieben jederzeit verschiedenen Modulen erweitert – speziellen Diagnosemodul (M1+) und/oder Reizstromtherapiemodul (MT) einfachen plug&amp;play-System. Einsatz virtuellen Medikamenten Softwareprogramme Meditest Homopath umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Ausgangsbecher Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitungen für Handelektroden abgeschirmtes Leitungspaar Schottglas Glasschale Deckel Abdeckkappe integrierter Ablagefläche Differenz-Abdeckplatte medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g, Grundplatte: 26x23cm Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Personen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über &gt;&gt; Personen Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Personen Der Erfolg Kindling GmbH Verständnis Einsatz Mitarbeiter für Ziele Unternehmens bestimmt. Unsere qualifizierten Mitarbeiter sichern hohen Standard Produkte verantwortungsvolle Arbeit innerhalb Qualitätsmanagementsystems. Die Geschäftsführung setzt Dipl.-Designerin Bürokauffrau Kerstin Abrams Dipl.-Ingenieur Eduard Abrams. Geschäftsgründer heutiger Consultant Franz Schulz vervollständigt unterstützt Team Erfahrung Entwicklung Qualitätsmanagement. Kerstin Abrams Geschäftsführerin Design Marketing Eduard Abrams Geschäftsführer Entwicklung Produktion Qualitätsmanagement Franz Schulz Consultant Entwicklung Qualitätsmanagement </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron Vistron Diagnostics and Therapy, Information transfer Perfect combination of diagnostics, electrotherapy and data transfer – the latest model our product portfolio impress you with its new technology, precision and ease of reading the new LED display. The Vistron combines the diagnostic and therapy component for bio-symmetrical function testing using the Electroacupuncture new, modern, flat housing design. Novelties include among other things the microprocessor-controlled light bar, the inertia-less of the measurement end value, as well as the measured indicator drop. The folding display makes the values optimally reviewable and readable. Membrane keyboards make the device easy to read and operate. The power supply is now provided as standard using high-grade medical power supply, approved under EN 60601-1, or optionally using easily replaceable 12 Volt rechargeable battery. [more details] Along with the proven features diagnostic and therapeutic applications, such as the “Opto-point” point locator the ergonomically designed stylus, you find new EAV functions which simplify processes everyday practice: Kindling Vistron EAV-Diagnostics and Therapy *Stationary operation with power supply Available for portable operation with optional rechargeable battery *Maintenance-free light bar display *Automatic or manual point measurement selectable *Saves the current measurement display until the next measurement is taken Volume of measurement tone can be regulated or turned off Integrated removable large honeycomb; can be switched off with button Tooth electrode that can be placed on the stylus for tooth enamel testing All measurement electrodes expanded assortment *Sweep wave therapy with simultaneous measurement display (T+M) *Expanded frequency spectrum to max. 199 Hz *Frequency range 0-10Hz or 10-100 Hz *Control of individual point therapy Also useable needle stimulation and ear acupuncture *Retec transfer unit for surge substance on carriers *Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Applications Diagnostic measurements and evaluations according to the standards of EAV Comfortable tooth enamel test Direct information transfer: input, e.g. nosodes, homeopathically prepared substances, information from the virtual data bank (Homopath, Meditest) etc; output e.g. medium, globuli, etc, or patient Sweep wave therapy (tonifying and sedating) via acupuncture points: Fixed frequency (0.1 – 19.9 Hz or 10 – 199 Hz); Frequency range (1.0 – 10.0 Hz or 10 – 100 Hz) Special Supplemental Options Extensive special accessories Expandable with all Kindling bioresonance devices Can be combined with EAV software Homopath or the Meditest software program for compiling assessment data and virtual resonance tests, which is available both beginner´s and expert´s version Quadrant switch for testing with hand, foot and forehead electrodes Scope of Delivery Pair of hand electrodes, brass 2 wires for hand electrodes (red, black) Stylus with fixed 4-slice-tip Dental electrode Output beaker XL Retec wire 0,5m Honeycomb ø ca. 10 cm, integrated and removeable Power supply Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 31x5,5(11)x28cm, Weight ca. 2200g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literature Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Literature Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Literature ELECTROACUPUNCTURE Einführung Elektroakupunktur Voll Begher, ML-Verlag Begher vermittelt theoretischen Grundlagen handwerkliche Rüstzeug korrekten, sach fachgerechten Handhabung EAV Praxis legt Integration Homöo Isopathie, Anwendung Therapieprinzips potenzierten Arzneimitteln, objektiver einleuchtender Form. Elektroakupunktur Voll Rossmann, (wird leider aufgelegt) Dieses Buch schildert Wissenswerte Elektroakupunktur: Es informiert u. a. über Grundlagen, Diagnose, Akupunktur- Medikamententest, beschreibt Kur- Heilverfahren vermittelt überraschende Einblicke menschliche Energiespektrum. Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band I) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band II) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Die Meßpunkte Elektroakupunktur Voll Händen Füßen Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Zeichnerische Darstellung Messpunkte Voll Händen Füßen Grundlagen Elektroakupunktur Voll Leonhardt, Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Ein Leitfaden Einführung Elektroakupunktur Systematik Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Grauberger Nosoden Therapie Cornelius, Pflaum Verlag Mit Entdeckung Elektroakupunktur Dr. Reinhold Voll (EAV) hierdurch möglichen Medikamententest Bedeutung Nosoden, klassischen Homöopathie Einsatz kamen, deutlich. Peter Cornelius Buch Zusammenstellung verfügbaren Nosoden wissenschaftlicher Akribie erarbeitet. Atlas Elektroakupunktur Ruf, ML-Verlag Dr. med. Ivor Ruf Atlas (218 Seiten) über 1170 Akupunkturpunkte erstmalig Werk geschaffen, Darstellung Beschreibung klassischen Akupunkturpunkte EAV neu gefundenen Messpunkte beschreibt. Die EAV Voll über 500 Punkte erarbeitet. Diese Zusammenfassung insbesondere für klassischen Akupunkteur Interesse, Bedeutung sowohl EAV-Punkte EAV entschlüsselten klassischen Akupunkturpunkte Beziehung Organen Teilabschnitten gezielten Einsatz für Behandlung Krankheiten Patienten ermöglicht, somit schnelleren therapeutischen Erfolg kann. Der inneren Uhr folgen Da Silva, Goldmann Verlag Der inneren Uhr folgen In zweistündiger Folge gleiche Zeit wandert Energie innerhalb Körpers Organsystem anderen. Kim Silva zeigt, Sie Wissen natürlichen Körperrhythmus Bereich optimal nutzen können: Beruf, kreativer Arbeit Lernen Essen Sexualität. Kommentar GebüH König, Volksheilkunde Verlag Dieser Kommentar beinhaltet erstmalig ausführliche Leistungsbeschreibungen entsprechend analogisierten Regularien Erstattungshinweisen. Die Anforderungen fachgerechte Diagnose ausführlich dargestellt. Die Jahren bewährte Erstattungstabelle Autors, exakten Leistungszuschüsse Beihilfen Postbeamtenkrankenkasse B, kopierfähigen Einlagen Patientenaufklärung abweichenden Honorarvereinbarung Buch für Heilpraktiker unentbehrlichen Nachschlagewerk. Hufeland-Leistungsverzeichnis Besonderen Therapierichtungen Hufelandgesellschaft, Haug Verlag Das Hufelandverzeichnis für Ärzte, Versicherte Patienten wertvolle Orientierungshilfe Abrechnung komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren. Es enthält Analog- GOÄ-Ziffern, anwendbar ambulanten Bereich berücksichtigt private Krankenkassen. Die Auswahl Verfahren erfolgte hoher praktischer Relevanz. So liegt Schwerpunkt Methoden, Naturheilkunde, Homöopathie, Akupunktur Anthroposophischen Medizin Anwendung kommen. Neu: - Tabelle Osteopathie Feldenkrais - Tabelle Ergebnissen Erhebung Qualitätssicherung Komplementärmedizin Mykosen Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen- Diagnose Therapie EAV Voll Homöopathie für Zahnärzte Bartak Dr. Jan Bartak bietet Buch homöopathischen Ratgeber, ständiger Begleiter (zahn-) ärztlichen Alltag konzipert ist. Homöopathie ganzheitliche Medizin pas excellence für beste Einstieg ganzheitliche (Zahn-) Heilkunde. Bei praktischen gezieltem Eingehen (zahn-) ärztliche Praxis Leser onzentrierter Form Geschichte ursprünglichen Grundlagen Homöopathie vertraut gemacht. Ergänzend Bartak komplementäre Methoden - speziell Elektroakupunktur Voll-, homöopathischen Verfahren (zahn-) ärztlichen Praxis harmonisch effektiv ergänzen können. Mikrobiologie + Homöopathie Ruf, ML-Verlag Darmparasitose Humanmedizin • Grundlagen • Klinik • Diagnostik • Therapieanmedizin Fonk, ASKE Verlag DARMPARASITOSE IN DER HUMANMEDIZIN – Grundlagen, Klinik, Diagnostik, Therapie: Lehrbuch, Praxis- Fachinformationen kombiniert. Für wen? Für Leser, zeitaufwändiges Literaturstudium schnell sachlich über Vielschichtigkeit Krankheitsbildes „Darmparasitose“ einschließlich therapeutischen Möglichkeiten informieren möchte. Für modernen Homo sapiens, zuvor vielfältigster Weise Gefahr Parasitose aussetzt, wissen ahnen. Zur Unterstützung Therapeuten, bereit ist, klinischen Blick verlassen handeln, Labor pathologischen Befund ist. Für Medizinstudenten Suche Brückenschlag Theorie Praxis. Für Humanmediziner, Repertoire Darmparasitose Regel vorkommt, für Darmparasiten modernen, hygienebewussten, hightech- pharma-orientierten Generation undenkbar somit Thema unseres Gesundheitswesens darstellen. Dieser Auffassung pragmatisches Handikap Vorschub leisten, nämlich modernen sanitären Anlagen, Stuhlkontrolle Patienten, früher unvermeidlich war, unmöglich machen. Last but not least für notwendige Entwicklung verbesserter, aussagefähigerer finanzierbarer Nachweismethoden für Routine-Labor. Rickettsiose - System Hauterkrankungen Fonk, ASKE Verlag Es Borreliose sein! Wussten Sie, Zecken Biss Infektionscocktail übertragen können? Dazu gehören Borrelien FSME-Viren, Rickettsien (Fleckfieber, Q-Fieber, Wolhynisches Fieber, Zeckenbiss-Fieber, Ehrlichien, Bartonellen), Babesien, Tularämie …. Rickettsien weltweit verbreitet Zecken, Milben (z.B. Grasmilben) Insekten. Rickettsiose – Krankheitsbilder: Gehirnhaut-, Herzinnenhaut-, Herzmuskelentzündungen, atypische Pneumonie, Lungenfibrose, Hepatitis, Polyarthritis, Polyradikulitis, Neurodermitis, Lymphome Non-Hodgkin-Lymphom, T-Zell-Lymphom u.a. Malignom. Dass Krankheiten Rickettsiose verbergen kann, differenzialdiagnostischen Überlegungen berücksichtigt. Diagnostik Rickettsiose: Eine Labordiagnose akuten Krankheitsfall möglich. Die Antikörper-Titer entwickeln Wochen, teilweise Monate Infektion. Hinzukommt, antibiotischen Therapie, Regel sofort eingeleitet wird, Antikörper entwickeln können. Die Rickettsiose unbekanntes Krankheitsbild, tatsächlich großer Bedeutung für Gesundheitswesen. Ohne bio-logische Diagnoseverfahren Diagnose Rickettsiose trotz bester, modernster High-Tech-Laborausrüstung akuten Stadium, häufig Spätstadium, gestellt. Das medizinische Paradigma Hanzl, Haug Verlag Brückenschlag Schulmedizin Komplementärmedizin: Dieses Buch beitragen, Kluft Schulmedizin naturheilkundlichen regulationsmedizinischen Verfahren überbrücken. Es klassischen Schulmediziner zeigen, daß Anpassung medizinischen Modelle modernste (natur-)wissenschaftliche Erkenntnisse Kybernetik, Systemtheorie, Quantenphysik Chaosforschung, neues medizinisches Paradigma, bestehende Misere Gebiet chronischer Erkrankungen überwunden kann. Den wissenschaftlichen Fundierung interessierten Vertretern komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren zeigen, daß Großteil Verfahren streng wissenschaftlich begründbar ist. Von Prof. Dr. F.-A. Popp Buch Bibel für komplementärmedizinischen Verfahren bezeichnet. Elektroakupunktur zahnärztl. Praxis Kramer, ML-Verlag Die Elektroakupunktur Krankheiten Ausbruch erkennen, Belastungen Körpers Umweltgifte austesten, Medikamentenrückstände -schäden messen, Allergieneigung testen, Krankheitsherde aufspüren Behandlungserfolge kontrollieren. Für Zahnarzt Elektroakupunktur besonderer Bedeutung, Basis üblichen klinischen Diagnostik zusätzliche Hilfe gibt, soliden odontogenen Herddiagnostik kommen. Kompendium Elektroakupunktur Rossmann, Haug-Verlag Praxisorientierte Einführung Grundlagen systematischen Elektroakupunktur Voll. Das System Grundregulation Pischinger, Haug Verlag Mit Fachbuch liegt Hauptwerk für wissenschaftliche Begründung biologischen Medizin Erklärungsmodell für Vielzahl komplementäerer Heilverfahren vor. Es liefert praxisorientierte, verständliche Einführung komplexe Materie: Das System Grundregulation bildet Pischinger Wechselwirkungen Zelle-Milieu-System ab. Es Gegenstand Entzündungs- Abwehrvorgänge zuständig für Lebensgrundlagenfunktionen. Anhaltende Störungen Grundregulation behindern genetisch programmierte Zellfunktion Krankheitserscheinungen Folge. Das Grundregulationssystem Erklärungsmodell Vielzahl komplementärer Heilverfahren. wendbares Konzept integriert: Humoralpathologie, Organpathologie, Neuralpathologie, Zellular- Permeabilitätspathologie. Wandlungsphasen Max + Moritz Pollmann, Haug Verlag Der Einstieg Denkweise Chinesischen Medizin, Welt Analogien Bildvergleiche, fällt westlich ausgebildeten Arzt leicht. Die grundlegende Lehre "Fünf Wandlungsphasen" "Fünf Elemente" Buch verständlich, einprägsam anschaulich dargestellt. Uns vertraute bekannte Figuren Wilhelm Buschs "Max Moritz", setzt Autor Beziehung Wesensart fünf Elemente. Wer hätte gedacht, daß Lehrer Lämpel, Schneider Böck guten Onkel Fritz Analogien chinesischen Typologie finden ließen? Der Leser findet Buch heitere, treffende Einführung Theorie Chinesischen Medizin konkrete diagnostische therapeutische Hinweise für Akupunkturpraxis, frei Motto: "Aber Weisheit Lehren muß Vergnügen hören." Das hyperaktive Kind Rosival, Ravensburger Nicht Hyperaktivität Hauptproblem "hyperaktiven Kinder", Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, hohe Sensibilität Impulsivität. Solche Kinder immer. Nur fallen Gesellschaft, unserem Schulsystem eher leiden, Eltern Erzieher, darunter, daß steuern können, Umfeld gefordert wird. Dieser Ratgeber erklärt beschreibt Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, Hyperaktivität auftreten kann, veranschaulicht Erscheinungsbild Beispielen Eltern Mut, Leben Kind schwieriger, hoffnungslos ist. Infektionskrankheiten Umweltgifte Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen ganzheitlich betrachtet Häring, Pro-Medicina Verlag Ein modernes Lehrbuch Mykologie Fotos Dokumentationen Praxis. Die häufigsten pathogenen Mykoseerreger eingehend beschrieben. Außerdem gezeigt, mykotische Keime Organismus ausbreiten Krankheitssymptomen führen können. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MT Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Akuport MT Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport MT EAV-Therapy Modular therapy device for the Elektroacupunctur The Kindling Akuport MT perfects EAV diagnosis through immediate therapeutic application with low-frequency impulses. Rectified or non-rectified sweep waves regulate and stabilise the energetic meridians the body. The six most important, specific frequencies are available up to1/10 hz precision. Application proceeds using surface electrodes or is targeted using the stylus on the Akuport M1+. With simple attachment (plug &amp; play), Akuport MT is combined with the EAV measurement device Akuport M1+ and is immediately ready to use. Kindling Akuport MT EAV Therapy Low frequency therapeutic applications *6 selected, specific frequencies (1.7 Hz, 2.4 Hz, 4 Hz, 6 Hz, 9.4 Hz, 10 Hz) 3 impulse forms for tonifying or sedation Intensity regulator, continuous High-performance therapeutic output *Dampened output for needle stimulation *Direct application using the stylus of the Akuport M1+ High-performance rechargeable batteries for up to 8 hours full-capacity operation Built-in interface for easy expansion plug &amp; play system *Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Therapeutic application with low-frequency electrical impulses following the standards of EAV Special Supplemental Options Expandable with EAV diagnostic module Akuport M1+ and with the bioresonance module Akuport MR2 plug &amp; play system Extensive special accessories, e. g. for needle stimulation Scope of Delivery Stand-Alone: Pair of hand electrodes, brass 2 wires for hand electrodes (red, black) 2 rechargeable batteries Charger Operating instructions In addition to Akuport M1+: Wire for hand electrode (red) 2 rechargeable batteries Charger Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 16x11x15cm, Weight ca. 400g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MT Modul Combination Akuport Tower Modul Combination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnostics The ideal starting device for the modern bioelectrical assessment procedures of EAV; expandable modular system with the Akuport MT and/or MR2. The Kindling Akuport M1+ is practical EAV diagnostic device constructed accord with the newest findings, and provides both beginners and experienced therapists with cost-efficient variant. The Akuport M1+ can be very easily expanded into complete unit (Akuport Tower) through its modular, plug-in system (plug &amp; play) with the EAV therapy component (MT) and/or with the bioresonance device (MR2) to make complete unit (Akuport Tower). Kindling Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnostics *EAV measurement system which meets the official standards of the International Medical Association for the Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll (EAV) Clear, easy-to-read pointer instrument *Ergonomically designed stylus with mounted, pressure compensated, replaceable sensor tip Optical point detector device the stylus Acoustic measurement support *Spread of scale (TP-Regulator) Battery operation Clear, easy-to-read operating displays *PC-connection port for working with Meditest or Homopath software using USB-interface *Built-in module interface for easy expansion plug &amp; play-system * Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Diagnostic measurements and evaluations according to the standards of EAV Testing with various products, incompatibilities, location contaminant loads and substances, etc. Special Supplemental Options The Akuport M1+ can be operated as individual device and expanded as basic device with various modules Expandable with the electrical stimulation therapy module (Akuport MT) and/or the bioresonance module (Akuport MR2) simple plug &amp; play system Can be combined with EAV software Homopath or the Meditest software program for compiling assessment data and virtual resonance tests, which is available both beginner´s and expert´s version Quadrant switch for testing with hand, foot and forehead electrodes Also available BFD-configuration with silver electrodes and silver measurement probe Extensive specialised accessories Scope of Delivery Pair of hand electrodes, brass Wire for hand electrode (black) Stylus with 4-slice-tip Honeycomb ø ca. 5 cm Wire for honeycomb Battery (9V-Block) Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 16x11x15cm, Weight ca. 400g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Ergonomically designed stylus Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MT Akuport M1+/MR2 Akuport Tower Modul combination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M2 Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Akuport M2 Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M2 EAV-Diagnostics This portable diagnostic device with integrated measurement of electrical current the mouth, large display instrument and digital display is ideal for the practice and for portable use. The individualised calibration of electrical potential of the skin and the option of measuring electrical current the mouth of the Akuport M2 provide both the beginner and the experienced therapist with optimal metrological preconditions for comfortable EAV. Kindling Akuport M2 Diagnostics *EAV measurement system which meets the official standards of the International Medical Association for the Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll (EAV) *Large, easy to read display *Digital display shows indicator-drop *Ergonomically designed stylus with mounted, pressure compensated, replaceable sensor tip *Optical point locating "OPTO-Point" with 10-digit-LED-bar the stylus and individual skin moisture compensation Large honeycomb with different hole sizes Acoustic measurement support through controllable tone Spread of scale (TP-Regulator) Built-in high performance rechargeable battery for 60 hours of operating time Automatic-charging device Clear, easy-to-read operating displays *PC-connection port for working with Meditest or Homopath software using USB-interface *Kindling Special ! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Diagnostic measurements and evaluations according to the standards of EAV Testing with various products, incompatibilities, location contaminant loads and substances, etc. Optional: Measurement of electrical current the mouth to detect foreign potential the oral cavity Special Supplemental Options Expandable with all Kindling bioresonance devices Can be combined with EAV software Homopath or the Meditest software program for compiling assessment data and virtual resonance tests, which is available both beginner´s and expert´s version Quadrant switch for testing with hand, foot and forehead electrodes Extensive special accessories, e. g. dental electrodes Scope of Delivery Pair of hand electrodes, brass 2 wires for hand electrodes (red, black) Stylus with 4-slice-tip Ball tip Honeycomb ø ca. 10 cm Wire for honeycomb Charger Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 21x9x13cm, Weight ca. 1000g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Ergonomically designed stylus Upgrade to Combi-2 EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Combi-2 Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Combi-2 Diagnostics and Therapy Versatility of diagnostics and treatment one device – the premium middle class for demanding users. Flexibility and reliable performance are characteristic of the Combi-2 and indispensible for modern EAV practices. The versatile characteristics of the device offer the therapist, whatever his/her specialty, basis for mature bio-energetic treatment plan. The Combi-2 combines modern metrological prerequisites for reliable diagnosis with various therapeutic applications through low frequency electrical impulses for regulating the body’s energetic meridians. Kindling Combi-2 EAV-Diagnostics and Therapy *EAV measurement system which meets the official standards of the International Medical Association for the Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll (EAV) *Large, removable display for individual placement the workplace Digital display (LCD) for indicator drop, conductance, frequency and tooth potential *Ergonomically designed stylus with mounted, pressure compensated, replaceable sensor tip *Optical point locating "OPTO-Point" with 10-digit-LED-bar the stylus and individual skin moisture compensation Spread of scale (TP-Regler) Acoustic measurement support through controllable tone *Sound reset switch – regulates the start of the accompanying signal tone Large, integrated honeycomb Modern membrane keyboard Built-in high performance rechargeable battery for 10 hours’ full output operation – *Optional: power supply from mains with medical power adapter Automatic-recharger or medical power adaptor Easy-to-read operating display *PC-connection port for working with Meditest or Homopath software using USB-interface *Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Diagnostic measurements and evaluations according to the standards of EAV Testing with various products, incompatibilities, location contaminant loads and substances, etc. Electrical stimulation therapy: Fixed frequency (0.1 – 19.9 Hz), frequency variation (1 – 10.0 Hz), current types: sedating, tonifying, sweep waves Current types: sedating, tonifying, sweep waves Measure of electrical potential teeth and comfortable tooth sensitivity test Special Supplemental Options Expandable with all Kindling bioresonance, especially with the Retec 2000, thanks to housing designed with each of the units mind Can be combined with EAV software Homopath or the Meditest software program for compiling assessment data and virtual resonance tests, which is available both beginner´s and expert´s version Quadrant switch for testing with hand, foot and forehead electrodes Extensive special accessories Optional: power supply from mains with medical power supply Scope of Delivery Pair of hand electrodes, brass 2 wires for hand electrodes (red, black) Stylus with 4-slice-tip Ball tip Honeycomb ø ca. 10 cm, integrated Pair of dental electrodes Charger, optional: power supply Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 21x23x18cm, Weight ca. 1700g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Ergonomically designed stylus Combi-2 / Retec 2000C EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Potentizer Akuport D-tec Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Vistron &gt;&gt; Potentizer Akuport D-tec Vistron Details Potentizer Akuport D-tec Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Potentizer Akuport D-tec Potentizer The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies. Can be combined with the bioresonance devices Akuport MR2 or RETEC 2000CP and the EAV diagnostic device Vistron. The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies that allow the user to use wide diversity of complementary medical processes. With the Akuport D-tec you can determine which potency is necessary every individual case. The Akuport D-tec works combination with other devices for bioenergetic methods - as stand-alone-version with the Vistron and Retec 2000CP or with the Akuport MR2 by plug&amp;play system. Kindling Akuport D-tec *Potency ranges: D3, D4, D6, D8, D10, D12, D15, D30, D60, D100, D200 Output for transfering the electronic potency to carrier medium Potentizing controll through LED display *Power supply from mains with medical power supply *Built-in module interface for easy expansion plug &amp; play-system *Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Preparation of individual potencies combination with bioenergetic methods (EAV, BFD, etc.) Preparation of auto-nosodes (e.g. with Sekrete, Exkrete) Diagnosis of allergies and intolerances Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Plug&amp;play-system allows supplement with the diagnosis device Akuport M1+, theray device Akuport MT and bioresonance MR2 to complete therapy unit (Akuport Tower) Extensive special accessories, e.g. screened output beaker Scope of Delivery Akuport D-tec as stand alone version with Retec 2000CP, Vistron or external device 1 Akuport D-tec 1 Power supply 1 Connection cable (Chinch-Chinch) 1 Cover cap (in housing design) 1 operation manual Vistron </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Details Vistron Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture &gt;&gt; Vistron &gt;&gt; Details Vistron Details Potentizer Akuport D-tec Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Details Vistron Vistron is electroacupuncture device with diagnostic and therapeutic component for bio-symmetrical function testing the Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll. The laptop-like housing allows the Vistron to be comfortably transported and the folding display makes optimal positioning at your work place possible. Power is supplied as standard using medical power supply, approved under EN 60601-1, or optionally using 12 Volt rechargeable battery. The medical power supply is used to recharge the battery. Acupuncture point measurements are displayed analogue as bar light bar display or as dot (energy saver mode). The measurement scale is divided into 0-100 lines, whereby the normal value range for points is 50-70, and that for hand measurements 80-90, both correspondingly marked. Measurement can be taken automatically, which shows the highest value and the indicator drop, or manually. An integrated honeycomb that can be turned off or detached enables the resonance test. Localisation of acupuncture points is affected on the LED-lighted indicator band the stylus using difference measurement against previously-recorded dermal baseline. Six of the nine digits the LED band are yellow, the rest are green. Depending on the height of the display, you move toward the point (yellow range) or if the green range, you have exactly localised it. An acoustic signal accompanies the display and the tone pitch varies depending on the value measured. The measurement tips on the stylus are exchangeable. The button on the stylus allows easy switching between diagnosis and treatment. Three types of impulses are available as treatment types: 1. Alternating sweep wave 2. Positive sweep wave 3. Negative sweep wave The treatment voltage is reached from low operating current through stepping up. The desired amplitude peak can be set with regulator. Safe isolation from the lighting grid is provided by the medical power supply compliant with ISO DIN 60601-1. Alternatively, the device can be operated using optional rechargeable battery. The control buttons for diagnosis (left blue) and treatment (right yellow) are arranged the control component. The treatment intensity regulator is located between them. The on/off button is green and located on the bottom right. The Vistron shuts off automatically after 20 minutes of inactivity. The honeycomb is located on the left and can be detached or turned off at the push of button. Operating conditions are shown the modern display, which can be adjusted to your optimal viewing angle: Operating functions are white and variable functions yellow. Battery status is shown with six-digit light band, depending on charge capacity. A 10-digit light band displays the intensity. Connection ports for accessories are located on the back. These include the stylus, hand electrodes and external honeycombs. Also located there is the jack for the AC/DC converter (computer connection), the volume control and the power supply jack. The integrated surge function serves as amplifier for homeopathic test substances. Time and intensity are fixed pre-sets. [back to Vistron main page ] Ergonomically designed stylus Potentizer Akuport D-tec combination with Vistron EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Firmenchronik Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über &gt;&gt; Firmenchronik Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Firmenchronik 1956 Firmengründung Marie-Luise Kindling Hannover 1956 Nervenpunktdetektor 1 für Punktlokalisation 1959 Nervenpunktdetektor 2 Messanzeige 1966 Nervenpunktdetektor 3 Messanzeige Therapieteil 1972 Nervenpunktdetektor 4 EAV-Gerät Akku-Betrieb 1978 Nervenpunktdetektor 4B Transistorisiertes EAV-Gerät Akku-Betrieb 1980 Übergang Firma Kindling Kindling GmbH Sitz Hildesheim Inhabender Geschäftsführer: Franz Schulz 1980 Akuport M; EAV-Reisegerät 1983 Kindling 2000 Komfort-EAV-Gerät Druckmessanzeige 1985 Computerunterstützte EAV Programmen ELADI (MS-DOS) HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer (ATARI) 1987 Vorstellung EAV-Geräte Dr. Voll 1988 Aufnahme Int. Ärztegesellschaft für EAV Präsident Dr. Fehrenbach 1990 Software ELADI MT Medikamententest 1993 Vorstellung RETEC-Therapie (Bioresonanz) RETEC 2000 1994 EAV-Combi 2 ersetzt Nervenpunktdetektor 4B 1995 ELADI VT Software virtueller Medikamententestung 1996 Software HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer Windows-Version 1996 Computergestützte EAV-System-Diagnostik Kindling 2000, Retec 2000 1997 RETEC 3000 Computergesteuerte, 2 Kanal multiplex, Resonanztherapie 1998 Umzug Gropiusstrasse Erweiterung Produktionsmöglichkeiten 1999 Kooperation Firma MBA GmbH für Vertrieb Service 1999 Erste Zertifizierung ISO-Norm 9000 2000 Akuport Plug-and-Play Modulsystem M1, MT MR 2002 Das EAV-Combi-2 2003 Kindling 2000s überarbeitete Version Design 2003 Curator Lichttherapiegerät Global Scaling Zusammenarbeit I.R.E.F. 2004 Retec 2000c Kompaktgerät neuer Software 2004 USB-Technologie für Software 2005 Zertifizierung Medizinprodukte-Norm EN ISO 13485 2005 Firmenjubiläum 25 Jahre Kindling Hildesheim 2007 Akuport MR2 Nachfolger Akuport MR 2008 Wechsel Geschäftsführung Dipl.-Des. Kerstin Abrams Dipl.-Ing. Eduard Abrams 2008 Canadische Zertifizierung CAN/CSA ISO 13485 2009 Vistron ; Generation EAV 2011 Akuport D-tec ; Potenzierer 2015 Kindling EASY ; Selbstkalibrierendes Bioresonanz-Gerät Nervenpunktdetektor 4B 1978 Akuport - EAV-Reisegerät 1980 Kindling 2000 1983 Kindling 2000 1990 Retec2000 1993 Kindling 2000S Kombination Retec 2000C </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zertifizierung Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über &gt;&gt; Zertifizierung Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Zertifizierung Zertifizierte Qualität Kindling GmbH gesetzlichen Vorgaben angepasstes, integriertes zertifiziertes Qualitätsmanagementsystem. Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät versehen sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! EG-Zertifikat gem. 93/42/EWG Anhang II Zertifikat gem. DIN EN ISO 13485 Zertifikat gem. CAN/CSA ISO 13485 </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Qualitätsmanagment Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Über &gt;&gt; Qualitätsmanagment Qualitätsmanagment Zertifizierung Firmenchronik Personen Kontakt Impressum AGBs | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Qualitätsmanagment Die Kindling GmbH 1999 gesetzlichen Vorgaben Strategie ausgerichtetes Qualitätsmanagementsystem aufgebaut, höchsten Qualitätsansprüchen Gebiet Medizintechnik gerecht werden. Das Qualitätsmanagementsystem DIN ISO 13485 TÜV NORD CERT GmbH überwacht zertifiziert. [Zertifizierung] Um Qualität Produkte, Prozesse Service gewährleisten, Arbeit folgenden Grundsätze bestimmt: Unsere Kunden Unsere Kunden stehen für Stelle. Wir müssen gegenwärtige zukünftige Erfordernisse Kunden verstehen, Anforderungen erfüllen streben, Erwartungen übertreffen. Die Erfüllung Kundenansprüche erfordert stets hohes Qualitätsniveau. Ein faires Preis-Leistungsverhältnis Produkte wichtig. Deshalb streben danach, unnötige Kosten vermeiden, vernünftigen Preise Produkte beibehalten können. Aufträge Kunden umgehend zuverlässig ausgeführt werden. Unsere Ziele Die ständige Verbesserung Gesamtleistung, Aufrechterhaltung Wirksamkeit Qualitätsmanagementsystems unseres Unternehmens, stellt permanentes Ziel dar, über Qualität Produkte gewährleisten. Die Kindling GmbH fühlt Qualitätspolitik verpflichtet, Mitarbeiter verantwortungsvollen aktiven Sicherung Qualität Produkte, Prozesse Service innerhalb jeweiligen Arbeitsumgebung aufgerufen. Unsere Mitarbeiter Auf Ebenen Mitarbeiter Wesen unseres Unternehmens aus. Die vollständige Einbeziehung Mitarbeiter ermöglicht, Fähigkeiten fördern Nutzen Unternehmens einzusetzen. Für Mitarbeiter Prinzip Fehlervermeidung Vorrang Fehlerbehebung. Ein systematisches Projektmanagement Einsatz verschiedenen Methoden Techniken Überprüfung garantiert, Produkt vorgegebenen Qualitätsansprüche erfüllt. Die Qualifizierung Validierung Produktionsprozessen stellt sicher, spezifizierte Produktqualität erreicht wird. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Literaturempfehlungen Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Literaturempfehlungen ELEKTROAKUPUNKTUR Einführung Elektroakupunktur Voll Begher, ML-Verlag Begher vermittelt theoretischen Grundlagen handwerkliche Rüstzeug korrekten, sach fachgerechten Handhabung EAV Praxis legt Integration Homöo Isopathie, Anwendung Therapieprinzips potenzierten Arzneimitteln, objektiver einleuchtender Form. Elektroakupunktur Voll Rossmann, (wird leider aufgelegt) Dieses Buch schildert Wissenswerte Elektroakupunktur: Es informiert u. a. über Grundlagen, Diagnose, Akupunktur- Medikamententest, beschreibt Kur- Heilverfahren vermittelt überraschende Einblicke menschliche Energiespektrum. Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band I) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band II) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Die Meßpunkte Elektroakupunktur Voll Händen Füßen Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Zeichnerische Darstellung Messpunkte Voll Händen Füßen Grundlagen Elektroakupunktur Voll Leonhardt, Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Ein Leitfaden Einführung Elektroakupunktur Systematik Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Grauberger Nosoden Therapie Cornelius, Pflaum Verlag Mit Entdeckung Elektroakupunktur Dr. Reinhold Voll (EAV) hierdurch möglichen Medikamententest Bedeutung Nosoden, klassischen Homöopathie Einsatz kamen, deutlich. Peter Cornelius Buch Zusammenstellung verfügbaren Nosoden wissenschaftlicher Akribie erarbeitet. Atlas Elektroakupunktur Ruf, ML-Verlag Dr. med. Ivor Ruf Atlas (218 Seiten) über 1170 Akupunkturpunkte erstmalig Werk geschaffen, Darstellung Beschreibung klassischen Akupunkturpunkte EAV neu gefundenen Messpunkte beschreibt. Die EAV Voll über 500 Punkte erarbeitet. Diese Zusammenfassung insbesondere für klassischen Akupunkteur Interesse, Bedeutung sowohl EAV-Punkte EAV entschlüsselten klassischen Akupunkturpunkte Beziehung Organen Teilabschnitten gezielten Einsatz für Behandlung Krankheiten Patienten ermöglicht, somit schnelleren therapeutischen Erfolg kann. Der inneren Uhr folgen Da Silva, Goldmann Verlag Der inneren Uhr folgen In zweistündiger Folge gleiche Zeit wandert Energie innerhalb Körpers Organsystem anderen. Kim Silva zeigt, Sie Wissen natürlichen Körperrhythmus Bereich optimal nutzen können: Beruf, kreativer Arbeit Lernen Essen Sexualität. Kommentar GebüH König, Volksheilkunde Verlag Dieser Kommentar beinhaltet erstmalig ausführliche Leistungsbeschreibungen entsprechend analogisierten Regularien Erstattungshinweisen. Die Anforderungen fachgerechte Diagnose ausführlich dargestellt. Die Jahren bewährte Erstattungstabelle Autors, exakten Leistungszuschüsse Beihilfen Postbeamtenkrankenkasse B, kopierfähigen Einlagen Patientenaufklärung abweichenden Honorarvereinbarung Buch für Heilpraktiker unentbehrlichen Nachschlagewerk. Hufeland-Leistungsverzeichnis Besonderen Therapierichtungen Hufelandgesellschaft, Haug Verlag Das Hufelandverzeichnis für Ärzte, Versicherte Patienten wertvolle Orientierungshilfe Abrechnung komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren. Es enthält Analog- GOÄ-Ziffern, anwendbar ambulanten Bereich berücksichtigt private Krankenkassen. Die Auswahl Verfahren erfolgte hoher praktischer Relevanz. So liegt Schwerpunkt Methoden, Naturheilkunde, Homöopathie, Akupunktur Anthroposophischen Medizin Anwendung kommen. Neu: - Tabelle Osteopathie Feldenkrais - Tabelle Ergebnissen Erhebung Qualitätssicherung Komplementärmedizin Mykosen Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen- Diagnose Therapie EAV Voll Homöopathie für Zahnärzte Bartak Dr. Jan Bartak bietet Buch homöopathischen Ratgeber, ständiger Begleiter (zahn-) ärztlichen Alltag konzipert ist. Homöopathie ganzheitliche Medizin pas excellence für beste Einstieg ganzheitliche (Zahn-) Heilkunde. Bei praktischen gezieltem Eingehen (zahn-) ärztliche Praxis Leser onzentrierter Form Geschichte ursprünglichen Grundlagen Homöopathie vertraut gemacht. Ergänzend Bartak komplementäre Methoden - speziell Elektroakupunktur Voll-, homöopathischen Verfahren (zahn-) ärztlichen Praxis harmonisch effektiv ergänzen können. Mikrobiologie + Homöopathie Ruf, ML-Verlag Darmparasitose Humanmedizin • Grundlagen • Klinik • Diagnostik • Therapieanmedizin Fonk, ASKE Verlag DARMPARASITOSE IN DER HUMANMEDIZIN – Grundlagen, Klinik, Diagnostik, Therapie: Lehrbuch, Praxis- Fachinformationen kombiniert. Für wen? Für Leser, zeitaufwändiges Literaturstudium schnell sachlich über Vielschichtigkeit Krankheitsbildes „Darmparasitose“ einschließlich therapeutischen Möglichkeiten informieren möchte. Für modernen Homo sapiens, zuvor vielfältigster Weise Gefahr Parasitose aussetzt, wissen ahnen. Zur Unterstützung Therapeuten, bereit ist, klinischen Blick verlassen handeln, Labor pathologischen Befund ist. Für Medizinstudenten Suche Brückenschlag Theorie Praxis. Für Humanmediziner, Repertoire Darmparasitose Regel vorkommt, für Darmparasiten modernen, hygienebewussten, hightech- pharma-orientierten Generation undenkbar somit Thema unseres Gesundheitswesens darstellen. Dieser Auffassung pragmatisches Handikap Vorschub leisten, nämlich modernen sanitären Anlagen, Stuhlkontrolle Patienten, früher unvermeidlich war, unmöglich machen. Last but not least für notwendige Entwicklung verbesserter, aussagefähigerer finanzierbarer Nachweismethoden für Routine-Labor. Rickettsiose - System Hauterkrankungen Fonk, ASKE Verlag Es Borreliose sein! Wussten Sie, Zecken Biss Infektionscocktail übertragen können? Dazu gehören Borrelien FSME-Viren, Rickettsien (Fleckfieber, Q-Fieber, Wolhynisches Fieber, Zeckenbiss-Fieber, Ehrlichien, Bartonellen), Babesien, Tularämie …. Rickettsien weltweit verbreitet Zecken, Milben (z.B. Grasmilben) Insekten. Rickettsiose – Krankheitsbilder: Gehirnhaut-, Herzinnenhaut-, Herzmuskelentzündungen, atypische Pneumonie, Lungenfibrose, Hepatitis, Polyarthritis, Polyradikulitis, Neurodermitis, Lymphome Non-Hodgkin-Lymphom, T-Zell-Lymphom u.a. Malignom. Dass Krankheiten Rickettsiose verbergen kann, differenzialdiagnostischen Überlegungen berücksichtigt. Diagnostik Rickettsiose: Eine Labordiagnose akuten Krankheitsfall möglich. Die Antikörper-Titer entwickeln Wochen, teilweise Monate Infektion. Hinzukommt, antibiotischen Therapie, Regel sofort eingeleitet wird, Antikörper entwickeln können. Die Rickettsiose unbekanntes Krankheitsbild, tatsächlich großer Bedeutung für Gesundheitswesen. Ohne bio-logische Diagnoseverfahren Diagnose Rickettsiose trotz bester, modernster High-Tech-Laborausrüstung akuten Stadium, häufig Spätstadium, gestellt. Das medizinische Paradigma Hanzl, Haug Verlag Brückenschlag Schulmedizin Komplementärmedizin: Dieses Buch beitragen, Kluft Schulmedizin naturheilkundlichen regulationsmedizinischen Verfahren überbrücken. Es klassischen Schulmediziner zeigen, daß Anpassung medizinischen Modelle modernste (natur-)wissenschaftliche Erkenntnisse Kybernetik, Systemtheorie, Quantenphysik Chaosforschung, neues medizinisches Paradigma, bestehende Misere Gebiet chronischer Erkrankungen überwunden kann. Den wissenschaftlichen Fundierung interessierten Vertretern komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren zeigen, daß Großteil Verfahren streng wissenschaftlich begründbar ist. Von Prof. Dr. F.-A. Popp Buch Bibel für komplementärmedizinischen Verfahren bezeichnet. Elektroakupunktur zahnärztl. Praxis Kramer, ML-Verlag Die Elektroakupunktur Krankheiten Ausbruch erkennen, Belastungen Körpers Umweltgifte austesten, Medikamentenrückstände -schäden messen, Allergieneigung testen, Krankheitsherde aufspüren Behandlungserfolge kontrollieren. Für Zahnarzt Elektroakupunktur besonderer Bedeutung, Basis üblichen klinischen Diagnostik zusätzliche Hilfe gibt, soliden odontogenen Herddiagnostik kommen. Kompendium Elektroakupunktur Rossmann, Haug-Verlag Praxisorientierte Einführung Grundlagen systematischen Elektroakupunktur Voll. Das System Grundregulation Pischinger, Haug Verlag Mit Fachbuch liegt Hauptwerk für wissenschaftliche Begründung biologischen Medizin Erklärungsmodell für Vielzahl komplementäerer Heilverfahren vor. Es liefert praxisorientierte, verständliche Einführung komplexe Materie: Das System Grundregulation bildet Pischinger Wechselwirkungen Zelle-Milieu-System ab. Es Gegenstand Entzündungs- Abwehrvorgänge zuständig für Lebensgrundlagenfunktionen. Anhaltende Störungen Grundregulation behindern genetisch programmierte Zellfunktion Krankheitserscheinungen Folge. Das Grundregulationssystem Erklärungsmodell Vielzahl komplementärer Heilverfahren. wendbares Konzept integriert: Humoralpathologie, Organpathologie, Neuralpathologie, Zellular- Permeabilitätspathologie. Wandlungsphasen Max + Moritz Pollmann, Haug Verlag Der Einstieg Denkweise Chinesischen Medizin, Welt Analogien Bildvergleiche, fällt westlich ausgebildeten Arzt leicht. Die grundlegende Lehre "Fünf Wandlungsphasen" "Fünf Elemente" Buch verständlich, einprägsam anschaulich dargestellt. Uns vertraute bekannte Figuren Wilhelm Buschs "Max Moritz", setzt Autor Beziehung Wesensart fünf Elemente. Wer hätte gedacht, daß Lehrer Lämpel, Schneider Böck guten Onkel Fritz Analogien chinesischen Typologie finden ließen? Der Leser findet Buch heitere, treffende Einführung Theorie Chinesischen Medizin konkrete diagnostische therapeutische Hinweise für Akupunkturpraxis, frei Motto: "Aber Weisheit Lehren muß Vergnügen hören." Das hyperaktive Kind Rosival, Ravensburger Nicht Hyperaktivität Hauptproblem "hyperaktiven Kinder", Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, hohe Sensibilität Impulsivität. Solche Kinder immer. Nur fallen Gesellschaft, unserem Schulsystem eher leiden, Eltern Erzieher, darunter, daß steuern können, Umfeld gefordert wird. Dieser Ratgeber erklärt beschreibt Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, Hyperaktivität auftreten kann, veranschaulicht Erscheinungsbild Beispielen Eltern Mut, Leben Kind schwieriger, hoffnungslos ist. Infektionskrankheiten Umweltgifte Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen ganzheitlich betrachtet Häring, Pro-Medicina Verlag Ein modernes Lehrbuch Mykologie Fotos Dokumentationen Praxis. Die häufigsten pathogenen Mykoseerreger eingehend beschrieben. Außerdem gezeigt, mykotische Keime Organismus ausbreiten Krankheitssymptomen führen können. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MT Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Akuport MT Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport MT EAV-Therapie Modulares Therapieteil für Elektroakupunktur Voll Das Kindling Akuport MT perfektioniert EAV-Diagnose sofortige Therapieanwendung niederfrequenten Stromimpulsen. Gleich- wechselgerichtete Kippschwingungen regulieren stabilisieren energetischen Laufbahnen Körper. Hierzu stehen 6 wichtigsten, spezifischen Frequenzen 1/10 hz genau Verfügung. Die Applikation erfolgt über Flächenelektroden gezielt über Punktsonde Akuport M1+. Durch einfaches Aufsetzen (plug&amp;play) Akuport MT EAV-Messgerät Akuport M1+ kombiniert sofort einsatzbereit. Kindling EAV Akuport MT Therapie Niederfrequenztherapieanwendungen *6 ausgewählte, spezifische Frequenzen (1.7 Hz, 2.4 Hz, 4 Hz, 6 Hz, 9.4 Hz, 10 Hz) 3 Impulsformen Tonisieren Sedieren Intensitätsregler, stufenlos Leistungsstarker Therapieausgang *Gedämpfter Ausgang Nadelstimulation *Direkte Applikation über Punktsonde Akuport M1+ leistungsstarke Akkus für 8 Stunden Vollbetrieb eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling ! Anwendungen Therapieanwendung niederfrequenten Stromimpulsen Standards EAV Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar EAV-Diagnosemodul Akuport M1+ Bioresonanzmodul (MR2) plug&amp;play-System Erweiterbar Kindling EAV-Modellen Sonderzubehör z. B. für Nadelstimulation Zahnreizmessung Lieferumfang Stand-Alone: 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitungen für Handelektrode (schwarz rot) 2 wiederaufladbare 9V-Block-Batterien Ladegerät Betriebsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Als Modulergänzung M1+: Messleitung für Handelektrode (rot) 2 wiederaufladbare 9V-Block-Batterien Automatik-Ladegerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MT Modulkombination Akuport Tower Modulkombination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Details Potenzierer D-tec Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Vistron EAV-Diagonose u. Therapie, Informationsübertragung Perfekte Kombination Diagnose, Elektrotherapie Informationsübertragung – überzeugend neuartige Technik präzisen Leuchtbandanzeige* Das Vistron vereint Diagnose- Therapieteil biosymetrischen Funktionstestung Elektroakupunktur Voll modernen flachen Gehäusedesign. Neuartig u. a. mikroprozessor- gesteuerte Lichtbalken, trägheitslos Messendwert, gemessenen Zeigerabfall darstellt. Durch klappbare Displayanzeige Werte optimal einseh- ablesbar. Folientastaturen lassen Gerät übersichtlich unkompliziert bedienen. Die Stromversorgung erfolgt standardmäßig über hochwertiges medizinisches Netzteil, zugelassen EN 60601-1, optional über 12 Volt Akku, einfach auszutauschen ist. [mehr Details] Neben bewährten Einrichtungen Diagnose- Therapieanwendungen, Punktsucher „Opto point“ ergonomisch geformten Messgriffel, finden Sie neuartige EAV-Funktionen, Prozesse täglichen Praxisalltag vereinfachen: Kindling Vistron Diagnose Therapie *Stationärer Betrieb Netzteil, Akkutausch nötig Für portablen Betrieb optionalen Akku lieferbar *Wartungsfreie Leuchtbalkenanzeige *Automatische manuelle Punktmessung wählbar *Speicherung aktuellen Messanzeige nächsten Messung Messton abschalt- regelbar Lautstärke Integrierte herausnehmbare große Testwabe, abschaltbar über Taste Aufsetzbare Zahnelektrode Messgriffel für Zahnherdtestung Alle Messelektroden erweiterten Angebot *Kippschwingungstherapie gleichzeitiger Messanzeige (T+M) *Erweitertes Frequenzspektrum max. 199 Hz *Frequenzschaukel 0-10Hz 10-100 Hz *Individuelle Punkttherapiesteuerung Auch für Nadelstimulation Ohrakupunktur einsetzbar *Retec Übertragungseinheit Überschwingen Substanzen Träger *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung diversen Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc komfortabler Zahnherdtest Direkte Informationsübertragung Eingang z. B. Nosoden, homöopathisch aufbereitete Substanzen, Informationen virtuellen Datenbank (Homopath, Meditest), etc. Ausgang z. B. Medium, Globuli, etc. Patient Kippschwingungstherapie (Tonisieren Sedieren) über Akupunkturpunkte: Festfrequenz (0,1 – 19,9 Hz 10 – 199 Hz) Frequenzschaukel (1,0 – 10,0 Hz 10 – 100 Hz) Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten umfangreiches Sonderzubehör Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest - kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich. Messstreckenumschalter Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden Messleitungen, 2m Punktsonde fester 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Zahntestspitze Retec-Ausgangsbecher XL Retec-Leitung 0,5m Universalwabe Netzgerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 31x5,5(11)x28cm, Gewicht: ca. 2200g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II * Deutschland, Niederlanden: Exklusiv-Vertrieb über MBA GmbH, Limburg Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Vistron EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnose Das ideale Einstiegsgerät modernen bioelektrischen Messverfahren EAV kompakten modularen System Das Kindling Akuport M1+ praxisgerechtes, neuesten Erkenntnissen konstruiertes EAV-Diagnosegerät stellt für Einsteiger erfahrenen Therapeuten kostengünstige Variante dar. Das Akuport M1+ modulares, steckbares System (plug&amp;play) EAV-Therapieteil (MT) und/oder Bioresonanzgerät (MR2) einfach Komplettanlage (Akuport Tower) erweitern. Kindling Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnose *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) übersichtliches Zeigerinstrument *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze optische Punktsucheinrichtung Punktsonde akustische Messdarstellung *Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) Batteriebetrieb übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle * Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung diversen Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das Akuport M1+ Einzelgerät betrieben jederzeit Basisgerät verschiedenen Modulen erweitert werden: Erweiterbar Reizstromtherapiemodul (MT) und/oder Bioresonanzmodul (MR2) einfachen plug&amp;play-System. Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung virtuellen Resonanztests, kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich Messtreckenumschalter Als BFD-Ausführung Silberelektroden Silbermessspitze erhältlich umfangreiches Sonderzubehör Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden Messleitung für Handelektrode (schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Testwabe ø ca. 5 cm Leitung für Testwabe Batterie (9V-Block) Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MT Akuport M1+/MR2 Akuport Tower Modulkombination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Personen Personen Der Erfolg Kindling GmbH Verständnis Einsatz Mitarbeiter für Ziele Unternehmens bestimmt. Unsere qualifizierten Mitarbeiter sichern hohen Standard Produkte verantwortungsvolle Arbeit innerhalb Qualitätsmanagementsystems. Die Geschäftsführung setzt Dipl.-Designerin Bürokauffrau Kerstin Abrams Dipl.-Ingenieur Eduard Abrams. Geschäftsgründer heutiger Consultant Franz Schulz vervollständigt unterstützt Team Erfahrung Entwicklung Qualitätsmanagement. Kerstin Abrams Geschäftsführerin Design Marketing Eduard Abrams Geschäftsführer Entwicklung Produktion Qualitätsmanagement Franz Schulz Consultant Entwicklung Qualitätsmanagement (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M2 Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Akuport M2 Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M2 EAV-Diagnose Das portable Diagnosegerät integrierter Mundstrommessung überzeugt großen Zeigerinstrument Digitalanzeige. Der ideale Begleiter Praxis Unterwegs. Der individuelle Hautabgleich Option Mundstrommessung Akuport M2 ermöglichen Einsteiger erfahrenen Therapeuten optimale messtechnische Voraussetzungen für konfortable EAV. Kindling EAV Akuport M2 Diagnose *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) *großes übersichtliches Zeigerinstrument *Digitale Anzeige Zeigerabfalls *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze *optische Punktsucheinrichtung „OPTO-Point“ 10-stelligem LED-Band Punktsonde individuellem Hautfeuchtigkeitsabgleich große Testwabe unterschiedlichen Lochgrößen akustische Messunterstützung regulierbaren Ton Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) eingebauter Hochleistungsakku für 60 Stunden Betriebszeit Automatik-Ladegerät - Überwachung Ladung notwendig übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Optional: Mundstrommessung Erfassung Fremdpotentialen Mundraum Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest, kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich Messtreckenumschalter Quadrantentestung Hand-, Fuß- Stirnelektrode Messonde für Mundstrommessung umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. Zahnpotentialelektroden Mundstrommessung Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitung für Handelektroden (rot, schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Kugelmessspitze Testwabe ø ca. 10cm Leitung für Testwabe Automatik-Ladegerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 21x9x13cm, Gewicht: ca. 1000g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde Upgrade Combi-2 EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Combi-2 Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Combi-2 EAV-Diagnose Therapie Die Vielseitigkeit Diagnose Therapie Gerät – gehobene Mittelklasse für anspruchsvolle Anwender. Flexibilität zuverlässige Leistung bezeichnend für Combi-2 unverzichtbar für moderne EAV-Praxen. Die vielfältigen Geräteeigenschaften bieten Therapeuten jeglicher Fachrichtung Grundlage für ausgereiftes bioenergetisches Konzept. Das Combi-2 vereint moderne messtechnische Voraussetzungen für sichere Diagnose unterschiedlichen Therapieanwendungen niederfrequente Stromimpulse Regulierung energetischen Laufbahnen Körper. Kindling EAV Combi-2 Diagnose Therapie *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) *großes, abnehmbares Zeigerinstrument individuellen Platzierung Arbeitsplatz Digitalanzeige (LCD) für Zeigerabfall, Frequenz Zahnpotential *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze *optische Punktsucheinrichtung „OPTO-Point“ 10-stelligem LED-Band Punktsonde individuellem Hautfeuchtigkeitsabgleich Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) akustische Messunterstützung regulierbaren Ton *Toneinsatz-Schaltung – regelt Einsatz begleitenden Ton-Signals große integrierte Testwabe moderne Folientastatur eingebauter Hochleistungsakku für 10 Stunden Vollbetrieb - *Optional: Netzbetrieb medizinischem Netzteil Automatik-Ladegerät bzw. medizinisches Netzteil übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle *Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Reizstromtherapie: Festfrequenz (0,1 – 19,9 Hz), Frequenzschaukel (1 – 10,0 Hz), Stromformen: Sedierend, Tonisierend, Kippschwingung Stromformen: Sedierend, Tonisierend, Kippschwingung Zahnpotentialmessung komfortabler Zahnreiztest Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten speziell Retec 2000 aufeinander abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept. Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest - kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich. Messtreckenumschalter umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. Zahnreizsonde Optional: Netzbetrieb medizinischem Netzteil Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitung für Handelektroden (rot, schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Kugelmessspitze Testwabe ø ca. 10cm Gerät integriert Zahnpotentialelektrode Automatik-Ladegerät bzw. medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 21x23x18cm, Gewicht: ca. 1700g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde Combi-2 / Retec 2000C EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron / Akuport D-tec Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Vistron / Akuport D-tec Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Vistron / Akuport D-tec EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Potenzieren Das Akuport D-tec Helfer EAV Gerätes Vistron. Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt elektronische Potenzen, Anwender große Vielfalt komplementär-medizinischen Prozessen ermöglichen. Über Vistron Informationen Trägermedium übertragen. Darüber hinaus stehen Funktionen Vistrons vollen Verfügung. Vistron (Elektroakupunktur Diagnose Therapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzierer) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Bioresonanz Retec 2000 CP – gekoppelt Combi-2 uneingeschränktes Arbeiten EAV Bioresonanz gewährleistet. Combi-2 Retec 2000 CP </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec Kombination Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport D-tec Kombination Potenzieren Integriert harmonisch Akuport-Kombinationen. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Akuport-Module bleiben hierbei erhalten. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es Stromversorgung nötig. Akuport M1+ (Diagnose) Akuport MT (Reizstromtherapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzieren) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonanztherapie) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Bioresonanz Der Akuport Tower vereint EAV Diagnose Therapie Vorzügen Bioresonanz. Einfach, schnell Platz sparend steht Ihnen komplette Systemeinheit Verfügung. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ , Akuport MT Akuport MR2 bleiben hierbei erhalten. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es Stromversorgung nötig. Akuport M1+ (Diagnose) Akuport MT (Reizstromtherapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzieren) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonanztherapie) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MR2 Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV-Diagnose Bioresonanz EAV- Bioresonanztherapie kompakten Systemeinheit. Der Ideale Einstieg modernen Mess- Retec-Therapieverfahren. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ Akuport MR2 bleiben hierbei erhalten. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es Stromversorgung nötig. Akuport M1+ (Diagnose) Akuport MT (Reizstromtherapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzieren) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonanztherapie) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MT Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Modellkombinationen &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec Kombination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ / MT EAV-Diagnose Therapie Abgestimmte Harmonie moderner EAV-Diagnose Therapie. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ Akuport MT bleiben hierbei erhalten. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es Stromversorgung nötig. Akuport M1+ (Diagnose) Akuport MT (Reizstromtherapie) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonanztherapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzieren) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Firmenchronik Firmenchronik 1956 Firmengründung Marie-Luise Kindling Hannover 1956 Nervenpunktdetektor 1 für Punktlokalisation 1959 Nervenpunktdetektor 2 Messanzeige 1966 Nervenpunktdetektor 3 Messanzeige Therapieteil 1972 Nervenpunktdetektor 4 EAV-Gerät Akku-Betrieb 1978 Nervenpunktdetektor 4B Transistorisiertes EAV-Gerät Akku-Betrieb 1980 Übergang Firma Kindling Kindling GmbH Sitz Hildesheim Inhabender Geschäftsführer: Franz Schulz 1980 Akuport M; EAV-Reisegerät 1983 Kindling 2000 Komfort-EAV-Gerät Druckmessanzeige 1985 Computerunterstützte EAV Programmen ELADI (MS-DOS) HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer (ATARI) 1987 Vorstellung EAV-Geräte Dr. Voll 1988 Aufnahme Int. Ärztegesellschaft für EAV Präsident Dr. Fehrenbach 1990 Software ELADI MT Medikamententest 1993 Vorstellung RETEC-Therapie (Bioresonanz) RETEC 2000 1994 EAV-Combi 2 ersetzt Nervenpunktdetektor 4B 1995 ELADI VT Software virtueller Medikamententestung 1996 Software HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer Windows-Version 1996 Computergestützte EAV-System-Diagnostik Kindling 2000, Retec 2000 1997 RETEC 3000 Computergesteuerte, 2 Kanal multiplex, Resonanztherapie 1998 Umzug Gropiusstrasse Erweiterung Produktionsmöglichkeiten 1999 Kooperation Firma MBA GmbH für Vertrieb Service 1999 Erste Zertifizierung ISO-Norm 9000 2000 Akuport Plug-and-Play Modulsystem M1, MT MR 2002 Das EAV-Combi-2 2003 Kindling 2000s überarbeitete Version Design 2003 Curator Lichttherapiegerät Global Scaling Zusammenarbeit I.R.E.F. 2004 Retec 2000c Kompaktgerät neuer Software 2004 USB-Technologie für Software 2005 Zertifizierung Medizinprodukte-Norm EN ISO 13485 2005 Firmenjubiläum 25 Jahre Kindling Hildesheim 2007 Akuport MR2 Nachfolger Akuport MR 2008 Wechsel Geschäftsführung Dipl.-Des. Kerstin Abrams Dipl.-Ing. Eduard Abrams 2008 Canadische Zertifizierung CAN/CSA ISO 13485 2009 Vistron ; Generation EAV 2011 Akuport D-tec ; Potenzierer 2015 Kindling EASY ; Selbstkalibrierendes Bioresonanz-Gerät (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zertifizierung Zertifizierung Zertifizierte Qualität Kindling GmbH gesetzlichen Vorgaben angepasstes, integriertes zertifiziertes Qualitätsmanagementsystem. Wichtig Gerätekauf! Achten Sie Vergleich Angebote Zulassung Herstellers. Diese Medizinprodukt CE Kennzeichen zugehörigen Nummer Überwachungsstelle Gerät versehen sein, z. B unserem Fall CE 0044. Andernfalls handeln Sie Zulassung Gefahr jegliche Produkthaftung! EG-Zertifikat gem. 93/42/EWG Anhang II Zertifikat gem. DIN EN ISO 13485 Zertifikat gem. CAN/CSA ISO 13485 (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Qualitätsmanagment Qualitätsmanagment Die Kindling GmbH 1999 gesetzlichen Vorgaben Strategie ausgerichtetes Qualitätsmanagementsystem aufgebaut, höchsten Qualitätsansprüchen Gebiet Medizintechnik gerecht werden. Das Qualitätsmanagementsystem DIN ISO 13485 TÜV NORD CERT GmbH überwacht zertifiziert. [Zertifizierung] Um Qualität Produkte, Prozesse Service gewährleisten, Arbeit folgenden Grundsätze bestimmt: Unsere Kunden Unsere Kunden stehen für Stelle. Wir müssen gegenwärtige zukünftige Erfordernisse Kunden verstehen, Anforderungen erfüllen streben, Erwartungen übertreffen. Die Erfüllung Kundenansprüche erfordert stets hohes Qualitätsniveau. Ein faires Preis-Leistungsverhältnis Produkte wichtig. Deshalb streben danach, unnötige Kosten vermeiden, vernünftigen Preise Produkte beibehalten können. Aufträge Kunden umgehend zuverlässig ausgeführt werden. Unsere Ziele Die ständige Verbesserung Gesamtleistung, Aufrechterhaltung Wirksamkeit Qualitätsmanagementsystems unseres Unternehmens, stellt permanentes Ziel dar, über Qualität Produkte gewährleisten. Die Kindling GmbH fühlt Qualitätspolitik verpflichtet, Mitarbeiter verantwortungsvollen aktiven Sicherung Qualität Produkte, Prozesse Service innerhalb jeweiligen Arbeitsumgebung aufgerufen. Unsere Mitarbeiter Auf Ebenen Mitarbeiter Wesen unseres Unternehmens aus. Die vollständige Einbeziehung Mitarbeiter ermöglicht, Fähigkeiten fördern Nutzen Unternehmens einzusetzen. Für Mitarbeiter Prinzip Fehlervermeidung Vorrang Fehlerbehebung. Ein systematisches Projektmanagement Einsatz verschiedenen Methoden Techniken Überprüfung garantiert, Produkt vorgegebenen Qualitätsansprüche erfüllt. Die Qualifizierung Validierung Produktionsprozessen stellt sicher, spezifizierte Produktqualität erreicht wird. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Zubehör &gt;&gt; Literaturempfehlungen Zubehör EAV Zubehör Bioresonanz Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Literaturempfehlungen ELEKTROAKUPUNKTUR Einführung Elektroakupunktur Voll Begher, ML-Verlag Begher vermittelt theoretischen Grundlagen handwerkliche Rüstzeug korrekten, sach fachgerechten Handhabung EAV Praxis legt Integration Homöo Isopathie, Anwendung Therapieprinzips potenzierten Arzneimitteln, objektiver einleuchtender Form. Elektroakupunktur Voll Rossmann, (wird leider aufgelegt) Dieses Buch schildert Wissenswerte Elektroakupunktur: Es informiert u. a. über Grundlagen, Diagnose, Akupunktur- Medikamententest, beschreibt Kur- Heilverfahren vermittelt überraschende Einblicke menschliche Energiespektrum. Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band I) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band II) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Die Meßpunkte Elektroakupunktur Voll Händen Füßen Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Zeichnerische Darstellung Messpunkte Voll Händen Füßen Grundlagen Elektroakupunktur Voll Leonhardt, Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Ein Leitfaden Einführung Elektroakupunktur Systematik Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Grauberger Nosoden Therapie Cornelius, Pflaum Verlag Mit Entdeckung Elektroakupunktur Dr. Reinhold Voll (EAV) hierdurch möglichen Medikamententest Bedeutung Nosoden, klassischen Homöopathie Einsatz kamen, deutlich. Peter Cornelius Buch Zusammenstellung verfügbaren Nosoden wissenschaftlicher Akribie erarbeitet. Atlas Elektroakupunktur Ruf, ML-Verlag Dr. med. Ivor Ruf Atlas (218 Seiten) über 1170 Akupunkturpunkte erstmalig Werk geschaffen, Darstellung Beschreibung klassischen Akupunkturpunkte EAV neu gefundenen Messpunkte beschreibt. Die EAV Voll über 500 Punkte erarbeitet. Diese Zusammenfassung insbesondere für klassischen Akupunkteur Interesse, Bedeutung sowohl EAV-Punkte EAV entschlüsselten klassischen Akupunkturpunkte Beziehung Organen Teilabschnitten gezielten Einsatz für Behandlung Krankheiten Patienten ermöglicht, somit schnelleren therapeutischen Erfolg kann. Der inneren Uhr folgen Da Silva, Goldmann Verlag Der inneren Uhr folgen In zweistündiger Folge gleiche Zeit wandert Energie innerhalb Körpers Organsystem anderen. Kim Silva zeigt, Sie Wissen natürlichen Körperrhythmus Bereich optimal nutzen können: Beruf, kreativer Arbeit Lernen Essen Sexualität. Kommentar GebüH König, Volksheilkunde Verlag Dieser Kommentar beinhaltet erstmalig ausführliche Leistungsbeschreibungen entsprechend analogisierten Regularien Erstattungshinweisen. Die Anforderungen fachgerechte Diagnose ausführlich dargestellt. Die Jahren bewährte Erstattungstabelle Autors, exakten Leistungszuschüsse Beihilfen Postbeamtenkrankenkasse B, kopierfähigen Einlagen Patientenaufklärung abweichenden Honorarvereinbarung Buch für Heilpraktiker unentbehrlichen Nachschlagewerk. Hufeland-Leistungsverzeichnis Besonderen Therapierichtungen Hufelandgesellschaft, Haug Verlag Das Hufelandverzeichnis für Ärzte, Versicherte Patienten wertvolle Orientierungshilfe Abrechnung komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren. Es enthält Analog- GOÄ-Ziffern, anwendbar ambulanten Bereich berücksichtigt private Krankenkassen. Die Auswahl Verfahren erfolgte hoher praktischer Relevanz. So liegt Schwerpunkt Methoden, Naturheilkunde, Homöopathie, Akupunktur Anthroposophischen Medizin Anwendung kommen. Neu: - Tabelle Osteopathie Feldenkrais - Tabelle Ergebnissen Erhebung Qualitätssicherung Komplementärmedizin Mykosen Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen- Diagnose Therapie EAV Voll Homöopathie für Zahnärzte Bartak Dr. Jan Bartak bietet Buch homöopathischen Ratgeber, ständiger Begleiter (zahn-) ärztlichen Alltag konzipert ist. Homöopathie ganzheitliche Medizin pas excellence für beste Einstieg ganzheitliche (Zahn-) Heilkunde. Bei praktischen gezieltem Eingehen (zahn-) ärztliche Praxis Leser onzentrierter Form Geschichte ursprünglichen Grundlagen Homöopathie vertraut gemacht. Ergänzend Bartak komplementäre Methoden - speziell Elektroakupunktur Voll-, homöopathischen Verfahren (zahn-) ärztlichen Praxis harmonisch effektiv ergänzen können. Mikrobiologie + Homöopathie Ruf, ML-Verlag Darmparasitose Humanmedizin • Grundlagen • Klinik • Diagnostik • Therapieanmedizin Fonk, ASKE Verlag DARMPARASITOSE IN DER HUMANMEDIZIN – Grundlagen, Klinik, Diagnostik, Therapie: Lehrbuch, Praxis- Fachinformationen kombiniert. Für wen? Für Leser, zeitaufwändiges Literaturstudium schnell sachlich über Vielschichtigkeit Krankheitsbildes „Darmparasitose“ einschließlich therapeutischen Möglichkeiten informieren möchte. Für modernen Homo sapiens, zuvor vielfältigster Weise Gefahr Parasitose aussetzt, wissen ahnen. Zur Unterstützung Therapeuten, bereit ist, klinischen Blick verlassen handeln, Labor pathologischen Befund ist. Für Medizinstudenten Suche Brückenschlag Theorie Praxis. Für Humanmediziner, Repertoire Darmparasitose Regel vorkommt, für Darmparasiten modernen, hygienebewussten, hightech- pharma-orientierten Generation undenkbar somit Thema unseres Gesundheitswesens darstellen. Dieser Auffassung pragmatisches Handikap Vorschub leisten, nämlich modernen sanitären Anlagen, Stuhlkontrolle Patienten, früher unvermeidlich war, unmöglich machen. Last but not least für notwendige Entwicklung verbesserter, aussagefähigerer finanzierbarer Nachweismethoden für Routine-Labor. Rickettsiose - System Hauterkrankungen Fonk, ASKE Verlag Es Borreliose sein! Wussten Sie, Zecken Biss Infektionscocktail übertragen können? Dazu gehören Borrelien FSME-Viren, Rickettsien (Fleckfieber, Q-Fieber, Wolhynisches Fieber, Zeckenbiss-Fieber, Ehrlichien, Bartonellen), Babesien, Tularämie …. Rickettsien weltweit verbreitet Zecken, Milben (z.B. Grasmilben) Insekten. Rickettsiose – Krankheitsbilder: Gehirnhaut-, Herzinnenhaut-, Herzmuskelentzündungen, atypische Pneumonie, Lungenfibrose, Hepatitis, Polyarthritis, Polyradikulitis, Neurodermitis, Lymphome Non-Hodgkin-Lymphom, T-Zell-Lymphom u.a. Malignom. Dass Krankheiten Rickettsiose verbergen kann, differenzialdiagnostischen Überlegungen berücksichtigt. Diagnostik Rickettsiose: Eine Labordiagnose akuten Krankheitsfall möglich. Die Antikörper-Titer entwickeln Wochen, teilweise Monate Infektion. Hinzukommt, antibiotischen Therapie, Regel sofort eingeleitet wird, Antikörper entwickeln können. Die Rickettsiose unbekanntes Krankheitsbild, tatsächlich großer Bedeutung für Gesundheitswesen. Ohne bio-logische Diagnoseverfahren Diagnose Rickettsiose trotz bester, modernster High-Tech-Laborausrüstung akuten Stadium, häufig Spätstadium, gestellt. Das medizinische Paradigma Hanzl, Haug Verlag Brückenschlag Schulmedizin Komplementärmedizin: Dieses Buch beitragen, Kluft Schulmedizin naturheilkundlichen regulationsmedizinischen Verfahren überbrücken. Es klassischen Schulmediziner zeigen, daß Anpassung medizinischen Modelle modernste (natur-)wissenschaftliche Erkenntnisse Kybernetik, Systemtheorie, Quantenphysik Chaosforschung, neues medizinisches Paradigma, bestehende Misere Gebiet chronischer Erkrankungen überwunden kann. Den wissenschaftlichen Fundierung interessierten Vertretern komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren zeigen, daß Großteil Verfahren streng wissenschaftlich begründbar ist. Von Prof. Dr. F.-A. Popp Buch Bibel für komplementärmedizinischen Verfahren bezeichnet. Elektroakupunktur zahnärztl. Praxis Kramer, ML-Verlag Die Elektroakupunktur Krankheiten Ausbruch erkennen, Belastungen Körpers Umweltgifte austesten, Medikamentenrückstände -schäden messen, Allergieneigung testen, Krankheitsherde aufspüren Behandlungserfolge kontrollieren. Für Zahnarzt Elektroakupunktur besonderer Bedeutung, Basis üblichen klinischen Diagnostik zusätzliche Hilfe gibt, soliden odontogenen Herddiagnostik kommen. Kompendium Elektroakupunktur Rossmann, Haug-Verlag Praxisorientierte Einführung Grundlagen systematischen Elektroakupunktur Voll. Das System Grundregulation Pischinger, Haug Verlag Mit Fachbuch liegt Hauptwerk für wissenschaftliche Begründung biologischen Medizin Erklärungsmodell für Vielzahl komplementäerer Heilverfahren vor. Es liefert praxisorientierte, verständliche Einführung komplexe Materie: Das System Grundregulation bildet Pischinger Wechselwirkungen Zelle-Milieu-System ab. Es Gegenstand Entzündungs- Abwehrvorgänge zuständig für Lebensgrundlagenfunktionen. Anhaltende Störungen Grundregulation behindern genetisch programmierte Zellfunktion Krankheitserscheinungen Folge. Das Grundregulationssystem Erklärungsmodell Vielzahl komplementärer Heilverfahren. wendbares Konzept integriert: Humoralpathologie, Organpathologie, Neuralpathologie, Zellular- Permeabilitätspathologie. Wandlungsphasen Max + Moritz Pollmann, Haug Verlag Der Einstieg Denkweise Chinesischen Medizin, Welt Analogien Bildvergleiche, fällt westlich ausgebildeten Arzt leicht. Die grundlegende Lehre "Fünf Wandlungsphasen" "Fünf Elemente" Buch verständlich, einprägsam anschaulich dargestellt. Uns vertraute bekannte Figuren Wilhelm Buschs "Max Moritz", setzt Autor Beziehung Wesensart fünf Elemente. Wer hätte gedacht, daß Lehrer Lämpel, Schneider Böck guten Onkel Fritz Analogien chinesischen Typologie finden ließen? Der Leser findet Buch heitere, treffende Einführung Theorie Chinesischen Medizin konkrete diagnostische therapeutische Hinweise für Akupunkturpraxis, frei Motto: "Aber Weisheit Lehren muß Vergnügen hören." Das hyperaktive Kind Rosival, Ravensburger Nicht Hyperaktivität Hauptproblem "hyperaktiven Kinder", Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, hohe Sensibilität Impulsivität. Solche Kinder immer. Nur fallen Gesellschaft, unserem Schulsystem eher leiden, Eltern Erzieher, darunter, daß steuern können, Umfeld gefordert wird. Dieser Ratgeber erklärt beschreibt Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, Hyperaktivität auftreten kann, veranschaulicht Erscheinungsbild Beispielen Eltern Mut, Leben Kind schwieriger, hoffnungslos ist. Infektionskrankheiten Umweltgifte Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen ganzheitlich betrachtet Häring, Pro-Medicina Verlag Ein modernes Lehrbuch Mykologie Fotos Dokumentationen Praxis. Die häufigsten pathogenen Mykoseerreger eingehend beschrieben. Außerdem gezeigt, mykotische Keime Organismus ausbreiten Krankheitssymptomen führen können. BIORESONANZ Allergien Tiere heilbar Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Biophysikalische Therapie Allergien Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Allergien nehmen weltweit zu. Allergien entwickeln stets variierende maskierte Formen - zuletzt umweltbedingt. Die Belastungen Asthma bronchiale, Heuschnupfen Neurodermitis reduzieren Lebensqualität Patienten dramatisch. Chemische Suppression Hyposensibilisierungsbehandlung zeigen unzureichend Erfolge erhöhten Nebenwirkungen Gefahren. Anhand langjähriger, sorgfältig dokumentierter Erfolge kinderärztlicher Praxis weist Verfasser nach, daß Allergien vollständig nachhaltig heilbar können, biophysikalisches Phänomen erkennt physikalischen Gesetzen behandelt. Auf Basis 'Bioresonanztherapie' bewährten Konzeption vermittelt Buch umfassend systematisch Grundlagen Praxis biophysikalischen 'Löschung' Allergien - Fremdsubstanzen belastende Nebenwirkungen, insbesondere Aspekt Kinderheilkunde. Bioresonanz - Heilen Medikamente Maasz-Daley, Lerch, Haug Verlag Heilen inneren Kraft: Die Bioresonanztherapie - revolutionäre wirksame Heilmethode - Fachkundigund verständlich beschrieben - Zahlreiche Fallbeispiele, Behandlungsmöglichkeiten anschaulicherläutert werden. Endlich Allergien mehr, Schluß quälenden Kopf- Rückenschmerzen. Die erfolgreiche Heilmethode deutschen Arzt Franz Morell entwickelt. Zahlreiche Beispiele Praxis veranschaulichen, Krankheiten Rheuma, Morbus Bechterew, akuten chronischen Schmerzzuständen, Migräne, Allergien, Asthma, Neurodermitis stressbedingten Erkrankungen bewährt hat. Die Bioresonanztherapie bietet Möglichkeit, Medikamente völlig schmerzlos gesund werden. Sie für Kinder geeignet. Neue Lebenskraft Bioresonanz Dr. med. Dörfler, Simondo Gesundheitsservice Erstmals möglich, Belastungen unseres energetischen Systems exakt erfasen. Die Behandlung greift tief Gefüge ermöglicht es, Patienten "rückwärts Sackgasse Krankheit" herauszuführen. Warum kränker? Wie funktioniert Energiesystem? Wie Diagnostik Therapie sich? Welche Mitarbeit Patienten verlangt? Wie Patient weiterhin gesund erhalten? Welche begleitenden Behandlungen hilfreich sinnvoll? </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Literaturempfehlungen ELEKTROAKUPUNKTUR Einführung Elektroakupunktur Voll Begher, ML-Verlag Begher vermittelt theoretischen Grundlagen handwerkliche Rüstzeug korrekten, sach fachgerechten Handhabung EAV Praxis legt Integration Homöo Isopathie, Anwendung Therapieprinzips potenzierten Arzneimitteln, objektiver einleuchtender Form. Elektroakupunktur Voll Rossmann, (wird leider aufgelegt) Dieses Buch schildert Wissenswerte Elektroakupunktur: Es informiert u. a. über Grundlagen, Diagnose, Akupunktur- Medikamententest, beschreibt Kur- Heilverfahren vermittelt überraschende Einblicke menschliche Energiespektrum. Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band I) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band II) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Die Meßpunkte Elektroakupunktur Voll Händen Füßen Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Zeichnerische Darstellung Messpunkte Voll Händen Füßen Grundlagen Elektroakupunktur Voll Leonhardt, Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Ein Leitfaden Einführung Elektroakupunktur Systematik Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Grauberger Nosoden Therapie Cornelius, Pflaum Verlag Mit Entdeckung Elektroakupunktur Dr. Reinhold Voll (EAV) hierdurch möglichen Medikamententest Bedeutung Nosoden, klassischen Homöopathie Einsatz kamen, deutlich. Peter Cornelius Buch Zusammenstellung verfügbaren Nosoden wissenschaftlicher Akribie erarbeitet. Atlas Elektroakupunktur Ruf, ML-Verlag Dr. med. Ivor Ruf Atlas (218 Seiten) über 1170 Akupunkturpunkte erstmalig Werk geschaffen, Darstellung Beschreibung klassischen Akupunkturpunkte EAV neu gefundenen Messpunkte beschreibt. Die EAV Voll über 500 Punkte erarbeitet. Diese Zusammenfassung insbesondere für klassischen Akupunkteur Interesse, Bedeutung sowohl EAV-Punkte EAV entschlüsselten klassischen Akupunkturpunkte Beziehung Organen Teilabschnitten gezielten Einsatz für Behandlung Krankheiten Patienten ermöglicht, somit schnelleren therapeutischen Erfolg kann. Der inneren Uhr folgen Da Silva, Goldmann Verlag Der inneren Uhr folgen In zweistündiger Folge gleiche Zeit wandert Energie innerhalb Körpers Organsystem anderen. Kim Silva zeigt, Sie Wissen natürlichen Körperrhythmus Bereich optimal nutzen können: Beruf, kreativer Arbeit Lernen Essen Sexualität. Kommentar GebüH König, Volksheilkunde Verlag Dieser Kommentar beinhaltet erstmalig ausführliche Leistungsbeschreibungen entsprechend analogisierten Regularien Erstattungshinweisen. Die Anforderungen fachgerechte Diagnose ausführlich dargestellt. Die Jahren bewährte Erstattungstabelle Autors, exakten Leistungszuschüsse Beihilfen Postbeamtenkrankenkasse B, kopierfähigen Einlagen Patientenaufklärung abweichenden Honorarvereinbarung Buch für Heilpraktiker unentbehrlichen Nachschlagewerk. Hufeland-Leistungsverzeichnis Besonderen Therapierichtungen Hufelandgesellschaft, Haug Verlag Das Hufelandverzeichnis für Ärzte, Versicherte Patienten wertvolle Orientierungshilfe Abrechnung komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren. Es enthält Analog- GOÄ-Ziffern, anwendbar ambulanten Bereich berücksichtigt private Krankenkassen. Die Auswahl Verfahren erfolgte hoher praktischer Relevanz. So liegt Schwerpunkt Methoden, Naturheilkunde, Homöopathie, Akupunktur Anthroposophischen Medizin Anwendung kommen. Neu: - Tabelle Osteopathie Feldenkrais - Tabelle Ergebnissen Erhebung Qualitätssicherung Komplementärmedizin Mykosen Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen- Diagnose Therapie EAV Voll Homöopathie für Zahnärzte Bartak Dr. Jan Bartak bietet Buch homöopathischen Ratgeber, ständiger Begleiter (zahn-) ärztlichen Alltag konzipert ist. Homöopathie ganzheitliche Medizin pas excellence für beste Einstieg ganzheitliche (Zahn-) Heilkunde. Bei praktischen gezieltem Eingehen (zahn-) ärztliche Praxis Leser onzentrierter Form Geschichte ursprünglichen Grundlagen Homöopathie vertraut gemacht. Ergänzend Bartak komplementäre Methoden - speziell Elektroakupunktur Voll-, homöopathischen Verfahren (zahn-) ärztlichen Praxis harmonisch effektiv ergänzen können. Mikrobiologie + Homöopathie Ruf, ML-Verlag Darmparasitose Humanmedizin • Grundlagen • Klinik • Diagnostik • Therapieanmedizin Fonk, ASKE Verlag DARMPARASITOSE IN DER HUMANMEDIZIN – Grundlagen, Klinik, Diagnostik, Therapie: Lehrbuch, Praxis- Fachinformationen kombiniert. Für wen? Für Leser, zeitaufwändiges Literaturstudium schnell sachlich über Vielschichtigkeit Krankheitsbildes „Darmparasitose“ einschließlich therapeutischen Möglichkeiten informieren möchte. Für modernen Homo sapiens, zuvor vielfältigster Weise Gefahr Parasitose aussetzt, wissen ahnen. Zur Unterstützung Therapeuten, bereit ist, klinischen Blick verlassen handeln, Labor pathologischen Befund ist. Für Medizinstudenten Suche Brückenschlag Theorie Praxis. Für Humanmediziner, Repertoire Darmparasitose Regel vorkommt, für Darmparasiten modernen, hygienebewussten, hightech- pharma-orientierten Generation undenkbar somit Thema unseres Gesundheitswesens darstellen. Dieser Auffassung pragmatisches Handikap Vorschub leisten, nämlich modernen sanitären Anlagen, Stuhlkontrolle Patienten, früher unvermeidlich war, unmöglich machen. Last but not least für notwendige Entwicklung verbesserter, aussagefähigerer finanzierbarer Nachweismethoden für Routine-Labor. Rickettsiose - System Hauterkrankungen Fonk, ASKE Verlag Es Borreliose sein! Wussten Sie, Zecken Biss Infektionscocktail übertragen können? Dazu gehören Borrelien FSME-Viren, Rickettsien (Fleckfieber, Q-Fieber, Wolhynisches Fieber, Zeckenbiss-Fieber, Ehrlichien, Bartonellen), Babesien, Tularämie …. Rickettsien weltweit verbreitet Zecken, Milben (z.B. Grasmilben) Insekten. Rickettsiose – Krankheitsbilder: Gehirnhaut-, Herzinnenhaut-, Herzmuskelentzündungen, atypische Pneumonie, Lungenfibrose, Hepatitis, Polyarthritis, Polyradikulitis, Neurodermitis, Lymphome Non-Hodgkin-Lymphom, T-Zell-Lymphom u.a. Malignom. Dass Krankheiten Rickettsiose verbergen kann, differenzialdiagnostischen Überlegungen berücksichtigt. Diagnostik Rickettsiose: Eine Labordiagnose akuten Krankheitsfall möglich. Die Antikörper-Titer entwickeln Wochen, teilweise Monate Infektion. Hinzukommt, antibiotischen Therapie, Regel sofort eingeleitet wird, Antikörper entwickeln können. Die Rickettsiose unbekanntes Krankheitsbild, tatsächlich großer Bedeutung für Gesundheitswesen. Ohne bio-logische Diagnoseverfahren Diagnose Rickettsiose trotz bester, modernster High-Tech-Laborausrüstung akuten Stadium, häufig Spätstadium, gestellt. Das medizinische Paradigma Hanzl, Haug Verlag Brückenschlag Schulmedizin Komplementärmedizin: Dieses Buch beitragen, Kluft Schulmedizin naturheilkundlichen regulationsmedizinischen Verfahren überbrücken. Es klassischen Schulmediziner zeigen, daß Anpassung medizinischen Modelle modernste (natur-)wissenschaftliche Erkenntnisse Kybernetik, Systemtheorie, Quantenphysik Chaosforschung, neues medizinisches Paradigma, bestehende Misere Gebiet chronischer Erkrankungen überwunden kann. Den wissenschaftlichen Fundierung interessierten Vertretern komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren zeigen, daß Großteil Verfahren streng wissenschaftlich begründbar ist. Von Prof. Dr. F.-A. Popp Buch Bibel für komplementärmedizinischen Verfahren bezeichnet. Elektroakupunktur zahnärztl. Praxis Kramer, ML-Verlag Die Elektroakupunktur Krankheiten Ausbruch erkennen, Belastungen Körpers Umweltgifte austesten, Medikamentenrückstände -schäden messen, Allergieneigung testen, Krankheitsherde aufspüren Behandlungserfolge kontrollieren. Für Zahnarzt Elektroakupunktur besonderer Bedeutung, Basis üblichen klinischen Diagnostik zusätzliche Hilfe gibt, soliden odontogenen Herddiagnostik kommen. Kompendium Elektroakupunktur Rossmann, Haug-Verlag Praxisorientierte Einführung Grundlagen systematischen Elektroakupunktur Voll. Das System Grundregulation Pischinger, Haug Verlag Mit Fachbuch liegt Hauptwerk für wissenschaftliche Begründung biologischen Medizin Erklärungsmodell für Vielzahl komplementäerer Heilverfahren vor. Es liefert praxisorientierte, verständliche Einführung komplexe Materie: Das System Grundregulation bildet Pischinger Wechselwirkungen Zelle-Milieu-System ab. Es Gegenstand Entzündungs- Abwehrvorgänge zuständig für Lebensgrundlagenfunktionen. Anhaltende Störungen Grundregulation behindern genetisch programmierte Zellfunktion Krankheitserscheinungen Folge. Das Grundregulationssystem Erklärungsmodell Vielzahl komplementärer Heilverfahren. wendbares Konzept integriert: Humoralpathologie, Organpathologie, Neuralpathologie, Zellular- Permeabilitätspathologie. Wandlungsphasen Max + Moritz Pollmann, Haug Verlag Der Einstieg Denkweise Chinesischen Medizin, Welt Analogien Bildvergleiche, fällt westlich ausgebildeten Arzt leicht. Die grundlegende Lehre "Fünf Wandlungsphasen" "Fünf Elemente" Buch verständlich, einprägsam anschaulich dargestellt. Uns vertraute bekannte Figuren Wilhelm Buschs "Max Moritz", setzt Autor Beziehung Wesensart fünf Elemente. Wer hätte gedacht, daß Lehrer Lämpel, Schneider Böck guten Onkel Fritz Analogien chinesischen Typologie finden ließen? Der Leser findet Buch heitere, treffende Einführung Theorie Chinesischen Medizin konkrete diagnostische therapeutische Hinweise für Akupunkturpraxis, frei Motto: "Aber Weisheit Lehren muß Vergnügen hören." Das hyperaktive Kind Rosival, Ravensburger Nicht Hyperaktivität Hauptproblem "hyperaktiven Kinder", Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, hohe Sensibilität Impulsivität. Solche Kinder immer. Nur fallen Gesellschaft, unserem Schulsystem eher leiden, Eltern Erzieher, darunter, daß steuern können, Umfeld gefordert wird. Dieser Ratgeber erklärt beschreibt Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, Hyperaktivität auftreten kann, veranschaulicht Erscheinungsbild Beispielen Eltern Mut, Leben Kind schwieriger, hoffnungslos ist. Infektionskrankheiten Umweltgifte Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen ganzheitlich betrachtet Häring, Pro-Medicina Verlag Ein modernes Lehrbuch Mykologie Fotos Dokumentationen Praxis. Die häufigsten pathogenen Mykoseerreger eingehend beschrieben. Außerdem gezeigt, mykotische Keime Organismus ausbreiten Krankheitssymptomen führen können. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MT Akuport MT EAV-Therapie Modulares Therapieteil für Elektroakupunktur Voll Das Kindling Akuport MT perfektioniert EAV-Diagnose sofortige Therapieanwendung niederfrequenten Stromimpulsen. Gleich- wechselgerichtete Kippschwingungen regulieren stabilisieren energetischen Laufbahnen Körper. Hierzu stehen 6 wichtigsten, spezifischen Frequenzen 1/10 hz genau Verfügung. Die Applikation erfolgt über Flächenelektroden gezielt über Punktsonde Akuport M1+. Durch einfaches Aufsetzen (plug&amp;play) Akuport MT EAV-Messgerät Akuport M1+ kombiniert sofort einsatzbereit. Kindling EAV Akuport MT Therapie Niederfrequenztherapieanwendungen *6 ausgewählte, spezifische Frequenzen (1.7 Hz, 2.4 Hz, 4 Hz, 6 Hz, 9.4 Hz, 10 Hz) 3 Impulsformen Tonisieren Sedieren Intensitätsregler, stufenlos Leistungsstarker Therapieausgang *Gedämpfter Ausgang Nadelstimulation *Direkte Applikation über Punktsonde Akuport M1+ leistungsstarke Akkus für 8 Stunden Vollbetrieb eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling ! Anwendungen Therapieanwendung niederfrequenten Stromimpulsen Standards EAV Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar EAV-Diagnosemodul Akuport M1+ Bioresonanzmodul (MR2) plug&amp;play-System Erweiterbar Kindling EAV-Modellen Sonderzubehör z. B. für Nadelstimulation Zahnreizmessung Lieferumfang Stand-Alone: 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitungen für Handelektrode (schwarz rot) 2 wiederaufladbare 9V-Block-Batterien Ladegerät Betriebsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Als Modulergänzung M1+: Messleitung für Handelektrode (rot) 2 wiederaufladbare 9V-Block-Batterien Automatik-Ladegerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron Vistron EAV-Diagonose u. Therapie, Informationsübertragung Perfekte Kombination Diagnose, Elektrotherapie Informationsübertragung – überzeugend neuartige Technik präzisen Leuchtbandanzeige* Das Vistron vereint Diagnose- Therapieteil biosymetrischen Funktionstestung Elektroakupunktur Voll modernen flachen Gehäusedesign. Neuartig u. a. mikroprozessor- gesteuerte Lichtbalken, trägheitslos Messendwert, gemessenen Zeigerabfall darstellt. Durch klappbare Displayanzeige Werte optimal einseh- ablesbar. Folientastaturen lassen Gerät übersichtlich unkompliziert bedienen. Die Stromversorgung erfolgt standardmäßig über hochwertiges medizinisches Netzteil, zugelassen EN 60601-1, optional über 12 Volt Akku, einfach auszutauschen ist. [mehr Details] Neben bewährten Einrichtungen Diagnose- Therapieanwendungen, Punktsucher „Opto point“ ergonomisch geformten Messgriffel, finden Sie neuartige EAV-Funktionen, Prozesse täglichen Praxisalltag vereinfachen: Kindling Vistron Diagnose Therapie *Stationärer Betrieb Netzteil, Akkutausch nötig Für portablen Betrieb optionalen Akku lieferbar *Wartungsfreie Leuchtbalkenanzeige *Automatische manuelle Punktmessung wählbar *Speicherung aktuellen Messanzeige nächsten Messung Messton abschalt- regelbar Lautstärke Integrierte herausnehmbare große Testwabe, abschaltbar über Taste Aufsetzbare Zahnelektrode Messgriffel für Zahnherdtestung Alle Messelektroden erweiterten Angebot *Kippschwingungstherapie gleichzeitiger Messanzeige (T+M) *Erweitertes Frequenzspektrum max. 199 Hz *Frequenzschaukel 0-10Hz 10-100 Hz *Individuelle Punkttherapiesteuerung Auch für Nadelstimulation Ohrakupunktur einsetzbar *Retec Übertragungseinheit Überschwingen Substanzen Träger *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung diversen Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc komfortabler Zahnherdtest Direkte Informationsübertragung Eingang z. B. Nosoden, homöopathisch aufbereitete Substanzen, Informationen virtuellen Datenbank (Homopath, Meditest), etc. Ausgang z. B. Medium, Globuli, etc. Patient Kippschwingungstherapie (Tonisieren Sedieren) über Akupunkturpunkte: Festfrequenz (0,1 – 19,9 Hz 10 – 199 Hz) Frequenzschaukel (1,0 – 10,0 Hz 10 – 100 Hz) Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten umfangreiches Sonderzubehör Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest - kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich. Messstreckenumschalter Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden Messleitungen, 2m Punktsonde fester 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Zahntestspitze Retec-Ausgangsbecher XL Retec-Leitung 0,5m Universalwabe Netzgerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 31x5,5(11)x28cm, Gewicht: ca. 2200g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II * Deutschland, Niederlanden: Exklusiv-Vertrieb über MBA GmbH, Limburg (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnose Das ideale Einstiegsgerät modernen bioelektrischen Messverfahren EAV kompakten modularen System Das Kindling Akuport M1+ praxisgerechtes, neuesten Erkenntnissen konstruiertes EAV-Diagnosegerät stellt für Einsteiger erfahrenen Therapeuten kostengünstige Variante dar. Das Akuport M1+ modulares, steckbares System (plug&amp;play) EAV-Therapieteil (MT) und/oder Bioresonanzgerät (MR2) einfach Komplettanlage (Akuport Tower) erweitern. Kindling Akuport M1+ EAV-Diagnose *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) übersichtliches Zeigerinstrument *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze optische Punktsucheinrichtung Punktsonde akustische Messdarstellung *Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) Batteriebetrieb übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *eingebaute Modulschnittstelle für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle * Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung diversen Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das Akuport M1+ Einzelgerät betrieben jederzeit Basisgerät verschiedenen Modulen erweitert werden: Erweiterbar Reizstromtherapiemodul (MT) und/oder Bioresonanzmodul (MR2) einfachen plug&amp;play-System. Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung virtuellen Resonanztests, kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich Messtreckenumschalter Als BFD-Ausführung Silberelektroden Silbermessspitze erhältlich umfangreiches Sonderzubehör Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden Messleitung für Handelektrode (schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Testwabe ø ca. 5 cm Leitung für Testwabe Batterie (9V-Block) Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxHxT): 16x11x15cm, Gewicht ca. 400g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Vistron &gt;&gt; Potenzierer D-tec Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Details Potenzierer D-tec Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Potenzierer Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen – kombinierbar Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP EAV Gerät Vistron . Bei bioenergetischen Testverfahren Potenzreihen Anwendung. Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt elektronische Potenzen, Anwender große Vielfalt komplementär-medizinischen Prozessen ermöglichen. Das Akuport D-tec arbeitet Kombination Geräten für bioenergetische Messverfahren - Stand-alone Version Vistron Retec 2000CP einfachen plug&amp;play-System Akuport MR2. Kindling Akuport D-tec *Potenzstufen: D3, D4, D6, D8, D10, D12, D15, D30, D60, D100, D200 Ausgang Übertragung elektronischen Potenz Trägermedium Potenzierungskontrolle LED-Anzeige *Netzbetrieb über medizinisches Netzteil *Modulares System für einfache Erweiterung plug&amp;play-System *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Erarbeitung individueller Potenzen Kombination bioenergetischen Messverfahren (EAV, BFD, usw.) Erstellung Auto-Nosoden (z.B. Sekrete, Exkrete) Feststellung Unverträglichkeiten Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Das plug&amp;play-System ermöglicht zusätzliches Ergänzen Diagnosegerätes Akuport M1+ Reizstromtherapiemodul Akuport MT kompletten Thereapieeinheit. Sonderzubehör z. B. abgeschirmte Ausgangsbecher Lieferumfang Maße (BxHxT): 16x6x15cm, Gewicht ca. 200g Akuport D-tec stand alone Version Retec 2000CP, Vistron Fremdgeräten Akuport D-tec Netzteil (für MPG-Geräte zugelassen) Verbindungsleitungen Kunststoffabdeckkappe Gehäusedesign Bedienungsanleitung Vistron </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M2 Akuport M2 EAV-Diagnose Das portable Diagnosegerät integrierter Mundstrommessung überzeugt großen Zeigerinstrument Digitalanzeige. Der ideale Begleiter Praxis Unterwegs. Der individuelle Hautabgleich Option Mundstrommessung Akuport M2 ermöglichen Einsteiger erfahrenen Therapeuten optimale messtechnische Voraussetzungen für konfortable EAV. Kindling EAV Akuport M2 Diagnose *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) *großes übersichtliches Zeigerinstrument *Digitale Anzeige Zeigerabfalls *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze *optische Punktsucheinrichtung „OPTO-Point“ 10-stelligem LED-Band Punktsonde individuellem Hautfeuchtigkeitsabgleich große Testwabe unterschiedlichen Lochgrößen akustische Messunterstützung regulierbaren Ton Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) eingebauter Hochleistungsakku für 60 Stunden Betriebszeit Automatik-Ladegerät - Überwachung Ladung notwendig übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle *Kindling Special ! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Optional: Mundstrommessung Erfassung Fremdpotentialen Mundraum Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest, kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich Messtreckenumschalter Quadrantentestung Hand-, Fuß- Stirnelektrode Messonde für Mundstrommessung umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. Zahnpotentialelektroden Mundstrommessung Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitung für Handelektroden (rot, schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Kugelmessspitze Testwabe ø ca. 10cm Leitung für Testwabe Automatik-Ladegerät Bedienungsanleitung inkl. Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 21x9x13cm, Gewicht: ca. 1000g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 Combi-2 EAV-Diagnose Therapie Die Vielseitigkeit Diagnose Therapie Gerät – gehobene Mittelklasse für anspruchsvolle Anwender. Flexibilität zuverlässige Leistung bezeichnend für Combi-2 unverzichtbar für moderne EAV-Praxen. Die vielfältigen Geräteeigenschaften bieten Therapeuten jeglicher Fachrichtung Grundlage für ausgereiftes bioenergetisches Konzept. Das Combi-2 vereint moderne messtechnische Voraussetzungen für sichere Diagnose unterschiedlichen Therapieanwendungen niederfrequente Stromimpulse Regulierung energetischen Laufbahnen Körper. Kindling EAV Combi-2 Diagnose Therapie *EAV-Messsystem offiziellen Standards IMGEAV (Internationale Medizinische Gesellschaft für Elektroakupunktur Voll) *großes, abnehmbares Zeigerinstrument individuellen Platzierung Arbeitsplatz Digitalanzeige (LCD) für Zeigerabfall, Frequenz Zahnpotential *Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde gefederter, druckkompensierter austauschbarer Messspitze *optische Punktsucheinrichtung „OPTO-Point“ 10-stelligem LED-Band Punktsonde individuellem Hautfeuchtigkeitsabgleich Spreizung Skala (TP-Regler) akustische Messunterstützung regulierbaren Ton *Toneinsatz-Schaltung – regelt Einsatz begleitenden Ton-Signals große integrierte Testwabe moderne Folientastatur eingebauter Hochleistungsakku für 10 Stunden Vollbetrieb - *Optional: Netzbetrieb medizinischem Netzteil Automatik-Ladegerät bzw. medizinisches Netzteil übersichtliche Betriebsanzeigen *PC-Anschluss für Arbeiten Meditest- Homopath-Software über USB-Schnittstelle *Kindling Special! Diese Features finden Sie Preissegment Kindling! Anwendungen Diagnostische Messungen Auswertungen Standards EAV Testung Produkten, Unverträglichkeiten, Standortbelastungen, Werkstoffen, etc. Reizstromtherapie: Festfrequenz (0,1 – 19,9 Hz), Frequenzschaukel (1 – 10,0 Hz), Stromformen: Sedierend, Tonisierend, Kippschwingung Stromformen: Sedierend, Tonisierend, Kippschwingung Zahnpotentialmessung komfortabler Zahnreiztest Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Erweiterbar Kindling-Bioresonanzgeräten speziell Retec 2000 aufeinander abgestimmtes Gehäusekonzept. Kombinierbar EAV-Software Homopath Meditest-Softwareprogramm Messdatenerfassung inkl. virtuellen Resonanztest - kostengünstige Einsteiger- Expertenversion erhältlich. Messtreckenumschalter umfangreiches Sonderzubehör z. B. Zahnreizsonde Optional: Netzbetrieb medizinischem Netzteil Lieferumfang 2 Messing-Handelektroden 2 Messleitung für Handelektroden (rot, schwarz) Punktsonde 4-Schlitz-Messspitze Kugelmessspitze Testwabe ø ca. 10cm Gerät integriert Zahnpotentialelektrode Automatik-Ladegerät bzw. medizinisches Netzteil Bedienungsanleitung Gerätebuch Maße (BxTxH)= 21x23x18cm, Gewicht: ca. 1700g Zugelassenes Medizinprodukt EN Richtlinie 93/42/EWG Anhang II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron / Akuport D-tec Vistron / Akuport D-tec EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Potenzieren Das Akuport D-tec Helfer EAV Gerätes Vistron. Das Akuport D-tec erzeugt elektronische Potenzen, Anwender große Vielfalt komplementär-medizinischen Prozessen ermöglichen. Über Vistron Informationen Trägermedium übertragen. Darüber hinaus stehen Funktionen Vistrons vollen Verfügung. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Bioresonanz Retec 2000 CP – gekoppelt Combi-2 uneingeschränktes Arbeiten EAV Bioresonanz gewährleistet. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport D-tec Kombination Potenzieren Integriert harmonisch Akuport-Kombinationen. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Akuport-Module bleiben hierbei erhalten. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 EAV-Diagnose, Therapie Bioresonanz Der Akuport Tower vereint EAV Diagnose Therapie Vorzügen Bioresonanz. Einfach, schnell Platz sparend steht Ihnen komplette Systemeinheit Verfügung. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ , Akuport MT Akuport MR2 bleiben hierbei erhalten. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV-Diagnose Bioresonanz EAV- Bioresonanztherapie kompakten Systemeinheit. Der Ideale Einstieg modernen Mess- Retec-Therapieverfahren. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ Akuport MR2 bleiben hierbei erhalten. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MT EAV-Diagnose Therapie Abgestimmte Harmonie moderner EAV-Diagnose Therapie. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Module Akuport M1+ Akuport MT bleiben hierbei erhalten. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Details Vistron Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Elektroakupunktur &gt;&gt; Vistron &gt;&gt; Details Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Vistron Details Potenzierer D-tec Akuport MT Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Details Vistron Das Vistron Elektroakupunkturgerät Diagnose- Therapieteil biosymetrischen Funktionstestung Elektroakupunktur Voll. Durch laptopähnliche Gehäuseform Vistron bequem transportiert klappbare Displayanzeige ermöglicht optimale Positionierung Arbeitsplatz. Der Betrieb erfolgt standardmäßig über medizinisches Netzteil, zugelassen EN 60601-1, optional über 12 Volt Akku. Zum Laden Akkus ebenfalls med. Netzteil genutzt. Die Messungen Akupunkturpunkte analog großen Lichtbandanzeige Balken Dot (stromsparend) dargestellt. Die Messskala 0-100 Teilstriche eingeteilt, wobei Normwertbereiche für Punkte 50-70, für Handmessungen 80-90 liegen entsprechend gekennzeichnet sind. Die Messung über Automatik, Höchstwert Zeigerabfall anzeigt, manuell durchgeführt werden. Eine integrierte abschaltbare bzw. herausnehmbare Messwabe ermöglicht Resonanztest. Die Lokalisation Akupunkturpunkte erfolgt LED-Leuchtband Messsonde mittels Differenzmessung vorher gespeicherten Haut-Nullwert. Von 9-stelligen LED-Band 6 LEDs gelb, restlichen grün ausgelegt. Je Höhe Anzeige bewegt Punkt (gelber Bereich), grünen Bereich exakt lokalisiert. Analog Anzeige ertönt akustisches Signal, wobei Tonhöhe Messwert variiert. Die Messspitzen Punktsonde auswechselbar. Mit Taste Punktsonde bequem Diagnose Therapie umgeschaltet werden. Als Therapieformen stehen Impulsarten Verfügung: 1. Wechselgerichtete Kippschwingung 2. Positive Kippschwingung 3. Negative Kippschwingung Die Therapiespannung niedrigen Betriebsspannung Hochtransformieren gewonnen. Mit Regler gewünschte Amplitudenhöhe eingestellt werden. Die sicherheitstechnische Trennung Lichtnetz erfolgt medizinische Netzteil ISO DIN 60601-1. Als Option alternativ Betrieb über wiederaufladbare Batterie möglich. Im Bedienteil Bedientaster für Diagnose (links blau) Therapie (rechts gelb) angeordnet. Dazwischen befindet Intensitätsregler Therapie. Die Ein- Ausschaltung erfolgt über grünen Taster unten rechts. Eine automatische Abschaltung Vistron erfolgt Nichtbenutzung 20 Minuten. Im modernen Display, optimal Betrachtungswinkel einzustellen ist, Betriebszustände Symbolen angezeigt: Betriebsfunktionen weiß veränderbare Funktionen gelb. Der Batteriezustand 6-stelligen Leuchtband, Ladekapazität, angezeigt. Für Intensitätsanzeige steht 10-stelliges Leuchtband Verfügung. An Rückseite befinden Anschlüsse für Zubehör. Dieses Punktsonde, Handelektroden externe Testwaben. Weiter Buchse für A/D-Wandler (Computeranschluss), Lautstärkeregler Power-Versorgungsbuchse vorhanden. Die integrierte Überschwingerfunktion dient Verstärker für homöopathische Testsubstanzen. Zeit Verstärkung fest vorgegeben. [ zurück Vistron-Hauptseite] Ergonomisch geformte Punktsonde Potenzierer Akuport D-tec Vistron EG-Konformitätserklärung </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör Bioresonanz Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Zubehör &gt;&gt; Zubehör Bioresonanz Zubehör EAV Zubehör Bioresonanz Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Zubehör Bioresonanz Sollten Sie gewünschtes Produkt finden, kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter. Akuport D-tec Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen. Kombinierbar EAV Gerät Vistron Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP. Elektroden Tiefensonden Eingangs- Ausgangsbecher Ampullen(halter)-Einsatz für Messbecher Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 4cm Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 5 cm Fußplatten einseitig beschichtet Magnetfolie, 1 Paar, ca. 25 12 cm Stirnelektrode Klammerelektrode Farbe (rot, gelb, schwarz, grün) Salbenstab / Individualisierungsstab Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde, klein Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde, groß Zahnfleischrolle Gesicht- Faltenrolle Leitungen Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 2m, 1 Paar Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 0,5m, 1 Paar Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 0,5m Farbe (rot, schwarz) Leerröhrchen Flaschen Tropfflasche, 10ml Tropfflasche, 30ml Globoliflasche, 10ml Ampullen, Ø 10mm Ampullen Rollrand, Ø 10mm Ampullen Korkverschluss Ø 15mm Ampullenschachteln Pappe für 90 Ampullen Netzteile Ladegeräte Auskünfte Netzteilen Ladegeräten können Grund speziellen Abstimmung einzelnen Geräten Anfrage Angabe Gerätenummer erteilt werden. Kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter! Sonstiges Magnetfeld-Retec-Matte, ca. 32 42cm Resonanzplättchen, 50Stk Resonanzplättchen, 50Stk, Kompass Erdungsband, 1,5m Stativ für Tiefensonde Becherglas, 50ml Petrischale Petrieschale Deckel Unarzneiliche Globoli, 1000g Größe 3 Si-Adapter, Farbe ** Alle Abbildungen möglichst großem Format abgebildet. Die Größenverhältnisse abgebildeten Gegenstände untereinander entsprechen demnach realistischen Größenverhältnissen. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Home Über Protonenresonanz Elektroakupunktur Bioresonanz Modellkombinationen Zubehör Software Vertrieb Service Sie hier: &gt;&gt; Zubehör &gt;&gt; Zubehör EAV Zubehör EAV Zubehör Bioresonanz Literaturempfehlungen | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Sollten Sie gewünschtes Produkt finden, kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter. Akuport D-tec Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen. Kombinierbar EAV Gerät Vistron Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP. Q-switch Umschalter für Sektorenmessung für 7 Messstrecken, wahlweise manuell automatisch steuerbar. Kombinierbar Kindling-EAV-Geräten. Elektroden Handelektroden, Messing, 1 Paar Handelektrode, Silber Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 4cm Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 5 cm Fußelektroden, Messing, 1 Paar Stirnelektrode Rollelektrode Duo-Rollelektrode Gummielektroden, 1 Paar, ca. 14 7 cm Gesicht- Faltenrolle Zahnfleischrolle Zahnelektrode Zahnelektroden, 1 Paar Leitung Waben Ampullenabgreifer Medikamenten-Testwabe, 6-Loch, Ø 5cm Medikamenten-Testwabe, 16-Loch, Ø 10cm Verbindungsstecker für Testwaben Abtastgabel für Einzelampullen Abtastplatte für 10 Ampullen Punktsonden Punktsonde für M1+ Punktsonde für M2 Punktsonde für Combi-2 Punktsonde für Vistron Punktsonde für K2000 Messspitzen 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Messing 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Messing für Vistron Kugel-Spitze, Messing Niederdruckmessspitze, Messing 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Silber Kugel-Spitze, Silber Niederdruckmessspitze, Silber Leitungen Messleitung, 2m Stecker: Si – Si, pro Farbe (schwarz, rot, grün, gelb) Messleitung, 2m Stecker: Si - DoppelSi schwarz Messleitung/Wabenleitung, 0,5m Stecker: DoppelSi - DoppelSi schwarz Messleitung/Wabenleitung, 0,5m Stecker: Si - Si schwarz Stimulationsleitung, 1 Paar Si-Stecker rot schwarz Stimulationsleitung Klinkenstecker für Akuport MT USB-Leitung, 2m Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: Klinke - Klinke Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: 6-pol.Din – Klinke Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: 6-pol.Din – 6-pol.Din Verbindungsleitung, 2,5m Stecker: Klinke - Chinch Verbindungsleitung, 2,5m Stecker: Klinke - DoppelSi Netzteile Ladegeräte Auskünfte Netzteilen Ladegeräten können Grund speziellen Abstimmung einzelnen Geräten Anfrage Angabe Gerätenummer erteilt werden. Kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter! Sonstiges Si-Adapter für Elektroden Waben Farbe (rot, schwarz) Messstreckenumschalter/Quadrantenumschalter Erdungsband, 1,5m ** Alle Abbildungen möglichst großer Qualität abgebildet. Die Größenverhältnisse abgebildeten Gegenstände untereinander entsprechen demnach realistischen Größenverhältnissen. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literaturempfehlungen Literaturempfehlungen ELEKTROAKUPUNKTUR Einführung Elektroakupunktur Voll Begher, ML-Verlag Begher vermittelt theoretischen Grundlagen handwerkliche Rüstzeug korrekten, sach fachgerechten Handhabung EAV Praxis legt Integration Homöo Isopathie, Anwendung Therapieprinzips potenzierten Arzneimitteln, objektiver einleuchtender Form. Elektroakupunktur Voll Rossmann, (wird leider aufgelegt) Dieses Buch schildert Wissenswerte Elektroakupunktur: Es informiert u. a. über Grundlagen, Diagnose, Akupunktur- Medikamententest, beschreibt Kur- Heilverfahren vermittelt überraschende Einblicke menschliche Energiespektrum. Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band I) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Regulationsmedizin Theorie Praxis (Band II) Dr. Leiner Kollegen, ML-Verlag Ein wertvolles Ausbildungs- Nachschlagewerk für Ärzte, Zahnärzte Therapeuten Richtungen Die Meßpunkte Elektroakupunktur Voll Händen Füßen Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Zeichnerische Darstellung Messpunkte Voll Händen Füßen Grundlagen Elektroakupunktur Voll Leonhardt, Dr. Voll, ML-Verlag Ein Leitfaden Einführung Elektroakupunktur Systematik Elektroakupunktur Dr. Voll Grauberger Nosoden Therapie Cornelius, Pflaum Verlag Mit Entdeckung Elektroakupunktur Dr. Reinhold Voll (EAV) hierdurch möglichen Medikamententest Bedeutung Nosoden, klassischen Homöopathie Einsatz kamen, deutlich. Peter Cornelius Buch Zusammenstellung verfügbaren Nosoden wissenschaftlicher Akribie erarbeitet. Atlas Elektroakupunktur Ruf, ML-Verlag Dr. med. Ivor Ruf Atlas (218 Seiten) über 1170 Akupunkturpunkte erstmalig Werk geschaffen, Darstellung Beschreibung klassischen Akupunkturpunkte EAV neu gefundenen Messpunkte beschreibt. Die EAV Voll über 500 Punkte erarbeitet. Diese Zusammenfassung insbesondere für klassischen Akupunkteur Interesse, Bedeutung sowohl EAV-Punkte EAV entschlüsselten klassischen Akupunkturpunkte Beziehung Organen Teilabschnitten gezielten Einsatz für Behandlung Krankheiten Patienten ermöglicht, somit schnelleren therapeutischen Erfolg kann. Der inneren Uhr folgen Da Silva, Goldmann Verlag Der inneren Uhr folgen In zweistündiger Folge gleiche Zeit wandert Energie innerhalb Körpers Organsystem anderen. Kim Silva zeigt, Sie Wissen natürlichen Körperrhythmus Bereich optimal nutzen können: Beruf, kreativer Arbeit Lernen Essen Sexualität. Kommentar GebüH König, Volksheilkunde Verlag Dieser Kommentar beinhaltet erstmalig ausführliche Leistungsbeschreibungen entsprechend analogisierten Regularien Erstattungshinweisen. Die Anforderungen fachgerechte Diagnose ausführlich dargestellt. Die Jahren bewährte Erstattungstabelle Autors, exakten Leistungszuschüsse Beihilfen Postbeamtenkrankenkasse B, kopierfähigen Einlagen Patientenaufklärung abweichenden Honorarvereinbarung Buch für Heilpraktiker unentbehrlichen Nachschlagewerk. Hufeland-Leistungsverzeichnis Besonderen Therapierichtungen Hufelandgesellschaft, Haug Verlag Das Hufelandverzeichnis für Ärzte, Versicherte Patienten wertvolle Orientierungshilfe Abrechnung komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren. Es enthält Analog- GOÄ-Ziffern, anwendbar ambulanten Bereich berücksichtigt private Krankenkassen. Die Auswahl Verfahren erfolgte hoher praktischer Relevanz. So liegt Schwerpunkt Methoden, Naturheilkunde, Homöopathie, Akupunktur Anthroposophischen Medizin Anwendung kommen. Neu: - Tabelle Osteopathie Feldenkrais - Tabelle Ergebnissen Erhebung Qualitätssicherung Komplementärmedizin Mykosen Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen- Diagnose Therapie EAV Voll Homöopathie für Zahnärzte Bartak Dr. Jan Bartak bietet Buch homöopathischen Ratgeber, ständiger Begleiter (zahn-) ärztlichen Alltag konzipert ist. Homöopathie ganzheitliche Medizin pas excellence für beste Einstieg ganzheitliche (Zahn-) Heilkunde. Bei praktischen gezieltem Eingehen (zahn-) ärztliche Praxis Leser onzentrierter Form Geschichte ursprünglichen Grundlagen Homöopathie vertraut gemacht. Ergänzend Bartak komplementäre Methoden - speziell Elektroakupunktur Voll-, homöopathischen Verfahren (zahn-) ärztlichen Praxis harmonisch effektiv ergänzen können. Mikrobiologie + Homöopathie Ruf, ML-Verlag Darmparasitose Humanmedizin • Grundlagen • Klinik • Diagnostik • Therapieanmedizin Fonk, ASKE Verlag DARMPARASITOSE IN DER HUMANMEDIZIN – Grundlagen, Klinik, Diagnostik, Therapie: Lehrbuch, Praxis- Fachinformationen kombiniert. Für wen? Für Leser, zeitaufwändiges Literaturstudium schnell sachlich über Vielschichtigkeit Krankheitsbildes „Darmparasitose“ einschließlich therapeutischen Möglichkeiten informieren möchte. Für modernen Homo sapiens, zuvor vielfältigster Weise Gefahr Parasitose aussetzt, wissen ahnen. Zur Unterstützung Therapeuten, bereit ist, klinischen Blick verlassen handeln, Labor pathologischen Befund ist. Für Medizinstudenten Suche Brückenschlag Theorie Praxis. Für Humanmediziner, Repertoire Darmparasitose Regel vorkommt, für Darmparasiten modernen, hygienebewussten, hightech- pharma-orientierten Generation undenkbar somit Thema unseres Gesundheitswesens darstellen. Dieser Auffassung pragmatisches Handikap Vorschub leisten, nämlich modernen sanitären Anlagen, Stuhlkontrolle Patienten, früher unvermeidlich war, unmöglich machen. Last but not least für notwendige Entwicklung verbesserter, aussagefähigerer finanzierbarer Nachweismethoden für Routine-Labor. Rickettsiose - System Hauterkrankungen Fonk, ASKE Verlag Es Borreliose sein! Wussten Sie, Zecken Biss Infektionscocktail übertragen können? Dazu gehören Borrelien FSME-Viren, Rickettsien (Fleckfieber, Q-Fieber, Wolhynisches Fieber, Zeckenbiss-Fieber, Ehrlichien, Bartonellen), Babesien, Tularämie …. Rickettsien weltweit verbreitet Zecken, Milben (z.B. Grasmilben) Insekten. Rickettsiose – Krankheitsbilder: Gehirnhaut-, Herzinnenhaut-, Herzmuskelentzündungen, atypische Pneumonie, Lungenfibrose, Hepatitis, Polyarthritis, Polyradikulitis, Neurodermitis, Lymphome Non-Hodgkin-Lymphom, T-Zell-Lymphom u.a. Malignom. Dass Krankheiten Rickettsiose verbergen kann, differenzialdiagnostischen Überlegungen berücksichtigt. Diagnostik Rickettsiose: Eine Labordiagnose akuten Krankheitsfall möglich. Die Antikörper-Titer entwickeln Wochen, teilweise Monate Infektion. Hinzukommt, antibiotischen Therapie, Regel sofort eingeleitet wird, Antikörper entwickeln können. Die Rickettsiose unbekanntes Krankheitsbild, tatsächlich großer Bedeutung für Gesundheitswesen. Ohne bio-logische Diagnoseverfahren Diagnose Rickettsiose trotz bester, modernster High-Tech-Laborausrüstung akuten Stadium, häufig Spätstadium, gestellt. Das medizinische Paradigma Hanzl, Haug Verlag Brückenschlag Schulmedizin Komplementärmedizin: Dieses Buch beitragen, Kluft Schulmedizin naturheilkundlichen regulationsmedizinischen Verfahren überbrücken. Es klassischen Schulmediziner zeigen, daß Anpassung medizinischen Modelle modernste (natur-)wissenschaftliche Erkenntnisse Kybernetik, Systemtheorie, Quantenphysik Chaosforschung, neues medizinisches Paradigma, bestehende Misere Gebiet chronischer Erkrankungen überwunden kann. Den wissenschaftlichen Fundierung interessierten Vertretern komplementärmedizinischer Verfahren zeigen, daß Großteil Verfahren streng wissenschaftlich begründbar ist. Von Prof. Dr. F.-A. Popp Buch Bibel für komplementärmedizinischen Verfahren bezeichnet. Elektroakupunktur zahnärztl. Praxis Kramer, ML-Verlag Die Elektroakupunktur Krankheiten Ausbruch erkennen, Belastungen Körpers Umweltgifte austesten, Medikamentenrückstände -schäden messen, Allergieneigung testen, Krankheitsherde aufspüren Behandlungserfolge kontrollieren. Für Zahnarzt Elektroakupunktur besonderer Bedeutung, Basis üblichen klinischen Diagnostik zusätzliche Hilfe gibt, soliden odontogenen Herddiagnostik kommen. Kompendium Elektroakupunktur Rossmann, Haug-Verlag Praxisorientierte Einführung Grundlagen systematischen Elektroakupunktur Voll. Das System Grundregulation Pischinger, Haug Verlag Mit Fachbuch liegt Hauptwerk für wissenschaftliche Begründung biologischen Medizin Erklärungsmodell für Vielzahl komplementäerer Heilverfahren vor. Es liefert praxisorientierte, verständliche Einführung komplexe Materie: Das System Grundregulation bildet Pischinger Wechselwirkungen Zelle-Milieu-System ab. Es Gegenstand Entzündungs- Abwehrvorgänge zuständig für Lebensgrundlagenfunktionen. Anhaltende Störungen Grundregulation behindern genetisch programmierte Zellfunktion Krankheitserscheinungen Folge. Das Grundregulationssystem Erklärungsmodell Vielzahl komplementärer Heilverfahren. wendbares Konzept integriert: Humoralpathologie, Organpathologie, Neuralpathologie, Zellular- Permeabilitätspathologie. Wandlungsphasen Max + Moritz Pollmann, Haug Verlag Der Einstieg Denkweise Chinesischen Medizin, Welt Analogien Bildvergleiche, fällt westlich ausgebildeten Arzt leicht. Die grundlegende Lehre "Fünf Wandlungsphasen" "Fünf Elemente" Buch verständlich, einprägsam anschaulich dargestellt. Uns vertraute bekannte Figuren Wilhelm Buschs "Max Moritz", setzt Autor Beziehung Wesensart fünf Elemente. Wer hätte gedacht, daß Lehrer Lämpel, Schneider Böck guten Onkel Fritz Analogien chinesischen Typologie finden ließen? Der Leser findet Buch heitere, treffende Einführung Theorie Chinesischen Medizin konkrete diagnostische therapeutische Hinweise für Akupunkturpraxis, frei Motto: "Aber Weisheit Lehren muß Vergnügen hören." Das hyperaktive Kind Rosival, Ravensburger Nicht Hyperaktivität Hauptproblem "hyperaktiven Kinder", Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, hohe Sensibilität Impulsivität. Solche Kinder immer. Nur fallen Gesellschaft, unserem Schulsystem eher leiden, Eltern Erzieher, darunter, daß steuern können, Umfeld gefordert wird. Dieser Ratgeber erklärt beschreibt Aufmerksamkeitsstörung, Hyperaktivität auftreten kann, veranschaulicht Erscheinungsbild Beispielen Eltern Mut, Leben Kind schwieriger, hoffnungslos ist. Infektionskrankheiten Umweltgifte Sarkisyanz, ML-Verlag Mykosen ganzheitlich betrachtet Häring, Pro-Medicina Verlag Ein modernes Lehrbuch Mykologie Fotos Dokumentationen Praxis. Die häufigsten pathogenen Mykoseerreger eingehend beschrieben. Außerdem gezeigt, mykotische Keime Organismus ausbreiten Krankheitssymptomen führen können. BIORESONANZ Allergien Tiere heilbar Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Biophysikalische Therapie Allergien Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Allergien nehmen weltweit zu. Allergien entwickeln stets variierende maskierte Formen - zuletzt umweltbedingt. Die Belastungen Asthma bronchiale, Heuschnupfen Neurodermitis reduzieren Lebensqualität Patienten dramatisch. Chemische Suppression Hyposensibilisierungsbehandlung zeigen unzureichend Erfolge erhöhten Nebenwirkungen Gefahren. Anhand langjähriger, sorgfältig dokumentierter Erfolge kinderärztlicher Praxis weist Verfasser nach, daß Allergien vollständig nachhaltig heilbar können, biophysikalisches Phänomen erkennt physikalischen Gesetzen behandelt. Auf Basis 'Bioresonanztherapie' bewährten Konzeption vermittelt Buch umfassend systematisch Grundlagen Praxis biophysikalischen 'Löschung' Allergien - Fremdsubstanzen belastende Nebenwirkungen, insbesondere Aspekt Kinderheilkunde. Bioresonanz - Heilen Medikamente Maasz-Daley, Lerch, Haug Verlag Heilen inneren Kraft: Die Bioresonanztherapie - revolutionäre wirksame Heilmethode - Fachkundigund verständlich beschrieben - Zahlreiche Fallbeispiele, Behandlungsmöglichkeiten anschaulicherläutert werden. Endlich Allergien mehr, Schluß quälenden Kopf- Rückenschmerzen. Die erfolgreiche Heilmethode deutschen Arzt Franz Morell entwickelt. Zahlreiche Beispiele Praxis veranschaulichen, Krankheiten Rheuma, Morbus Bechterew, akuten chronischen Schmerzzuständen, Migräne, Allergien, Asthma, Neurodermitis stressbedingten Erkrankungen bewährt hat. Die Bioresonanztherapie bietet Möglichkeit, Medikamente völlig schmerzlos gesund werden. Sie für Kinder geeignet. Neue Lebenskraft Bioresonanz Dr. med. Dörfler, Simondo Gesundheitsservice Erstmals möglich, Belastungen unseres energetischen Systems exakt erfasen. Die Behandlung greift tief Gefüge ermöglicht es, Patienten "rückwärts Sackgasse Krankheit" herauszuführen. Warum kränker? Wie funktioniert Energiesystem? Wie Diagnostik Therapie sich? Welche Mitarbeit Patienten verlangt? Wie Patient weiterhin gesund erhalten? Welche begleitenden Behandlungen hilfreich sinnvoll? (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Welcome Welcome Dear Visitor, we are happy to present you our newest: Kindling EASY! Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor. For the first time we present the Kindling EASY on following trade fairs and invite you to test and inform you on site: 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Elektroacupuncture Bioresonance Our electroacupuncture devices offer you ease of working with EAV ans other methods at reasonable prices. In our inventory you find both manually controlled and computer-controlled bioresonance devices for successful use your practice. With more than 25 years of experience and certified quality management, Kindling is one of the leading manufacturers of high-quality devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Dr. Voll and Bioresonance. On our website, we offer you overview of our products as well as contacts to qualified seminars and distributors. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044. Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! Our production is subject to the high standard assured under the Quality Management System DIN EN ISO 13485 (CAN/CSA 13485), which is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. All devices are registered medical products, registered with the German Institute for Medical Documentation and Information (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information). [Certification] (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Certification Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company &gt;&gt; Certification Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Certification Certified Quality Kindling GmbH has Quality Management System that is aligned with legal regulations, integrated and certified. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044 . Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! Our production is subject to the high standard assured under the Quality Management System DIN EN ISO 13485 (CAN/CSA 13485), which is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. All devices are registered medical products, registered with the German Institute for Medical Documentation and Information (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information). EG-Certification 93/42/EWG Anhang II Certification DIN EN ISO 13485 Certification CAN/CSA ISO 13485 </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling EASY Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance &gt;&gt; Kindling EASY Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Kindling EASY Bioresonance Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor. For futher information download our information flyer and do not hesitate to contact us! FLYER Download HERE [2.366 KB] </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. ************************* ************************* Watch out buying medical device! You use the device your practice? Is the device certified as medical product? See more information HERE ************************* Trade Fairs For Trade Fairs your country, please contact our dirstributors on-site . 18.4.2015 CAM 2015, Düsseldorf 9.5.2015 Roadshow: Testen – Anfassen – Ausprobieren, Köln 13.-14.6.2015 Deutscher Heilpraktikerkongress, Karlsruhe 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg ************************* </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Links Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Links | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Links Light therapy www.curator-med.de **************************************************************** Geobiologie Austria Geovital-Akademie für Geobiologie &amp; Strahlenschutz 6934 Sulzberg / Vorarlberg, Austria www.geovital-akademie.com **************************************************************** </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Distributors Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Distributors | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Distributors Germany Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Germany Phone: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 Internet: www.kindling.de/eng E-mail: info@kindling.de ******************************************************************** The Netherlands R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Netherlands Phone: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Austria Trikomvit Austria e.U. Dr. M. Hohl Georgestraße 27 4222 Langenstein Phone: +43 7237438011 Internet: www.trikomvit.at E-Mail: info@trikomvit.at ******************************************************************** Spain Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spain Phone: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Turkey Anfora Saglik Tic.Ltd. Sti Karaman Mahallesi Açelya Sokak Ufuk Apt. No 8 03730 Afyonkarahisar Internet: www.akupunkturkey.com E-Mail: info@akupunkturkey.com ******************************************************************** Canada Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Canada Phone: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Canada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Phone: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** Japan Gain Inc. Mr. Yasuaki Yoshikawa 6F Onoe Building, 4-4-2 Takadanobaba Shinjuku-ku, Tokiyo, Japan Phone: +81 (0)3-5332-6334 Fax: +81 (0)3-5332-3488 E-mail: lucky@gain-life.jp ******************************************************************** ******************************************************************** If you cannot find contact person your country, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Your Kindling-Team </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Seminars Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Seminars | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Seminars Our partners offer extensive seminars their specific national languages. Please contact the specific company or us. We be glad to assist you with getting touch with them. MBA GmbH Lindenstr. 1 65555 Limburg a. d. Lahn/Offheim Germany Phone: +49-(0)6431-9217900 Fax: +49-(0)6431-92179089 Internet: www.mba-gmbh.de E-Mail: mba@teliko.net ******************************************************************** R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Netherlands Phone: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spain Phone: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Canada Phone: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Canada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Phone: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** If you cannot find contact person your country, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Your Kindling-Team Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Germany Phone: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 Internet: www.kindling.de/eng E-mail: info@kindling.de </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Software Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Software | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Software Computer-based working Computer-based working alternative methods is becoming more and more important. It simplifies extensive documentations and allows to work effectively. As result of the elimination of many preparations software is of steadily increasing importance by making digital preparations available (digital waves). In close cooperation with experienced doctors, practitioners and software engineers two different software systems were developed which are adapted to the Kindling devices. HOMOPATH ® Further information here </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Accessories Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Accessories Accessories Electroacupuncture Accessories Bioresonance | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Accessories for Elektroakupuncture and Bioresonance Accessories for the Elektroakupuncture Accessories for the Bioresonance For precise measurements and successful treatments with our Kindling EAV devices, we offer suitable accessories for all applications. Here you find specially designed standard and specialised accessories for successful use of Kindling bioresonance devices. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Modul Combinations Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Modul Combinations Devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll Combination with Bioresonance Therapy On this page you find the combination options for housing types that are specifically designed to be compatible with each other. Additionally, all Kindling devices our current product inventory can be combined with each other and most can be connected to all Kindling software programs. Akuport M1+ / MT Coordinated harmony between modern EAV diagnostics and therapy. Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV and bioresonance therapy compact system unit. The ideal starter for modern measurement and rectifying therapy procedures. Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 The Akuport Tower combines EAV diagnostics and treatment with the advantages of bioresonance. Easy, quick and compact, you have complete system unit at your disposal. Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport-Geräten Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Using Retec 2000 CP combined with the Combi-2 you find no boundaries to your work EAV and bioresonance. Vistron / Akuport D-tec The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies - here combination with EAV diagnostic device Vistron. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System By simply stacking the modules, contact and power supply are mutually established. The devices react as unit. You just need one power supply. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Bioresonance Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Bioresonance Devices for Bioresonance Therapy The Kindling devices our current product inventory can largely be combined with each other [Model Combinations] and connected to our Kindling software programs. Kindling EASY Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor Akuport MR2 Modular device for resonance therapy – as stand-alone version or can be combined with the EAV diagnostic device Akuport M1+. Retec 2000 CP Software controlled bioresonance device for universal and versatile resonance application. Potentizer Akuport D-tec The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies. Can be combined with the bioresonance devices Akuport MR2 or RETEC 2000CP and the EAV diagnostic device Vistron. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Electroacupuncture Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Electroacupuncture Vistron Combi-2 Akuport M2 Akuport M1+ Akuport MT Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Electroacupuncture Devices for the Electroacupuncture Most Kindling devices our current inventory can be combined with each other [Model Combinations] and can be connected with all Kindling software programs. DIAGNOSTICS &amp; THERAPY Vistron Perfect combination of diagnosis, electrotherapy and data transfer – the latest model our product portfolio impress you with its new technology and precise, easy to read bar display. Combi-2 Versatility of diagnosis and treatment one device – the premium middle class for demanding users. Akuport M1+/MT Alone or combined simple plug &amp; play-system, these devices can be tailored to suit individualised work places. DIAGNOSTICS Akuport M2 This portable diagnostic device with integrated measurement of electrical current the mouth, large display instrument and digital display is ideal for the practice and for portable use. Akuport M1+ The ideal starting device for the modern bioelectrical assessment procedures of EAV; expandable modular system with the Akuport MT and/or MR2. THERAPY Akuport MT A therapeutic device available for electroacupuncture, as module for the M1+ or as stand-alone version. Our devices are approved medical products compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Creating New Momentum with Quality and Skill For more than 30 years, the Kindling company has been known for its electroacupuncture devices Germany and around the world. As one of the market leaders the development and production of devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll (EAV) and Bioresonance, Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik is important partner for doctors, dentists and healing practitioners who utilise biometric system diagnostics. Our many years of experience and in-depth collaboration with our customers ensure high standard of quality and enable us to optimise products close relationship to practice, and to continue with new developments. We are approved developer and manufacturer of medical products. This requires compliance with the demands of EU-Guideline 93/42/EEC as well as the existence of monitored quality assurance system (EN DIN ISO 13485, CAN/CSA 13485). The monitoring and certification is performed by the notified body TÜV NORD CERT GmbH (ID-Number 0044). [Certification] The application of the CE-label, including the ID-Number 0044, on our devices indicates that this is certified and approved medical product. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044. Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! The high quality of our products, technically skilful consultation, as well as reliable technical services, form the basis for the solid market position of our products. To provide you with full service, high-value training and continuing education, we have worked cooperation with MBA GmbH since 1999. MBA is responsible for Kindling products for the entire German market and is specialised customer-specific consulting, high-quality training and continuing education programs. Furthermore, there are sales operations other countries such as the Netherlands, Spain, North America, Taiwan, and Japan, amongst others. [Dirstributors] Take look at the product variety on our website or contact us – we satisfy your requirements regarding the creation of the optimal workplace. Your Kindling-Team </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Welcome Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Home | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Welcome Dear Visitor, we are happy to present you our newest: Kindling EASY! Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor. For the first time we present the Kindling EASY on following trade fairs and invite you to test and inform you on site: 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg Elektroacupuncture Bioresonance Our electroacupuncture devices offer you ease of working with EAV ans other methods at reasonable prices. In our inventory you find both manually controlled and computer-controlled bioresonance devices for successful use your practice. With more than 25 years of experience and certified quality management, Kindling is one of the leading manufacturers of high-quality devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Dr. Voll and Bioresonance. On our website, we offer you overview of our products as well as contacts to qualified seminars and distributors. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044. Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! Our production is subject to the high standard assured under the Quality Management System DIN EN ISO 13485 (CAN/CSA 13485), which is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. All devices are registered medical products, registered with the German Institute for Medical Documentation and Information (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information). [Certification] ************************* ************************* Watch out buying medical device! You use the device your practice? Is the device certified as medical product? See more information HERE ************************* Trade Fairs For Trade Fairs your country, please contact our dirstributors on-site . 18.4.2015 CAM 2015, Düsseldorf 9.5.2015 Roadshow: Testen – Anfassen – Ausprobieren, Köln 13.-14.6.2015 Deutscher Heilpraktikerkongress, Karlsruhe 29.8.2015 Deutscher Naturheilkundetag, Hannover 28.10.-1.11.2015 Medizinische Woche Baden-Baden 21.-22.11.2015 Norddeutscher Heilpraktiker Fortbildungskongress, Hamburg ************************* </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör Bioresonanz Zubehör Bioresonanz Sollten Sie gewünschtes Produkt finden, kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter. Akuport D-tec Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen. Kombinierbar EAV Gerät Vistron Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP. Elektroden Tiefensonden Eingangs- Ausgangsbecher Ampullen(halter)-Einsatz für Messbecher Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 4cm Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 5 cm Fußplatten einseitig beschichtet Magnetfolie, 1 Paar, ca. 25 12 cm Stirnelektrode Klammerelektrode Farbe (rot, gelb, schwarz, grün) Salbenstab / Individualisierungsstab Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde, klein Magnetfeld-Tiefensonde, groß Zahnfleischrolle Gesicht- Faltenrolle Leitungen Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 2m, 1 Paar Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 0,5m, 1 Paar Retec-Leitung, abgeschirmt, 0,5m Farbe (rot, schwarz) Leerröhrchen Flaschen Tropfflasche, 10ml Tropfflasche, 30ml Globoliflasche, 10ml Ampullen, Ø 10mm Ampullen Rollrand, Ø 10mm Ampullen Korkverschluss Ø 15mm Ampullenschachteln Pappe für 90 Ampullen Netzteile Ladegeräte Auskünfte Netzteilen Ladegeräten können Grund speziellen Abstimmung einzelnen Geräten Anfrage Angabe Gerätenummer erteilt werden. Kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter! Sonstiges Magnetfeld-Retec-Matte, ca. 32 42cm Resonanzplättchen, 50Stk Resonanzplättchen, 50Stk, Kompass Erdungsband, 1,5m Stativ für Tiefensonde Becherglas, 50ml Petrischale Petrieschale Deckel Unarzneiliche Globoli, 1000g Größe 3 Si-Adapter, Farbe ** Alle Abbildungen möglichst großem Format abgebildet. Die Größenverhältnisse abgebildeten Gegenstände untereinander entsprechen demnach realistischen Größenverhältnissen. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Zubehör für Elektroakupunktur Sollten Sie gewünschtes Produkt finden, kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter. Akuport D-tec Modulares Gerät Erzeugung elektronischer Potenzen. Kombinierbar EAV Gerät Vistron Bioresonanzgeräten Akuport MR2 Retec 2000CP. Q-switch Umschalter für Sektorenmessung für 7 Messstrecken, wahlweise manuell automatisch steuerbar. Kombinierbar Kindling-EAV-Geräten. Elektroden Handelektroden, Messing, 1 Paar Handelektrode, Silber Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 4cm Kugelelektroden, 1 Paar, Ø 5 cm Fußelektroden, Messing, 1 Paar Stirnelektrode Rollelektrode Duo-Rollelektrode Gummielektroden, 1 Paar, ca. 14 7 cm Gesicht- Faltenrolle Zahnfleischrolle Zahnelektrode Zahnelektroden, 1 Paar Leitung Waben Ampullenabgreifer Medikamenten-Testwabe, 6-Loch, Ø 5cm Medikamenten-Testwabe, 16-Loch, Ø 10cm Verbindungsstecker für Testwaben Abtastgabel für Einzelampullen Abtastplatte für 10 Ampullen Punktsonden Punktsonde für M1+ Punktsonde für M2 Punktsonde für Combi-2 Punktsonde für Vistron Punktsonde für K2000 Messspitzen 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Messing 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Messing für Vistron Kugel-Spitze, Messing Niederdruckmessspitze, Messing 4-Schlitz-Spitze, Silber Kugel-Spitze, Silber Niederdruckmessspitze, Silber Leitungen Messleitung, 2m Stecker: Si – Si, pro Farbe (schwarz, rot, grün, gelb) Messleitung, 2m Stecker: Si - DoppelSi schwarz Messleitung/Wabenleitung, 0,5m Stecker: DoppelSi - DoppelSi schwarz Messleitung/Wabenleitung, 0,5m Stecker: Si - Si schwarz Stimulationsleitung, 1 Paar Si-Stecker rot schwarz Stimulationsleitung Klinkenstecker für Akuport MT USB-Leitung, 2m Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: Klinke - Klinke Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: 6-pol.Din – Klinke Verbindungsleitung, 2m Stecker: 6-pol.Din – 6-pol.Din Verbindungsleitung, 2,5m Stecker: Klinke - Chinch Verbindungsleitung, 2,5m Stecker: Klinke - DoppelSi Netzteile Ladegeräte Auskünfte Netzteilen Ladegeräten können Grund speziellen Abstimmung einzelnen Geräten Anfrage Angabe Gerätenummer erteilt werden. Kontaktieren Sie – helfen Ihnen gerne weiter! Sonstiges Si-Adapter für Elektroden Waben Farbe (rot, schwarz) Messstreckenumschalter/Quadrantenumschalter Erdungsband, 1,5m ** Alle Abbildungen möglichst großer Qualität abgebildet. Die Größenverhältnisse abgebildeten Gegenstände untereinander entsprechen demnach realistischen Größenverhältnissen. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Certification Certification Certified Quality Kindling GmbH has Quality Management System that is aligned with legal regulations, integrated and certified. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044 . Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! Our production is subject to the high standard assured under the Quality Management System DIN EN ISO 13485 (CAN/CSA 13485), which is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. All devices are registered medical products, registered with the German Institute for Medical Documentation and Information (Deutsches Institut für Medizinische Dokumentation Information). EG-Certification 93/42/EWG Anhang II Certification DIN EN ISO 13485 Certification CAN/CSA ISO 13485 (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> General Terms and Conditions Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company &gt;&gt; General Terms and Conditions Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | General Terms and Conditions § General The following conditions apply exclusively for our sales. Purchase conditions of our customers do not establish obligations on our part, even if we do not explicitly refuse them. If our shipment is accepted, then our sales and payment conditions are considered recognised. § Offers Our offers are non-binding. Incoming orders are only binding on your receipt of confirmation. This applies to oral agreements and declarations of any kind. § Orders All orders and any modifications to them are to be sent to us written form. § Delivery Delivery is strictly ex-works; shipping and packaging be made according to our best judgement. § Complaints Complaints must be sent to us writing within 30 days of the date of delivery. § Packaging Packaging be billed at cost. § Payment Our invoices are payable within eight days of receipt of invoice. The invoices are payable net, without any discount for prompt payment or other deductions, to the extent that nothing to the contrary is marked on the invoice. In the event that payment is not rendered promptly, we reserve the right to bill for default interest and the costs of bank credit. We reserve the right to process orders from new customers or customers with poor payment history on pre-payment basis only. § Reservation of Title The delivered goods remain our property until paid for full. If the goods are sold before this, the resulting claim is deemed ceded to us. If proceeds are received for the claim, these are to be transferred to us. § Place of Fulfilment and Court of Jurisdiction The place of fulfilment for delivery and payment is Hildesheim. The Court of Jurisdiction for both parties is the District Court of Hildesheim, Germany. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> People Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company &gt;&gt; People Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | People The success of Kindling GmbH is determined by the understanding of and commitment to company goals, shared by all of our employees. Our qualified employees assure the high standard of our products through their responsible work within our Quality Management Systems. The management consists of Designer and Management Executive, Kerstin Abrams and Engineer, Eduard Abrams. The company’s founder and current Consultant, Franz Schulz, complements and supports the Team with his experience Development and Quality Management. Kerstin Abrams Managing Director Design Marketing Eduard Abrams Managing Director Development Production Quality Management Franz Schulz Consultant Development Quality Management </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling EASY Kindling EASY Bioresonance Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor. For futher information download our information flyer and do not hesitate to contact us! FLYER Download HERE (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGBs AGBs § Allgemeines Für Verkäufe gelten ausschließlich nachstehenden Bedingungen. Einkaufsbedingungen Kunden verpflichten nicht, widersprechen. Wenn Lieferung angenommen wird, gelten Verkaufs- Zahlungsbedingungen anerkannt. § Angebote Unsere Angebote unverbindlich. Eingehende Aufträge Ihnen zugehende Bestätigung für verbindlich. Dies gilt ebenfalls für mündliche Absprachen Erklärungen Art. § Bestellungen Alle Bestellungen Änderungen schriftlicher Form richten. § Lieferung Die Lieferung erfolgt grundsätzlich Werk, Versand Verpackung erfolgen bestem Ermessen. § Beanstandungen Beanstandungen müssen innerhalb 30 Tagen Lieferdatum schriftlich gerichtet sein. § Verpackung Die Verpackung Selbstkostenpreis berechnet. § Zahlung Unsere Rechungen zahlbar innerhalb 8 Tagen Rechnungseingang. Die Rechnungen zahlbar rein netto, Abzug Skonto sonstigen Abzügen, sofern Rechungen Gegenteiliges vermerkt ist. Bei Nichteinhaltung pünktlicher Zahlung behalten vor, Verzugszinsen Kosten Bankkredite jeweils gültigen Höhe Rechnung stellen. Wir behalten vor, Aufträge Neukunden Kunden negativer Zahlungshistorie Vorauskasse bearbeiten. § Eigentumsvorbehalt Die gelieferte Ware bleibt restlosen Bezahlung Eigentum. Wird Ware vorher verkauft, gilt entstandene Forderung abgetreten. Gehen Forderung Beträge ein, abzuführen. § Erfüllungsort Gerichtsstand Erfüllungsort für Lieferung Zahlung Hildesheim. Gerichtsstand für Teile Amtsgericht Hildesheim, Deutschland. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Links Links Light therapy www.curator-med.de **************************************************************** Geobiologie Austria Geovital-Akademie für Geobiologie &amp; Strahlenschutz 6934 Sulzberg / Vorarlberg, Austria www.geovital-akademie.com **************************************************************** (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Distributors Distributors Germany Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Germany Phone: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 Internet: www.kindling.de/eng E-mail: info@kindling.de ******************************************************************** The Netherlands R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Netherlands Phone: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Austria Trikomvit Austria e.U. Dr. M. Hohl Georgestraße 27 4222 Langenstein Phone: +43 7237438011 Internet: www.trikomvit.at E-Mail: info@trikomvit.at ******************************************************************** Spain Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spain Phone: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Turkey Anfora Saglik Tic.Ltd. Sti Karaman Mahallesi Açelya Sokak Ufuk Apt. No 8 03730 Afyonkarahisar Internet: www.akupunkturkey.com E-Mail: info@akupunkturkey.com ******************************************************************** Canada Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Canada Phone: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Canada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Phone: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** Japan Gain Inc. Mr. Yasuaki Yoshikawa 6F Onoe Building, 4-4-2 Takadanobaba Shinjuku-ku, Tokiyo, Japan Phone: +81 (0)3-5332-6334 Fax: +81 (0)3-5332-3488 E-mail: lucky@gain-life.jp ******************************************************************** ******************************************************************** If you cannot find contact person your country, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Your Kindling-Team (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Seminars Seminars Our partners offer extensive seminars their specific national languages. Please contact the specific company or us. We be glad to assist you with getting touch with them. MBA GmbH Lindenstr. 1 65555 Limburg a. d. Lahn/Offheim Germany Phone: +49-(0)6431-9217900 Fax: +49-(0)6431-92179089 Internet: www.mba-gmbh.de E-Mail: mba@teliko.net ******************************************************************** R. L. Vlieger Mounebuorren 17 9132 EJ Engwierum Netherlands Phone: +31-(0)511-408445 Internet: www.kindling.nl E-Mail: rl.vlieger@kindling.nl ******************************************************************** Cearbe Kindling C/Santiago Galas Urb. Rio Salia n9 E-39500 CABEZON Dela SAL Spain Phone: +34-942-701146 Internet: www.electroacupuntura.net E-Mail: info@electroacupuntura.net ******************************************************************** Matrixx Solutions 359 Pompano Crt Oshawa, Ontario L1K 1M9 Canada Phone: +1-905-259-7536 Internet: www.matrixx.ca E-Mail: info@matrixx.ca Lyra Nara 3 Dempsey Crt. Caledon, ON L7E 0E3 Canada Toll Free: +1-888-773-3196 Internet: www.lyranara.com ******************************************************************** Taiwan Anma Bio-technology Inc Mr. T.K. Chou 5/F, No. 68, Ren Ai Road , Section 2, Taipei Taiwan 100 Phone: +886232810808 E-Mail: tkc0412@anma.com.tw ******************************************************************** If you cannot find contact person your country, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Your Kindling-Team Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Gropiusstr. 9 31137 Hildesheim Germany Phone: +49 (0)5121-511997 Fax: +49 (0)5121-511927 Internet: www.kindling.de/eng E-mail: info@kindling.de (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Software Software Computer-based working Computer-based working alternative methods is becoming more and more important. It simplifies extensive documentations and allows to work effectively. As result of the elimination of many preparations software is of steadily increasing importance by making digital preparations available (digital waves). In close cooperation with experienced doctors, practitioners and software engineers two different software systems were developed which are adapted to the Kindling devices. HOMOPATH ® Further information here (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Accessories Accessories for Elektroakupuncture and Bioresonance Accessories for the Elektroakupuncture Accessories for the Bioresonance For precise measurements and successful treatments with our Kindling EAV devices, we offer suitable accessories for all applications. Here you find specially designed standard and specialised accessories for successful use of Kindling bioresonance devices. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Modul Combinations Modul Combinations Devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll Combination with Bioresonance Therapy On this page you find the combination options for housing types that are specifically designed to be compatible with each other. Additionally, all Kindling devices our current product inventory can be combined with each other and most can be connected to all Kindling software programs. Akuport M1+ / MT Coordinated harmony between modern EAV diagnostics and therapy. Akuport M1+ / MR2 EAV and bioresonance therapy compact system unit. The ideal starter for modern measurement and rectifying therapy procedures. Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 The Akuport Tower combines EAV diagnostics and treatment with the advantages of bioresonance. Easy, quick and compact, you have complete system unit at your disposal. Akuport D-tec Kombination Akuport-Geräten Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Using Retec 2000 CP combined with the Combi-2 you find no boundaries to your work EAV and bioresonance. Vistron / Akuport D-tec The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies - here combination with EAV diagnostic device Vistron. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Bioresonance Bioresonance Devices for Bioresonance Therapy The Kindling devices our current product inventory can largely be combined with each other [Model Combinations] and connected to our Kindling software programs. Kindling EASY Individual treatment without point measurement / tensor Akuport MR2 Modular device for resonance therapy – as stand-alone version or can be combined with the EAV diagnostic device Akuport M1+. Retec 2000 CP Software controlled bioresonance device for universal and versatile resonance application. Potentizer Akuport D-tec The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies. Can be combined with the bioresonance devices Akuport MR2 or RETEC 2000CP and the EAV diagnostic device Vistron. (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Electroacupuncture Electroacupuncture Devices for the Electroacupuncture Most Kindling devices our current inventory can be combined with each other [Model Combinations] and can be connected with all Kindling software programs. DIAGNOSTICS &amp; THERAPY Vistron Perfect combination of diagnosis, electrotherapy and data transfer – the latest model our product portfolio impress you with its new technology and precise, easy to read bar display. Combi-2 Versatility of diagnosis and treatment one device – the premium middle class for demanding users. Akuport M1+/MT Alone or combined simple plug &amp; play-system, these devices can be tailored to suit individualised work places. DIAGNOSTICS Akuport M2 This portable diagnostic device with integrated measurement of electrical current the mouth, large display instrument and digital display is ideal for the practice and for portable use. Akuport M1+ The ideal starting device for the modern bioelectrical assessment procedures of EAV; expandable modular system with the Akuport MT and/or MR2. THERAPY Akuport MT A therapeutic device available for electroacupuncture, as module for the M1+ or as stand-alone version. Our devices are approved medical products compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik Creating New Momentum with Quality and Skill For more than 30 years, the Kindling company has been known for its electroacupuncture devices Germany and around the world. As one of the market leaders the development and production of devices for Electroacupuncture acc. to Voll (EAV) and Bioresonance, Kindling GmbH Medizintechnik is important partner for doctors, dentists and healing practitioners who utilise biometric system diagnostics. Our many years of experience and in-depth collaboration with our customers ensure high standard of quality and enable us to optimise products close relationship to practice, and to continue with new developments. We are approved developer and manufacturer of medical products. This requires compliance with the demands of EU-Guideline 93/42/EEC as well as the existence of monitored quality assurance system (EN DIN ISO 13485, CAN/CSA 13485). The monitoring and certification is performed by the notified body TÜV NORD CERT GmbH (ID-Number 0044). [Certification] The application of the CE-label, including the ID-Number 0044, on our devices indicates that this is certified and approved medical product. Important information about buying device! When comparing offers, always check the manufacturer’s certifications. For medical product, this is CE label with the matching number of the regulatory office on the device. In our case, this is CE 0044. Without manufacturer’s certification, you be taking responsibility and risk, without any product liability! The high quality of our products, technically skilful consultation, as well as reliable technical services, form the basis for the solid market position of our products. To provide you with full service, high-value training and continuing education, we have worked cooperation with MBA GmbH since 1999. MBA is responsible for Kindling products for the entire German market and is specialised customer-specific consulting, high-quality training and continuing education programs. Furthermore, there are sales operations other countries such as the Netherlands, Spain, North America, Taiwan, and Japan, amongst others. [Dirstributors] Take look at the product variety on our website or contact us – we satisfy your requirements regarding the creation of the optimal workplace. Your Kindling-Team (C) 2006 - Alle Rechte vorbehalten Diese Seite drucken </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Vistron / Akuport D-tec Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Vistron / Akuport D-tec Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Vistron / Akuport D-tec Diagnostics, therapy and potentizing Akuport D-tec as small helper from Vistron The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies that allow the user to use wide diversity of complementary medical processes. Using the Vistron, these information can be transferred on carrier medium. In addition all functions of the EAV device Vistron are at their full disposal. Vistron (Electroacupuncture diagnostics and therapy) Akuport D-tec (Potentizer) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Diagnostics, therapy and bioresonance Using Retec 2000 CP combined with the Combi-2 you find no boundaries to your work EAV and bioresonance. Combi-2 Retec 2000 CP </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec combination Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Akuport D-tec combination Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport D-tec combination Potenzieren Integriert harmonisch Akuport-Kombinationen. Das einfache Plug &amp; Play System Akuportreihe erlaubt schnelles Zusammensetzten einzelner Module Platz sparenden Systemeinheit. Alle Funktionen einzelnen Akuport-Module bleiben hierbei erhalten. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Durch einfaches Aufsetzten Module Kontakt Stromversorgung untereinander hergestellt. Die Geräte reagieren Einheit. Es Stromversorgung nötig. Akuport M1+ (Diagnose) Akuport MT (Reizstromtherapie) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonanztherapie) Akuport D-tec (Potenzieren) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+/ MT/ MR2 Diagnostics, therapy and bioresonance The Akuport Tower combines EAV diagnostics and treatment with the advantages of bioresonance. Easy, quick and compact, you have complete system unit at your disposal. The easy Plug &amp; Play System allows quickly assembling of the single Akuport moduls to complete unit. All previous functions of the module Akuport M1+ , Akuport MT Akuport MR2 remain the same. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System By simply stacking the modules, contact and power supply are mutually established. The devices react as unit. You just need one power supply. Akuport M1+ (Diagnostics) Akuport MT (Therapy) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonance) Akuport D-tec (Potentizer) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MR2 Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ / MR2 Diagnostics and bioresonance EAV and bioresonance therapy compact system unit. The ideal starter for modern measurement and rectifying therapy procedures. The easy Plug &amp; Play System allows quickly assembling of the single Akuport moduls to complete unit. All previous functions of the module Akuport M1+ and Akuport MR2 remain the same. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System By simply stacking the modules, contact and power supply are mutually established. The devices react as unit. You just need one power supply. Akuport M1+ (Diagnostics) Akuport MT (Therapy) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonance) Akuport D-tec (Potentizer) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport M1+ / MT Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Model Combinations &gt;&gt; Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MT Akuport M1+ / MR2 Akuport M1+ / MT / MR2 Akuport D-tec combination Combi-2 / Retec 2000 CP Vistron / Akuport D-tec | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport M1+ / MT Diagnostics and therapy Coordinated harmony between modern EAV diagnostics and therapy. The easy Plug &amp; Play System allows quickly assembling of the single Akuport moduls to complete unit. All previous functions of the module Akuport M1+ and Akuport MT remain the same. Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System By simply stacking the modules, contact and power supply are mutually established. The devices react as unit. You just need one power supply. Akuport M1+ (Diagnostics) Akuport MT (Therapy) Akuport MR2 (Bioresonance) Akuport D-tec (Potentizer) </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Accessories for Bioresonance Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Accessories &gt;&gt; Accessories Bioresonance Accessories Electroacupuncture Accessories Bioresonance | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Accessories for Bioresonance If you cannot find desired product here, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Akuport D-tec Modular supplement to produce electronic potencies. The Akuport D-tec works combination with other devices for bioenergetic methods - as stand-alone-version with the Vistron and Retec 2000CP or with the Akuport MR2 by plug&amp;play system. Electrodes and magnetic field electrodes Input or Output beaker Ampoules holder for beaker Ball electrodes, 1 pair, Ø 4cm Ball electrodes, 1 pair, Ø 5cm Foot electrodes, brass coated with magnetic foil on one side 1 pair, ca. 25 12 cm Forehead electrode Clamp electrode per color (red, yellow, black, green) Ointment electrode Magnetic field electrode, lite Magnetic field electrode, strong Face roller Gingival roller Wires Retec wire, screened, 2m, 1 pair Retec wire, screened, 0,5m, 1 pair Retec wire, screened, 0,5m per color (red, black) Ampoules and Bottles Dropping bottle, 10ml Dropping bottle, 30ml Globoli bottle, 10ml Ampoules incl. lid, Ø 10mm Ampoules with rolled edge incl. lid, Ø 10mm Ampoules incl. cork lid Ø 15mm Ampoule-box, paperboard Power supplies and Charger Information concerning power supplies and rechargers can only be provided if you give the device’s number, since these are especially designed and constructed for the individual devices. Please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Other accessories Magnetic field mat, ca. 32 42cm Resonance platelets, 50 pieces Resonance platelets, 50 pieces, with compass Earthing strap, 1,5m Tripod for magnetic field electrode Glass beaker, 50ml Petri dish Petri dish with lid Non-medical globoli, 1000g size 3 Si-Adapter (adapter for safety plug) for electrodes and honeycombs per color (red, black) ** All illustrations are shown the best possible quality. The relative size ratios of the objects shown do not, however, correspond to the realistic size ratios. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Accessories for Electroacupuncture Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Accessories &gt;&gt; Accessories Electroacupuncture Accessories Electroacupuncture Accessories Bioresonance | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Accessories for Electroacupuncture If you cannot find desired product here, please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Akuport D-tec Modular supplement to produce electronic potencies. The Akuport D-tec works combination with other devices for bioenergetic methods - as stand-alone-version with the Vistron and Retec 2000CP or with the Akuport MR2 by plug&amp;play system. Q-switch Quadrant switch for sector measurement. You can choose up to 7 sections of measurements optionally manually or automatically controllable. Combinable to every Kindling EAV devices. Electrodes Hand elektrodes, brass, 1 pair Hand elektrode, silver Ball electrodes, 1 pair, Ø 4cm Ball electrodes, 1 pair, Ø 5 cm Foot electrodes, brass 1 pair, ca. 25 12 cm Forehead electrode Roller electrode Duo-Roller electrode Rubber electrodes, 1 pair, ca. 14 7 cm Face roller Gingeval roller Dental electrode Dental electrodes, 1 pair with wire Honeycombs and test plates for ampoules Honeycomb, 6-hole, Ø 5cm Honeycomb, 16-hole, Ø 10cm Connection plug for honeycombs Test plate for single ampoules Test plate for 10 ampoules Stylus Stylus for M1+ Stylus for M2 Stylus for Combi-2 Stylus for Vistron Stylus for K2000 Measuring tips 4-slice tip, brass 4-slice tip, brass for Vistron Ball tip, brass Low-Pressure tip, brass Body tip, brass Ear tip, brass 4-slice tip, silver Ball tip, silver Low-Pressure tip, silver Body tip, silver Ear tip, silver Wires Measuring wire, 2m plugs: Si - Si, per color (black, red, green, yellow) Measuring wire, 2m plugs: Si - doubleSi, black Measuring wire / Honeycomb wire, 0,5m plugs: doubleSi - doubleSi black Measuring wire / Honeycomb wire, 0,5m plugs: Si - Si black Stimulation wire, 1 pair with adapter for safety plug red and black Stimulation wire, 1 pair with jack plug for Akuport MT USB wire, 2m Connecting wire, 2m Plugs: jack - jack Connecting wire, 2m plugs: 6-pin Din – jack Connecting wire, 2m plugs: 6-pin Din – 6-pin Din Connecting wire, 2,5m plugs: jack - chinch Connecting wire, 2,5m plugs: jack - doubleSi Power supplies and Charger Information concerning power supplies and rechargers can only be provided if you give the device’s number, since these are especially designed and constructed for the individual devices. Please contact us. We be glad to assist you! Other accessories Si-Adapter (adapter for safety plug) for electrodes and honeycombs per color (red, black) Quadrant switch Earthing strap, 1,5m ** All illustrations are shown the best possible quality. The relative size ratios of the objects shown do not, however, correspond to the realistic size ratios. </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Literature Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance &gt;&gt; Literature Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Literature BIORESONANCE Allergien Tiere heilbar Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Biophysikalische Therapie Allergien Schuhmacher, Sonntag Verlag Allergien nehmen weltweit zu. Allergien entwickeln stets variierende maskierte Formen - zuletzt umweltbedingt. Die Belastungen Asthma bronchiale, Heuschnupfen Neurodermitis reduzieren Lebensqualität Patienten dramatisch. Chemische Suppression Hyposensibilisierungsbehandlung zeigen unzureichend Erfolge erhöhten Nebenwirkungen Gefahren. Anhand langjähriger, sorgfältig dokumentierter Erfolge kinderärztlicher Praxis weist Verfasser nach, daß Allergien vollständig nachhaltig heilbar können, biophysikalisches Phänomen erkennt physikalischen Gesetzen behandelt. Auf Basis 'Bioresonanztherapie' bewährten Konzeption vermittelt Buch umfassend systematisch Grundlagen Praxis biophysikalischen 'Löschung' Allergien - Fremdsubstanzen belastende Nebenwirkungen, insbesondere Aspekt Kinderheilkunde. Bioresonanz - Heilen Medikamente Maasz-Daley, Lerch, Haug Verlag Heilen inneren Kraft: Die Bioresonanztherapie - revolutionäre wirksame Heilmethode - Fachkundigund verständlich beschrieben - Zahlreiche Fallbeispiele, Behandlungsmöglichkeiten anschaulicherläutert werden. Endlich Allergien mehr, Schluß quälenden Kopf- Rückenschmerzen. Die erfolgreiche Heilmethode deutschen Arzt Franz Morell entwickelt. Zahlreiche Beispiele Praxis veranschaulichen, Krankheiten Rheuma, Morbus Bechterew, akuten chronischen Schmerzzuständen, Migräne, Allergien, Asthma, Neurodermitis stressbedingten Erkrankungen bewährt hat. Die Bioresonanztherapie bietet Möglichkeit, Medikamente völlig schmerzlos gesund werden. Sie für Kinder geeignet. Neue Lebenskraft Bioresonanz Dr. med. Dörfler, Simondo Gesundheitsservice Erstmals möglich, Belastungen unseres energetischen Systems exakt erfasen. Die Behandlung greift tief Gefüge ermöglicht es, Patienten "rückwärts Sackgasse Krankheit" herauszuführen. Warum kränker? Wie funktioniert Energiesystem? Wie Diagnostik Therapie sich? Welche Mitarbeit Patienten verlangt? Wie Patient weiterhin gesund erhalten? Welche begleitenden Behandlungen hilfreich sinnvoll? </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport D-tec Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance &gt;&gt; Akuport D-tec Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport D-tec Potentizer The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies from native or virtual potencies. Can be combined with the bioresonance devices Akuport MR2 or RETEC 2000CP and the EAV diagnostic device Vistron. The Akuport D-tec produces electronic potencies that allow the user to use wide diversity of complementary medical processes. With the Akuport D-tec you can determine which potency is necessary every individual case. The Akuport D-tec works combination with other devices for bioenergetic methods - as stand-alone-version with the Vistron and Retec 2000CP or with the Akuport MR2 by plug&amp;play system. Kindling Akuport D-tec *Potency ranges: D3, D4, D6, D8, D10, D12, D15, D30, D60, D100, D200 Output for transfering the electronic potency to carrier medium Potentizing controll through LED display *Power supply from mains with medical power supply *Built-in module interface for easy expansion plug &amp; play-system *Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Preparation of individual potencies combination with bioenergetic methods (EAV, BFD, etc.) Preparation of auto-nosodes (e.g. with Sekrete, Exkrete) Diagnosis of allergies and intolerances Spezielle Ergänzungsmöglichkeiten Plug&amp;play-system allows supplement with the diagnosis device Akuport M1+, theray device Akuport MT and bioresonance MR2 to complete therapy unit (Akuport Tower) Extensive special accessories, e.g. screened output beaker Scope of Delivery Akuport D-tec combination with Akuport MR2 1 Akuport D-tec 1 Power cord (onward transmission) 1 operation manual Akuport D-tec as stand alone version with Retec 2000CP, Vistron or external device 1 Akuport D-tec 1 Power supply 1 Connection cable (Chinch-Chinch) 1 Cover cap (in housing design) 1 operation manual Dimensions (WxHxD): 16x6x15cm, Weight ca. 200g Kindling Plug&amp;Play-system Akuport MR2/D-tec Akuport M1+/MR2/D-tec Akuport M1+/MT/MR2/D-tec Vistron/D-tec </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Retec 2000 CP Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance &gt;&gt; Retec 2000 CP Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Retec 2000 CP Bioresonance Software-controlled bioresonance device for universal and versatile resonance application with more than 300 protocols. Through the multi-functional setting of all parameters, the Retec 2000 C sets unique, forward-thinking standards for resonance application. It is operated combination with externally connected PC (Notebook). The matching software impress you with its self-explanatory user interface and it supports the treatment process through sorted indicator lists, which can be targeted to the symptom. With the help of optically displayed complement of electrodes and equipping the output flask, one can rapidly learn to use it. Work with multi-protocol to run down up to 5 programs automaticaly. Or use the detailed user interface to adjust all needed parameters manually . If you wish you can store them. Even the possibility of electronical potentizing is included. Multi-protocol Multi-protocol mode gives you the oppertunity to choose out of more than 300 protocols 5 protocols which be executed consecutively. The multi-protocol can be stored for next session with your client. Details Detail-mode for editing or creating individual protocols. Changes or settings can be reached by clicking on the switch symbol or its marking field. If parameter unit is assigned to the switch symbol (e.g. amplifier setting) window opens into which the value is then written. The values can be increased (arrow up) or decreased (arrow down) by clicking on the arrows. Potentizing Electonical potentation is valided by Dr.Würthle. By using harmonical and dis-harmonical informations potentizing up to D100 is possible. Kindling Retec 2000CP Therapy Bipolar therapy device Integrated input and output panels *Kindling special External flask expansion through two inputs and outputs each Differential procedure, no environmental influences during transfer *Kindling special Easy use of the Retec hardware and clear menu design the software Can be delegated Illustrated accessory suggestions therapy selection *Kindling special Simple updating procedure by means of self-installing CD-ROM More than 300 fixed programs sorted by indications Frequency range up to 1,000,000 Hz Filter range up to 100,000 Hz Automatic belt run and wobble operation Individually adjustable amplification up to 100-fold up to decreasing increments by 0.01 Direct and inverse switching Separator-switching (H, DI), direct and inverse (A, AI) 50 Hz frequency filter (interfering field suppression) Test function of output amplified with wires *Kindling special Treatment control with LED-display *Kindling special Display of remaining treatment time Power supply using medical power supply – Optional: operation using rechargeable battery Easy-to-read operating displays Accessories tray on top of device Housing designed to be compatible with Kindling EAV Combi-2 High resistance to interference through external PC Compatible with all commercially available PCs (Windows XP, Vista, Windows7, Windows8) with CD-ROM-drive and free USB-Port Kindling Special ! You find this feature that price categroy only with Kindling! Applications Therapy with more than 300 fixed programs sorted by indications Direct and inverse therapy Medication transfer using direct transfer Diverting using inverse transfer beaker configuration: input, e.g. nosodes, viruses, bacteria, secretions, excretions, parasites, heavy metals, virtual database etc; outpatient , e.g. patient, medium, globuli etc. Multitherapy Potentizing Enter the oscillation patterns the Homopath software Special Supplemental Options The Akuport MR2 can be used as individual device and expanded at any time with EAV Combi-2 Use of virtual medication using the software programs Meditest and Homopath Extensive special accessories, e. g. screened output beaker Scope of Delivery 1 Pair of hand electrodes, brass 1 Pair of foot electrodes, brass 1 Pair of rubber electrode 1 Magnetic field electrode, lite 1 Magnetic field electrode, strong 1 Ointment electrode 1 Magnetic field mat 2 Paar Retecleitungen 2m 2 Pairs of screened wires, 2m 3 Petri dishes Software Retec2000pro on CD-ROM USB wire Medical power supply Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 20x8x38cm, Weight ca. 1700g Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Combi-2/Retec 2000C EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Akuport MR2 Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Bioresonance &gt;&gt; Akuport MR2 Kindling EASY Akuport MR2 Retec 2000 CP Akuport D-tec Literature | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Akuport MR2 Bioresonance Modular device for resonance therapy – as stand-alone version or can be combined with the EAV diagnostic device Akuport M1+. The Kindling Akuport MR2 expands EAV diagnosis with modern resonance therapy. The body’s own physiological oscillations or externally assigned oscillation information regulates and stabilises the body’s energetic meridians, activating and strengthening the body’s own healing powers. Inverse and direct operations are used here for broad spectrum of frequencies. Through combination with virtual medications from the software programs, the scope of application can be greatly expanded. Kindling Akuport MR2 Therapy *Large frequency range through to 1,000,000 Hz *High and low pass for acute and degenerative treatment Continuous amplification through 60-fold, clearly adjustable Direct and inverse therapy *Integrated input and output panels *Differential procedure, no environmental influences during transfer External flask expansion through two inputs and outputs each Broad indicator spectrum Timer switch Therapy control using LED-display *Power supply from mains with medical power supply *Built-in module interface for easy expansion plug &amp; play-system *Kindling Special! You only find these features this price range at Kindling! Applications Direct and inverse therapy Medication transfer using direct transfer Diverting using inverse transfer beaker configuration: input, e.g. nosodes, viruses, bacteria, secretions, excretions, parasites, heavy metals, virtual database etc; outpatient, e.g. patient, medium, globuli etc. Enter the oscillation patterns the Homopath software Special Supplemental Options The Akuport MR2 can be used as individual device and expanded at any time with the Akuport M1+ and/or Akuport MT by plug&amp;play system. Use of virtual medication using the software programs Meditest and Homopath Extensive special accessories, e. g. screened output beaker Scope of Delivery Pair of handelectrodes, brass Pair of screened wires for hand electrodes Glas beaker Petri dish Cover with integrated accessory tray Differential cover Medical power supply Operating instructions Dimensions (WxHxD): 16x11x15cm, Weight ca. 400g Ground plate: 26x23cm Approved medical product compliant with EN Guideline 93/42/EWG Appendix II Kindling Plug&amp;Play-System Akuport M1+/MR2 Modul combination Akuport MR2/D-tec Modul combination Akuport Tower Modul combination Akuport M1+/MT/MR2 EG-Declaration of Conformity </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Company History Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company &gt;&gt; Company History Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Company History 1956 Marie-Luise Kindling founded the company Hannover 1956 Nervenpunktdetektor 1 for point localisation 1959 Nervenpunktdetektor 2 with measurement display 1966 Nervenpunktdetektor 3 with measurement display and therapy unit 1972 Nervenpunktdetektor 4 the first battery powered EAV device 1978 Nervenpunktdetektor 4B Transistorized EAV device 1980 Transition of the Kindling Company to Kindling GmbH located Hildesheim Owner and Managing Director: Franz Schulz 1980 Akuport M EAV travelling device 1983 Kindling 2000 Comfortable EAV device with pressure reading 1985 Computer-aided EAV with the software ELADI (MS-DOS) and HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer (ATARI) 1987 Presentation of the EAV devices to Dr. Voll 1988 Admission into the Int. Ärztegesellschaft für EAV by president Dr. Fehrenbach 1990 Software ELADI MT with medicine testing 1993 Presentation of the RETEC therapy (Bioresonance) through the device RETEC 2000 1994 EAV-Combi 2 replaces the Nervenpunktdetektor 4B 1995 ELADI VT Software with virtually medicine testing 1996 Software HOMOPATH Drs. Rossmann / Mayer as Windows version 1996 Computer-aided EAV-System-Diagnostic with Kindling 2000 and Retec 2000 1997 RETEC 3000 Computergesteuerte, 2 Kanal multiplex, Resonanztherapie 1998 Relocation to Gropiusstrasse extension of the production 1999 Cooperation with MBA GmbH for sales and service Germany 1999 First Certification acc. to ISO-Norm 9000 2000 Akuport Plug-and-Play system M1, MT and MR 2002 The new EAV-Combi-2 2003 Kindling 2000s updated version modern design 2003 Curator device for light therapy acc. to Global Scaling cooperation with the I.R.E.F. 2004 Retec 2000c Compact device with new software 2004 USB technology for software 2005 Certification acc. to Medical Devices - Quality Management Systems EN ISO 13485 2005 Company anniversary 25 years Kindling Hildesheim 2007 Akuport MR2 successor of the Akuport MR 2008 Change of management to Dipl.-Des. Kerstin Abrams Dipl.-Ing. Eduard Abrams 2008 Canadian Certification CAN/CSA ISO 13485:2003 2009 Vistron the new generation of EAV devices 2011 Akuport D-tec potentizer Nervenpunktdetektor 4B 1978 Akuport - EAV-Reisegerät 1980 Kindling 2000 1983 Kindling 2000 1990 Retec2000 1993 Kindling 2000S Kombination Retec 2000C </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> Quality Management Home Our Company Electroacupuncture Bioresonance Model Combinations Accessories Software Seminars Distributors Links You are here: &gt;&gt; Our Company &gt;&gt; Quality Management Quality Management Certification Company History People Contact Imprint General Terms and Conditions | Kontakt | Impressum | AGBs | Quality Management Since 1999, Kindling GmbH has developed Quality Management System focused on legal stipulations and strategy, order to meet to the highest quality requirements the area of medical technology. The Quality Management System DIN ISO 13485:2007 is monitored and certified by TÜV NORD CERT GmbH. [Certification] To ensure the quality of our products, processes and service, our work is governed by the following principles: Our Customers Our customers are of the highest importance to us. For this reason, we have to understand their current and future needs, meet their demands and strive to exceed all of their expectations. Meeting customer demands requires that we constantly maintain high level of quality. A fair quality-to-performance ratio our products is very important to us. For this reason, we strive to avoid unnecessary costs order to keep the prices of our products reasonable. Commissions from our customers be quickly and reliably fulfilled. Our Goals Constant improvement, as well as the maintenance and effectiveness of the Quality Management Systems of our company, are permanent goals that allow us to guarantee the quality of our products. Kindling GmbH is pledged to policy of quality, and all employees are called to conscientiously and actively securing the quality of our products, processes and service within their particular work environments. Our Employees Our employees are the essence of our company, at all levels. Complete involvement of our employees makes it possible to develop their skills for the benefit of the company. The principle of fault prevention takes precedence over that of troubleshooting for all of our employees. Systematic Project Management and the use of different methods and techniques for testing guarantees that the product fulfils the required quality demands. The qualification and validation of our production processes assures that the specified product quality be achieved. </fragment> </item> </root> 