<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> <root> <item> <fragment> RETAILERS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS RETAILERS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Bitte wählen Sie gewünschte Land anschließend Stadt ... LAND Land auswählen... Austria Azerbaijan Belgium Canada Denmark Germany Great Britain Greece Ireland Latvia Luxembourg Netherlands Poland Russia Switzerland Ukraine USA STADT Stadt auswählen... instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGENCIES — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR AUSTRIA PERSONAL-DRESSROOM HORST STEINACKER FASHION PALAIS 1. STOCK STUDIO 14 ALTE MATTSEERSTRAßE 26 AT - 5101 BERGHEIM BEI SALZBURG +43662650666 horst.steinacker@personal-dressroom.at Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR BELGIUM PARALLÈLE BVBA J.VAN ELEWIJCKSTRAAT 52 1853 STROMBEEK-BEVER / BELGIUM +3222679955 audrey@parallele.be Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR CANADA BAILEY INTERNATIONAL 52 AVENUE LOCKHART H3P1X8 MONT-ROYAL / QUÉBEC +1514895 78 98 marysebailey@bell.net Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR THE NETHERLANDS S.M.L.XL. AGENTUREN FASHION HOUSE 1.05 KON. WILHELMINAPLEIN 8-10 1062 HK AMSTERDAM / NETHERLANDS +31206177971 info@smlxlagenturen.nl Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENGY FOR POLAND MAJKA REINHARDT SP.Z.O.O. ULICA JODLOWA 9 83-330 GLINCZ / POLAND +48587330791 majka@majkareinhardt.pl Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR RUSSIA NK FASHION, MODEMARKETING UND VERTRIEBSBERATUNG STETTINER STRAßE 35 70825 KORNTAL-MÜNCHINGEN +4971151870729 nk@nkfashion.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR SWITZERLAND FASHION LINE AG SEESTRAßE 112 8803 RÜSCHLIKON / SWITZERLAND +41447045904 b.schmid@fashion-line.ch Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> SHOWROOMS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SHOWROOMS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM DÜSSELDORF CONTACT PERSON: PETRA EMPEL KENNEDY PARK KAISERSWERTHER STR. 119 40474 DÜSSELDORF +49211943277 duesseldorf@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM HAMBURG CONTACT PERSON: NICOLE BROCKMANN NEUER WALL 80 20354  HAMBURG +494038613200 hamburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM MÜNCHEN CONTACT PERSON: ESTHER OSTHUES GOLDBERG STUDIOS MÜLLERSTRAßE 46 A 80469 MÜNCHEN muenchen@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> FLAGSHIP STORES — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 26, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE HAMBURG NEUER WALL 80 20354  Hamburg +494027144998 store-hamburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE FRANKFURT KAISERHOFSTRAßE 6 60313  FRANKFURT +496913014896 store-frankfurt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE MÜNCHEN FÜNF HÖFE THEATINERSTRAßE 15 80333  MÜNCHEN +498944447040 store-muenchen@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE SYLT BRADERUPER WEG 1 LADEN 3 25999 KAMPEN/ SYLT +494651446488 store-sylt@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> SERVICE — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SERVICE SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS KONTAKTIERN SIE UNS: ST.EMILE Josef Reis GmbH &amp; Co.KG Wallstraße 6 63839 Kleinwallstadt Tel.: +49602266240 Fax: +496022662435 office@st-emile.de NEWSLETTER ANMELDUNG Um aktuelle Meldungen Kollektionen, Kampagnen, Events Sale-Angeboten erhalten, tragen Sie bitte Ihren Namen Ihre E-Mail-Adresse unten stehende Felder ein. First Name Last Name Email Address ANMELDEN Datenschutz wichtig halten ein. Liebe Kundin, Kunde danken Ihnen für Ihr Interesse ST.EMILE. Von an, Sie Erste/r über Kollektionen, Events News informiert. Sollten Sie Informationen benötigen, wenden Sie bitte unseren Kunden- Service Telefonnummer: +49 6022 66240. Mit Grüßen Ihr ST.EMILE Team KATALOGBESTELLUNG Vorname * Nachname * E-Mail Adresse Straße * Hausnummer * Postleitzahl * Stadt * Land * Liebe Kundin, Kunde Merci, Sie unseren aktuellen ST.EMILE Katalog bestellt haben. In nächsten Tagen Ihnen postalisch zukommen lassen - wünschen Spaß Schmökern senden beste Grüße. Ihr ST.EMILE Team P.S. Bei Fragen steht Ihnen Kunden-Service Telefonnummer +49 6022 66240 gerne jederzeit Verfügung. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> CAREER — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS CAREER BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER BE A part of St.Emile CAREER Sollte passende Stelle für Sie angezeigt werden, freuen über Ihre Initiativ-Bewerbung office@st-emile.de OFFENE STELLEN Verkaufsmitarbeiterin 120 STD. für ST.EMILE STORE Designer Outlet Berlin, PDF Download Aushilfe 450 Euro Basis für ST.EMILE STORE im Designer Outlet Berlin, PDF Download instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> PRESS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS PRESS BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER VOGUE NR 12_2014 Seite 262: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: KATHRIN SCHIFFNER Fotos: JULIA NONI GALA NR.47_2014 Seite 46: ST.EMILE DRESS Produktion: SEBASTIAN STEIN Fotos: PR MAXI Nr.1_2015 Seite 39: ST.EMILE blouse &amp; trousers left Produktion: ANJA NOLTENIUS Fotos: PHILIPP RATHMER WOMAN_Nr.11_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE COAT Produktion: JAKOB SCHAEFER Fotos: PR GALA Nr.42_2014 Seite : ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: SEBASTIAN STEIN Fotos: PR TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT Nr.46_2014 Seite 59: ST.EMILE LOOKBOOK Produktion: NADINE LOHNER Fotos: PR MYWAY Nr.12_2014 Seite 116: ST.EMILE DRESS Produktion: TINI RATHE Fotos: GISI RAMEKEN BRIGITTE NR.1_2015 Seite 24: ST.EMILE COMPLETE LOOK Produktion: JANA KRUSE Fotos: SEVIM ASLAN INTOUCH STYLE Nr.6_2014 Seite 23: ST.EMILE SKIRT Produktion: THORSTEN REDMANN Fotos: PR TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT_Nr.47_2014 Seite 64: ST.EMILE PREVIEW AW15 Produktion: NADINE LOHNER Fotos: PR DONNA NR.11_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE PULLOVER &amp; COVER Produktion: PIA LEONIE KNOLL Fotos: JAAN-ERIC FISCHER BRIGITTE NR.23_2014 S. 28: ST.EMILE TROUSERS / S.32 CAPE Produktion: JESSICA FEIX Fotos: DIRK MERTEN BRIGITTE WOMAN Nr.12_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE BLOUSE Produktion: JOANA CLARO Fotos: FREDRIK MAGNUSON TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT Nr.31_2014 Seite 47: ST.EMILE SHOWROOM LOOK Produktion: Nadine Lohner Fotos: Nadine Lohner GRAZIA Nr. 59_2014 Seite 59: ST.EMILE BLOUSE Produktion: ANASTASIA VERLMINSKI Fotos: PR JOLIE PAD Oktober_2014 Seite 5: ST.EMILE JACKET Streetstyle-Heft Fotos: PR VOGUE FASHION NEWS AW14 Seite 6: ST.EMILE LOOKBOOK Produktion: Fotos: PR EXPERIENCE MAGAZIN Nr.2_2015 Seite 76: ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: ALBERT KELLER Fotos: PR GRAZIA Nr.48_2014 Seite 72: ST.EMILE SKIRT Snake Print Produktion: ANASTASIA VELMINSKI Fotos: PR MYSELF Oktober 2014 Seite 94: ST.EMILE TROUSERS Produktion: THERESA PICHLER Fotos: TOBIAS LUNDKVIST MYWAY Nr.9_2014 Seite 22: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: MICHAELA GERGANOFF Fotos: DET KEMPKE COSMOPOLITAN Oktober_2014 Seite 76: ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: SABINE IRGER Fotos: LEO KRUMBACHER MYSELF November 2014 Seite 104: ST.EMILE PULLOVER WHITE Produktion: JULIA ZIRPERL Fotos: PR GRAZIA Nr. 52_2014 Seite 57: ST.EMILE BLOUSE BLUE Produktion: ANASTASIA VELMINSKI Fotos: PR FREUNDIN NR.25_2014 Seite 33: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: STEPHANIE RAU Fotos: NICK LEARY TM MAGAZIN NR.9_2014 Seite 42: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: SILKE BUECKER Fotos: BJOERN GIESBRECHT MYWAY Nr.7_2014 Seite 24: ST.EMILE TOP Produktion: MICHAELA GERGANOFF Fotos: SONJA SCHAEFER TM Nr.1_2015 Seite 73: ST.EMILE FASHION SKETCH Produktion: VANESSA PECHERSKI Fotos: ST.EMILE DESIGN instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> NEWS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS NEWS BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER Marta Szymendera verstärkt Kreativ Team ST.EMILE Die Designerin, Mitte 2013 über Jahre Head- später Senior Head of Creative Management BOSS WOMAN tätig zuvor fünf Jahre Designerin STRENESSE GABRIELE STREHLE, ST.EMILE Kreativ Team Februar 2015 Beraterin unterstützen. In Zeitraum Kreativ Team Uwe Jürdens ST.EMILE DNA herangeführt, „die Heritage DNA ST.EMILE Zukunftswerte“, Uwe Jürdens. Uwe Jürdens weiter: „Schon Pre Collection für Herbst/ Winter 2015 gezeigt, verschiedene Maßnahmen z.B. deutlichen Straffung Kollektion spitzeren Aussage richtigen Weg eingeschlagen haben“. Nach erfolgreich verlaufenden Beraterzeitraum beiderseits vereinbart, Frau Szymendera zukünftig „Head of Design“ benennen. Christoph Heuter übernimmt technische Leitung ST.EMILE Christoph Heuter (47) übernimmt sofort technische Leitung ST. EMILE Kleinwallstadt somit Nachfolge Sabine Weingarten an. Bevor ST. EMILE wechselte, Düsseldorf Elégance GmbH Director Product tätig. Internationale Erfahrung sammelte Laurèl GmbH München, Tätigkeit Geschäftsleitung Funktion technischen Leiters für Einkaufsbüros Primera Group Hongkong Shanghai Member of the Board mitverantwortlich war. Weitere Führungserfahrungen Fachkompetenz sammelte anderem namhaften Firmen Hugo Boss Switzerland (Head of Quality Management). ST.EMILE @ Vogue Fashion Night out Düsseldorf Wir gefreut VOGUE Fashion Night Out Jahr 2014 - diesmal größer - feiern. Alle VOGUE-Fans ST.EMILE Flagship Store Grabenstraße 17 rundum entertained. Mit ST.EMILE Fenster-Inszenierungen, Model-Botschafterinnen, Instore Outfit-Catwalks, Gewinnspielen, limitierten "VFNO-Specials" und, logisch: Lounge Musik Drinks. Die ST.EMILE Herzenssache: Zusätzlich Programmpunkten ST.EMILE Store Shwe Shwe Püppchen Charity VOGUE Initiative ST.EMILE Corporate Facebook Seite liebevollen Behind the Scenes-Story vorgestellt.  WWW.FACEBOOK.COM/ST.EMILE Business time Berlin ST.EMILE präsentiert Frühjahr/ Sommer Kollektion 2015 Fachpublikum Messe „show and order“ Berlin We love... die faszinierende Symbiose roughen alten Kraftwerk farbenfrohen, hochwertigen Kollektionen show &amp; order gezeigt werden! Leichtigkeit Coolness unserem Messestand XXL Balloons, luftig Takt Live-Musik "mittanzten". Frühlingserwachen by ST.EMILE Mit hauchzarten Kuss voller Frühlingsgefühle Kundinnen Winterschlaf „geweckt“. Wir inspirierenden Lifestyle-Kosmos Fashion, Beauty Styling eingetaucht köstlichen, Leckereien liebevoll zubereiteten Drinks Fashion Styling Promi Stylistin Violetta Vio angeboten, Stars Sternchen bekommen. Frühlingspoesie pur! instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> BRAND — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS BRAND BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER „ST.EMILE“ bedeutet, lässige COOLNESS, WEIBLICHKEIT GLAMOUR miteinander verschmelzen. Trendorientiert, exklusiv, höchster Qualität perfekter Passform steht Kollektion für HIGH FASHION einem  FEMININEN SMART &amp; CASUAL LOOK. FACETTENREICH EINZELTEILIG. „WOMAN PUR“ Dieses Credo vorherrschenden Zeitgeist verknüpfen Essenz Kollektion. Modernität, Design Qualität Stelle. Ohne Kompromisse! Eine Kollektion, Ebenen überzeugt. Wir setzen Saison für Saison HERZBLUT ENGAGEMENT daran, Titel „Fashion-Label“ neu verdienen. Durch HOCHWERTIGSTE VERARBEITUNG Verwendung FEINSTER MATERIALIEN Trendstücken LIEBLINGSTEILE. Innovativ ambitioniert kreieren raffinierte Schnitte PERFEKTER PASSFORM unterstreichen Persönlichkeit Kundin, verkleiden. In enger Zusammenarbeit namhaftesten Handelspartnern In- Ausland, ST.EMILE Flagship-Stores deutschen Großstädten Luxusinsel Sylt präsentieren zudem INTERNATIONALES Unternehmen, DNA unverkennbar trägt Saison für Saison Zukunft transponiert. Das Motto „Woman pure“ gilt heute. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> MAIN COLLECTION — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS MAIN COLLECTION COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION LUXURY CASUAL OVERSIZED STRICKPULLIS UND KANIN-CARDIGANS SORGEN FÜR LUXURIÖSE CASUAL-MOMENTE. AN DER BUSINESSLINIE MACHEN DEZENTE LEODRUCKE IN ANTRAZIT AUF GRAU BEI CASHGORA-MÄNTELN UND TULPENKLEIDERN EINEN STARKEN JOB. IM DUETT MIT TOUGHEM FUCHSIA ZEIGEN SICH SCHMALE  PENCIL-SKIRTS UND EIN STATEMENT-CASHMERE-TRENCH ALS FIRST ROW PIECES. ZAUBERHAFTE ZOPF-PULLIS AUS COSY-ALPACA-STRICK ZU GREIGEFARBENEN PAILLETTENRÖCKEN UND CRÊPE-HOSEN IN SOFTEM PEACH - URBAN CHIC PAR EXCELLENCE. ENJOY ST.EMILE instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> PRE COLLECTION — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS PRE COLLECTION COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BLACK BEAUTY KLASSIKER UND RIESENGITTERDRUCKE BEWEISEN, DASS ES BEI SCHWARZ-WEISS KOMBIS NICHT KLEINKARIERT ZUGEHEN MUSS. COOL CAT KITT ZÄHMT SEINE FARBKAMERADEN CORAL UND AZURBLAU ZU EINEM STARKEN FARB-TEAM. GEMEINSAM FORMEN SIE GEOMETRICAL PRINTS AUF LAYER-RÖCKEN, SEIDENBLUSEN UND GROSSRHOMBEN AUF ZARTEM SOFTMERINO-STRICK. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashion AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION AUTUMN / WINTER ´15 ENTSPANNT UND ELEGANT ZUGLEICH - MIT KLAREN SCHNITTEN, FEINSTEN MATERIALIEN UND IN MONOCHROMEN FARBWELTEN. LUXURY CASUAL. GANZ EASY. SCHAUEN SIE SELBST! ENJOY ST.EMILE instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> CAREER — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS CAREER BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER BE A part of St.Emile CAREER Sollte passende Stelle für Sie angezeigt werden, freuen über Ihre Initiativ-Bewerbung office@st-emile.de OFFENE STELLEN Verkaufsmitarbeiterin 120 STD. für ST.EMILE STORE Designer Outlet Berlin, PDF Download Aushilfe 450 Euro Basis für ST.EMILE STORE im Designer Outlet Berlin, PDF Download instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> SERVICE — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SERVICE SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS KONTAKTIERN SIE UNS: ST.EMILE Josef Reis GmbH &amp; Co.KG Wallstraße 6 63839 Kleinwallstadt Tel.: +49602266240 Fax: +496022662435 office@st-emile.de NEWSLETTER ANMELDUNG Um aktuelle Meldungen Kollektionen, Kampagnen, Events Sale-Angeboten erhalten, tragen Sie bitte Ihren Namen Ihre E-Mail-Adresse unten stehende Felder ein. First Name Last Name Email Address ANMELDEN Datenschutz wichtig halten ein. Liebe Kundin, Kunde danken Ihnen für Ihr Interesse ST.EMILE. Von an, Sie Erste/r über Kollektionen, Events News informiert. Sollten Sie Informationen benötigen, wenden Sie bitte unseren Kunden- Service Telefonnummer: +49 6022 66240. Mit Grüßen Ihr ST.EMILE Team KATALOGBESTELLUNG Vorname * Nachname * E-Mail Adresse Straße * Hausnummer * Postleitzahl * Stadt * Land * Liebe Kundin, Kunde Merci, Sie unseren aktuellen ST.EMILE Katalog bestellt haben. In nächsten Tagen Ihnen postalisch zukommen lassen - wünschen Spaß Schmökern senden beste Grüße. Ihr ST.EMILE Team P.S. Bei Fragen steht Ihnen Kunden-Service Telefonnummer +49 6022 66240 gerne jederzeit Verfügung. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> BRAND — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS BRAND BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER „ST.EMILE“ bedeutet, lässige COOLNESS, WEIBLICHKEIT GLAMOUR miteinander verschmelzen. Trendorientiert, exklusiv, höchster Qualität perfekter Passform steht Kollektion für HIGH FASHION einem  FEMININEN SMART &amp; CASUAL LOOK. FACETTENREICH EINZELTEILIG. „WOMAN PUR“ Dieses Credo vorherrschenden Zeitgeist verknüpfen Essenz Kollektion. Modernität, Design Qualität Stelle. Ohne Kompromisse! Eine Kollektion, Ebenen überzeugt. Wir setzen Saison für Saison HERZBLUT ENGAGEMENT daran, Titel „Fashion-Label“ neu verdienen. Durch HOCHWERTIGSTE VERARBEITUNG Verwendung FEINSTER MATERIALIEN Trendstücken LIEBLINGSTEILE. Innovativ ambitioniert kreieren raffinierte Schnitte PERFEKTER PASSFORM unterstreichen Persönlichkeit Kundin, verkleiden. In enger Zusammenarbeit namhaftesten Handelspartnern In- Ausland, ST.EMILE Flagship-Stores deutschen Großstädten Luxusinsel Sylt präsentieren zudem INTERNATIONALES Unternehmen, DNA unverkennbar trägt Saison für Saison Zukunft transponiert. Das Motto „Woman pure“ gilt heute. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> FLAGSHIP STORES — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 26, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE HAMBURG NEUER WALL 80 20354  Hamburg +494027144998 store-hamburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE FRANKFURT KAISERHOFSTRAßE 6 60313  FRANKFURT +496913014896 store-frankfurt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE MÜNCHEN FÜNF HÖFE THEATINERSTRAßE 15 80333  MÜNCHEN +498944447040 store-muenchen@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE SYLT BRADERUPER WEG 1 LADEN 3 25999 KAMPEN/ SYLT +494651446488 store-sylt@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> PRESS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS PRESS BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER VOGUE NR 12_2014 Seite 262: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: KATHRIN SCHIFFNER Fotos: JULIA NONI GALA NR.47_2014 Seite 46: ST.EMILE DRESS Produktion: SEBASTIAN STEIN Fotos: PR MAXI Nr.1_2015 Seite 39: ST.EMILE blouse &amp; trousers left Produktion: ANJA NOLTENIUS Fotos: PHILIPP RATHMER WOMAN_Nr.11_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE COAT Produktion: JAKOB SCHAEFER Fotos: PR GALA Nr.42_2014 Seite : ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: SEBASTIAN STEIN Fotos: PR TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT Nr.46_2014 Seite 59: ST.EMILE LOOKBOOK Produktion: NADINE LOHNER Fotos: PR MYWAY Nr.12_2014 Seite 116: ST.EMILE DRESS Produktion: TINI RATHE Fotos: GISI RAMEKEN BRIGITTE NR.1_2015 Seite 24: ST.EMILE COMPLETE LOOK Produktion: JANA KRUSE Fotos: SEVIM ASLAN INTOUCH STYLE Nr.6_2014 Seite 23: ST.EMILE SKIRT Produktion: THORSTEN REDMANN Fotos: PR TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT_Nr.47_2014 Seite 64: ST.EMILE PREVIEW AW15 Produktion: NADINE LOHNER Fotos: PR DONNA NR.11_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE PULLOVER &amp; COVER Produktion: PIA LEONIE KNOLL Fotos: JAAN-ERIC FISCHER BRIGITTE NR.23_2014 S. 28: ST.EMILE TROUSERS / S.32 CAPE Produktion: JESSICA FEIX Fotos: DIRK MERTEN BRIGITTE WOMAN Nr.12_2014 Seite 32: ST.EMILE BLOUSE Produktion: JOANA CLARO Fotos: FREDRIK MAGNUSON TEXTILWIRTSCHAFT Nr.31_2014 Seite 47: ST.EMILE SHOWROOM LOOK Produktion: Nadine Lohner Fotos: Nadine Lohner GRAZIA Nr. 59_2014 Seite 59: ST.EMILE BLOUSE Produktion: ANASTASIA VERLMINSKI Fotos: PR JOLIE PAD Oktober_2014 Seite 5: ST.EMILE JACKET Streetstyle-Heft Fotos: PR VOGUE FASHION NEWS AW14 Seite 6: ST.EMILE LOOKBOOK Produktion: Fotos: PR EXPERIENCE MAGAZIN Nr.2_2015 Seite 76: ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: ALBERT KELLER Fotos: PR GRAZIA Nr.48_2014 Seite 72: ST.EMILE SKIRT Snake Print Produktion: ANASTASIA VELMINSKI Fotos: PR MYSELF Oktober 2014 Seite 94: ST.EMILE TROUSERS Produktion: THERESA PICHLER Fotos: TOBIAS LUNDKVIST MYWAY Nr.9_2014 Seite 22: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: MICHAELA GERGANOFF Fotos: DET KEMPKE COSMOPOLITAN Oktober_2014 Seite 76: ST.EMILE VEST Produktion: SABINE IRGER Fotos: LEO KRUMBACHER MYSELF November 2014 Seite 104: ST.EMILE PULLOVER WHITE Produktion: JULIA ZIRPERL Fotos: PR GRAZIA Nr. 52_2014 Seite 57: ST.EMILE BLOUSE BLUE Produktion: ANASTASIA VELMINSKI Fotos: PR FREUNDIN NR.25_2014 Seite 33: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: STEPHANIE RAU Fotos: NICK LEARY TM MAGAZIN NR.9_2014 Seite 42: ST.EMILE PULLOVER Produktion: SILKE BUECKER Fotos: BJOERN GIESBRECHT MYWAY Nr.7_2014 Seite 24: ST.EMILE TOP Produktion: MICHAELA GERGANOFF Fotos: SONJA SCHAEFER TM Nr.1_2015 Seite 73: ST.EMILE FASHION SKETCH Produktion: VANESSA PECHERSKI Fotos: ST.EMILE DESIGN instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> PRE COLLECTION — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS PRE COLLECTION COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BLACK BEAUTY KLASSIKER UND RIESENGITTERDRUCKE BEWEISEN, DASS ES BEI SCHWARZ-WEISS KOMBIS NICHT KLEINKARIERT ZUGEHEN MUSS. COOL CAT KITT ZÄHMT SEINE FARBKAMERADEN CORAL UND AZURBLAU ZU EINEM STARKEN FARB-TEAM. GEMEINSAM FORMEN SIE GEOMETRICAL PRINTS AUF LAYER-RÖCKEN, SEIDENBLUSEN UND GROSSRHOMBEN AUF ZARTEM SOFTMERINO-STRICK. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR SWITZERLAND FASHION LINE AG SEESTRAßE 112 8803 RÜSCHLIKON / SWITZERLAND +41447045904 b.schmid@fashion-line.ch AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SHOWROOMS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM MÜNCHEN CONTACT PERSON: ESTHER OSTHUES GOLDBERG STUDIOS MÜLLERSTRAßE 46 A 80469 MÜNCHEN muenchen@st-emile.de SHOWROOMS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE SYLT BRADERUPER WEG 1 LADEN 3 25999 KAMPEN/ SYLT +494651446488 store-sylt@st-emile.de FLAGSHIP STORES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE MÜNCHEN FÜNF HÖFE THEATINERSTRAßE 15 80333  MÜNCHEN +498944447040 store-muenchen@st-emile.de FLAGSHIP STORES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE FRANKFURT KAISERHOFSTRAßE 6 60313  FRANKFURT +496913014896 store-frankfurt@st-emile.de FLAGSHIP STORES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 26, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE HAMBURG NEUER WALL 80 20354  Hamburg +494027144998 store-hamburg@st-emile.de FLAGSHIP STORES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> FLAGSHIP STORES — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS FLAGSHIP STORES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 26, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE HAMBURG NEUER WALL 80 20354  Hamburg +494027144998 store-hamburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE FRANKFURT KAISERHOFSTRAßE 6 60313  FRANKFURT +496913014896 store-frankfurt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 25, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE MÜNCHEN FÜNF HÖFE THEATINERSTRAßE 15 80333  MÜNCHEN +498944447040 store-muenchen@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE STORE SYLT BRADERUPER WEG 1 LADEN 3 25999 KAMPEN/ SYLT +494651446488 store-sylt@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SHOWROOMS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM HAMBURG CONTACT PERSON: NICOLE BROCKMANN NEUER WALL 80 20354  HAMBURG +494038613200 hamburg@st-emile.de SHOWROOMS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SHOWROOMS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM DÜSSELDORF CONTACT PERSON: PETRA EMPEL KENNEDY PARK KAISERSWERTHER STR. 119 40474 DÜSSELDORF +49211943277 duesseldorf@st-emile.de SHOWROOMS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> SHOWROOMS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS SHOWROOMS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM DÜSSELDORF CONTACT PERSON: PETRA EMPEL KENNEDY PARK KAISERSWERTHER STR. 119 40474 DÜSSELDORF +49211943277 duesseldorf@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM HAMBURG CONTACT PERSON: NICOLE BROCKMANN NEUER WALL 80 20354  HAMBURG +494038613200 hamburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 ST.EMILE SHOWROOM MÜNCHEN CONTACT PERSON: ESTHER OSTHUES GOLDBERG STUDIOS MÜLLERSTRAßE 46 A 80469 MÜNCHEN muenchen@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR RUSSIA NK FASHION, MODEMARKETING UND VERTRIEBSBERATUNG STETTINER STRAßE 35 70825 KORNTAL-MÜNCHINGEN +4971151870729 nk@nkfashion.de AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENGY FOR POLAND MAJKA REINHARDT SP.Z.O.O. ULICA JODLOWA 9 83-330 GLINCZ / POLAND +48587330791 majka@majkareinhardt.pl AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR THE NETHERLANDS S.M.L.XL. AGENTUREN FASHION HOUSE 1.05 KON. WILHELMINAPLEIN 8-10 1062 HK AMSTERDAM / NETHERLANDS +31206177971 info@smlxlagenturen.nl AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR CANADA BAILEY INTERNATIONAL 52 AVENUE LOCKHART H3P1X8 MONT-ROYAL / QUÉBEC +1514895 78 98 marysebailey@bell.net AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR BELGIUM PARALLÈLE BVBA J.VAN ELEWIJCKSTRAAT 52 1853 STROMBEEK-BEVER / BELGIUM +3222679955 audrey@parallele.be AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR AUSTRIA PERSONAL-DRESSROOM HORST STEINACKER FASHION PALAIS 1. STOCK STUDIO 14 ALTE MATTSEERSTRAßE 26 AT - 5101 BERGHEIM BEI SALZBURG +43662650666 horst.steinacker@personal-dressroom.at AGENCIES Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> AGENCIES — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS AGENCIES SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR AUSTRIA PERSONAL-DRESSROOM HORST STEINACKER FASHION PALAIS 1. STOCK STUDIO 14 ALTE MATTSEERSTRAßE 26 AT - 5101 BERGHEIM BEI SALZBURG +43662650666 horst.steinacker@personal-dressroom.at Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR BELGIUM PARALLÈLE BVBA J.VAN ELEWIJCKSTRAAT 52 1853 STROMBEEK-BEVER / BELGIUM +3222679955 audrey@parallele.be Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR CANADA BAILEY INTERNATIONAL 52 AVENUE LOCKHART H3P1X8 MONT-ROYAL / QUÉBEC +1514895 78 98 marysebailey@bell.net Jasmin Langer January 24, 2015 AGENCY FOR THE NETHERLANDS S.M.L.XL. AGENTUREN FASHION HOUSE 1.05 KON. WILHELMINAPLEIN 8-10 1062 HK AMSTERDAM / NETHERLANDS +31206177971 info@smlxlagenturen.nl Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENGY FOR POLAND MAJKA REINHARDT SP.Z.O.O. ULICA JODLOWA 9 83-330 GLINCZ / POLAND +48587330791 majka@majkareinhardt.pl Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR RUSSIA NK FASHION, MODEMARKETING UND VERTRIEBSBERATUNG STETTINER STRAßE 35 70825 KORNTAL-MÜNCHINGEN +4971151870729 nk@nkfashion.de Jasmin Langer January 22, 2015 AGENCY FOR SWITZERLAND FASHION LINE AG SEESTRAßE 112 8803 RÜSCHLIKON / SWITZERLAND +41447045904 b.schmid@fashion-line.ch Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> MAIN COLLECTION — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS MAIN COLLECTION COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION LUXURY CASUAL OVERSIZED STRICKPULLIS UND KANIN-CARDIGANS SORGEN FÜR LUXURIÖSE CASUAL-MOMENTE. AN DER BUSINESSLINIE MACHEN DEZENTE LEODRUCKE IN ANTRAZIT AUF GRAU BEI CASHGORA-MÄNTELN UND TULPENKLEIDERN EINEN STARKEN JOB. IM DUETT MIT TOUGHEM FUCHSIA ZEIGEN SICH SCHMALE  PENCIL-SKIRTS UND EIN STATEMENT-CASHMERE-TRENCH ALS FIRST ROW PIECES. ZAUBERHAFTE ZOPF-PULLIS AUS COSY-ALPACA-STRICK ZU GREIGEFARBENEN PAILLETTENRÖCKEN UND CRÊPE-HOSEN IN SOFTEM PEACH - URBAN CHIC PAR EXCELLENCE. ENJOY ST.EMILE instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> OUTLETS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer May 26, 2015 WERTHEIM VILLAGE UNIT 35 ALMOSENBERG 97877  WERTHEIM +49342914652 wertheim@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET LANDQUART TARDISSTRAßE 80 UNIT 27 7302  LANDQUART / SWITZERLAND +41815445216 alpenrhein@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET BERLIN ALTER SPANDAUER WEG 1 / 42-43 14641 WUSTERMARK +493323423634 berlin@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 INGOLSTADT VILLAGE SHOP 87 OTTO-HAHN-STRAßE 1 85055 INGOLSTADT +498419516910 ingolstadt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET KLEINWALLSTADT WALLSTRAßE 6 63839 KLEINWALLSTADT +4960226624114 kleinwallstadt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 NEUMÜNSTER DESIGNER OUTLET EINHEIT 58 ODERSTRAßE 11 24539  NEUMÜNSTER +4943217552098 neumuenster@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET ROERMOND STADSWEIDE 4 6041 TD  ROERMOND / NETHERLANDS +31475550030 roermond@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SALZBURG KASERNENSTRAßE 1 SHOP 00.030 5073 WALS / AUSTRIA +43662857235 salzburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SOLTAU EINHEIT EG 0.52 GEWERBEGEBIET 29614 SOLTAU OST II RAHRSBERG 7 +4951919794685 soltau@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SOLTAU EINHEIT EG 0.52 GEWERBEGEBIET 29614 SOLTAU OST II RAHRSBERG 7 +4951919794685 soltau@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SALZBURG KASERNENSTRAßE 1 SHOP 00.030 5073 WALS / AUSTRIA +43662857235 salzburg@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET ROERMOND STADSWEIDE 4 6041 TD  ROERMOND / NETHERLANDS +31475550030 roermond@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 NEUMÜNSTER DESIGNER OUTLET EINHEIT 58 ODERSTRAßE 11 24539  NEUMÜNSTER +4943217552098 neumuenster@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET KLEINWALLSTADT WALLSTRAßE 6 63839 KLEINWALLSTADT +4960226624114 kleinwallstadt@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 INGOLSTADT VILLAGE SHOP 87 OTTO-HAHN-STRAßE 1 85055 INGOLSTADT +498419516910 ingolstadt@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET BERLIN ALTER SPANDAUER WEG 1 / 42-43 14641 WUSTERMARK +493323423634 berlin@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET LANDQUART TARDISSTRAßE 80 UNIT 27 7302  LANDQUART / SWITZERLAND +41815445216 alpenrhein@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> — ST.EMILE AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer May 26, 2015 WERTHEIM VILLAGE UNIT 35 ALMOSENBERG 97877  WERTHEIM +49342914652 wertheim@st-emile.de OUTLETS Older Newer Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> <item> <fragment> OUTLETS — Trend-oriented, exklusive, of the highest quality and perfect fit, the high fashion collection stands for feminine, casual and smart look. AUTUMN/WINTER 15 COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION ABOUT BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER CONTACT SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS COLLECTION PRE COLLECTION MAIN COLLECTION BRAND NEWS PRESS CAREER SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS OUTLETS SERVICE FLAGSHIP STORES SHOWROOMS AGENCIES RETAILERS OUTLETS Jasmin Langer May 26, 2015 WERTHEIM VILLAGE UNIT 35 ALMOSENBERG 97877  WERTHEIM +49342914652 wertheim@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET LANDQUART TARDISSTRAßE 80 UNIT 27 7302  LANDQUART / SWITZERLAND +41815445216 alpenrhein@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET BERLIN ALTER SPANDAUER WEG 1 / 42-43 14641 WUSTERMARK +493323423634 berlin@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 INGOLSTADT VILLAGE SHOP 87 OTTO-HAHN-STRAßE 1 85055 INGOLSTADT +498419516910 ingolstadt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET KLEINWALLSTADT WALLSTRAßE 6 63839 KLEINWALLSTADT +4960226624114 kleinwallstadt@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 NEUMÜNSTER DESIGNER OUTLET EINHEIT 58 ODERSTRAßE 11 24539  NEUMÜNSTER +4943217552098 neumuenster@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 OUTLET ROERMOND STADSWEIDE 4 6041 TD  ROERMOND / NETHERLANDS +31475550030 roermond@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SALZBURG KASERNENSTRAßE 1 SHOP 00.030 5073 WALS / AUSTRIA +43662857235 salzburg@st-emile.de Jasmin Langer January 23, 2015 DESIGNER OUTLET SOLTAU EINHEIT EG 0.52 GEWERBEGEBIET 29614 SOLTAU OST II RAHRSBERG 7 +4951919794685 soltau@st-emile.de Sidebar Title (H3) Morbi leo risus, porta ac consectetur ac, vestibulum at eros. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus. *This sidebar is displayed on all blog pages. It render on both the list and item views of each blog you create. instagram vimeo facebook IMPRINT ST.EMILE ST.EMILE is german fashionlabel and means melding of casual coolness, femininity and glamour. ST.EMILE / Josef Reis GmbH &amp; CO. KG | 6 Wallstraße, Kleinwallstadt, BY, 63839, Germany instagram vimeo facebook </fragment> </item> </root> 